But, um.
但是，嗯。
Hello. Hello.
你好。 你好。
Wait. Why am I here?
等待。 为什么我在这里？
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
Give me a second.
你稍等一会儿。
What the heck?
有没有搞错？
Oh. Oops.
哦。 哎呀。
OK. Ah.
好的。 啊。
Hello.
你好。
Hi, guys.
嗨，大家好。
Good morning.
早上好。
Good evening, everybody.
晚上好大家。
They're waiting for me.
他们在等我。
Let's get right into the game.
让我们直接进入游戏。
I think I just want to say hi there.
我想我只是想在那里打个招呼。
I love you guys a lot.
我非常爱你们。
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
Some of the notifications will be off
某些通知将在流中关闭，因此我们可以专注于与 Vox 的合作。
for the stream,
so we can just focus on the collab with Vox.
Ike and Reimu.
池和灵梦。
So I just want to say, like,
those will be off, but
所以我只想说，就像，那些会关闭，但是
I'll be reading through the donations,
and all the subs
我将通读捐款，所有的潜艇都在蘑菇结束或合作结束之后。
are after the mushrooms over
or after the collab's over.
Okay. Yeah, I'll be there.
好的。 是的，我会在那里。
I will be there.
我会在那里。
All right.
好的。
I think they're waiting for me, though.
不过，我想他们在等我。
I don't wanna keep them waiting
any longer, ok?
我不想让他们再等了，好吗？
Reimu just called me a bitch, so hold on
灵梦刚刚叫我婊子，等一下
OK, let me see.
好的，让我看看。
Where is he now? That's a reality?
他现在在哪里？ 那是现实吗？
No. Mm hmm.
不，嗯嗯。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, Hello.
哦你好。
Here you go.
干得好。
Hello. Here you go now.
你好。 现在给你。
Welcome back.
欢迎回来。
Hello. Hello. Hi.
你好。 你好。 你好。
Hello. Are you guys live too?
你好。 你们也住吗？
Yeah. OK, punk.
是的。 好吧，朋克。
Nice. Hi.
好的。 你好。
I mean, a bitch.
我的意思是，一个婊子。
We're, um. Yeah.
我们，嗯。 是的。
Well.
好。
Well, sorry.
嗯，对不起。
That was rude of me.
那是对我的粗鲁。
Bish Bish. There you go. Thanks lot.
比什比什。 你去吧。 非常感谢。
That's the one I know.
那是我认识的那个。
Yeah. There.
是的。 那里。
Yeah, there's. A big difference.
是的，有。 很大的不同。
She's you
她是你
know.
知道。
It's a lot more.
还有很多。
It's like,
它像是，
how do I put it?
我该怎么说？
One, one?
一一？
You got to know if you know, you know.
你要知道，如果你知道，你知道。
I think. If you know, You know.
我认为。 如果你知道，你知道。
You know.
你知道。
You know, you know.
你知道，你知道。
But I don't. Really friends.
但我没有。 真是朋友。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
Is everyone ready.
大家准备好了吗。
I don't know how to like when
we see I have to start right?
我不知道怎么样，当我们看到我必须开始对吗？
Well, I, I yeah there is a big button that
嗯，我，我是的，有一个大按钮可以开始游戏。
starts the game.
Is big button that's a start game. Really.
是一个开始游戏的大按钮。 真的。
Oh, there is a big one.
That's a start game. Yeah.
哦，有一个大的。 那是一个开始游戏。 是的。
You fucking.
你他妈
Hold on. I says I collect. I can.
坚持，稍等。 我说我收藏。 我可以。
Hold on, I can select the map
size, the difficulty and the lives.
等等，我可以选择地图大小、难度和生命。
If you go to the photos. Yeah.
如果你去看照片。 是的。
So all there's only
所以只有一个故事和不同的案例。 这意味着什么？ 是的。
one story and different cases.
What does that mean? Yeah.
Yeah, that this story, it's not just,
like, farcical, like just random pieces.
是的，这个故事，它不仅仅是，像，闹剧，像随机的片段。
I mean, you can do both
我的意思是，你可以两者都做
Oh. I'm not doing.
哦。 我没有做。
Do what do we do?
做我们做什么？
Want to seen some stuff? Story? cases?
想看一些东西吗？ 故事？ 案例？
Which one? Let's just do a story.
哪一个？ 让我们做一个故事。
I'll see the story.
我会看到这个故事。
Configuring your own character.
配置自己的角色。
Wait.How do you do that?
等等，你是怎么做到的？
You go to the tent.
你去帐篷。
Yeah,
but how do you change your character?
是的，但是你如何改变你的性格？
Like, completely? Boxes like. This.
像，完全？ 盒子之类的。 这。
No options for me.
我没有选择。
Yeah. Like you go to the tent.
是的。 就像你去帐篷一样。
That's different.
那是不同的。
I'm in the. Tents.
我在。 帐篷。
Go to the tent.
You can. Oh, I'm in the all.
去帐篷。 你可以。 哦，我在所有。
Oh, wait. I'm in. The tent.
等一下。 我在。帐篷。
But I don't have any o.
但是我没有任何o。
Press the arrows.
按箭头。
There's only, like, three character.
只有，就像，三个字符。
Pieces I'll be this baby girl.
件我将成为这个女婴。
I think I'm just a bearded man.
我想我只是一个留胡子的人。
I'm just going to be the stoner.
我只是要成为石匠。
That's.
那是。
Yeah.
是的。
OK. Do not make fun of this guy.
好的。 不要取笑这个家伙。
He's pecing. Done in the.
他在啄食。 中完成。
All right.
好的。
Reimu, you and vox are matching shirts.
灵梦，你和vox是相配的衬衫。
Aoh, adorable. I said, so we get to go
啊，可爱。 我说那我们走吧
let go of this stoner guy.
放开这个石匠。
You know, we can all be stoner together.
你知道，我们都可以在一起。
All right,
you guys ready? We get into the game.
好了，你们准备好了吗？ 我们进入游戏。
Yeah. Let's go. Oh, I'll just disappear.
是的。 我们走吧。 哦，我会消失的。
I got cut off.
我被切断了。
Hello? Open the door.
你好？ 打开门。
You don't even want to play.
你甚至不想玩。
All right, here we are.
好吧，我们到了。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I think I can barely hear you,
so I think I'm everything is.
我想我几乎听不见你，所以我想我就是一切。
Yeah, the game is very loud.
是的，游戏声音很大。
Oh, my goodness.
哦，我的天啊。
Yeah. Music.
I can barely even hear myself.
是的。 音乐。 我什至几乎听不见自己的声音。
Yeah, me too.
我也是。
I'm know everything except for the voice.
除了声音，我什么都知道。
The sound is.
声音是。
so loud. It's fucking hilarious.
那么大声。 太他妈搞笑了
Kind of sounds scuffs. Yeah.
听起来有点磨损。 是的。
Hello, gamers.
你好，游戏玩家。
Hello. Hello. Hello.
你好。 你好。 你好。
Guys.
伙计们。
How's the sound?
声音怎么样？
How's the sound? Nice. Yeah.
声音怎么样？ 好的。 是的。
How does that sound? Do they sound better?
听起来怎么样？ 他们听起来更好吗？
I increase the volumes.
我增加音量。
Oh, my. God. It's still so loud.
天啊。 上帝。 它仍然那么响亮。
So sorry.
非常抱歉。
I I'll try not to be loud.
我会尽量不大声。
I'd be happy to face my melody.
我很乐意面对我的旋律。
Yeah.
是的。
You're like whispering in my ear
well, I do the same to you.
你就像在我耳边好好的耳语，我对你也一样。
I do the same to you,yeah yeah yeah.Do you like that?
我对你也一样，是的，是的，你喜欢吗？
I should be able to hear
you guys better now.
我现在应该能更好地听到你们的声音了。
I'll go ask you your favourite sandwich, you bitch.
我去问问你最喜欢的三明治，你这个婊子。
My favourite sandwich?
我最喜欢的三明治？
What is my favourite sandwich?
我最喜欢的三明治是什么？
You like cheese?
你喜欢奶酪吗？
Oh, there's more there's lower.
哦，还有更多有更低的。
There's more? Yeah,
I found some more, too.
还有更多？ 是的，我也发现了一些。
All right. So what do we got?
好的。 那么我们得到了什么？
Our captain's warning. Here you are.
我们船长的警告。 这个给你。
Have read out loud.
已大声朗读。
Hey, Jason.
嘿，杰森。
I'm looking for that box of tape recorders
我正在寻找那盒录音机，而你正在设置那些愚蠢的鬼魂。
while you're setting
those stupid ghosts up.
What? What?
什么？ 什么？
You'll find them in and lineal
oh, you owe you big time shooting range.
你会发现它们是直系的哦，你欠你很大的时间射击场。
can't afford to lose many prises. Johnny.
输不起很多奖品。 约翰尼。
Johnny. I‘m John Jones. Yeah.
约翰尼。 我是约翰琼斯。 是的。
I thought it said Johnny.
我以为它说的是约翰尼。
I like Jenny.
我喜欢珍妮。
Jenny, Jenny.
珍妮，珍妮。
You got the legs, right? That's right.
你有腿，对吧？ 没错。
Survival says lt's in.
生存说它在。
I wish this doctor would be quiet.
我希望这位医生保持安静。
And you got new legs.
你得到了新的腿。
You said you want the dog to be quiet.
你说你想让狗安静。
There's a dog got the duck. It's another.
有一只狗抓到了鸭子。 这是另一个。
This is nothing.
这不重要。
Nothing, nothing.
没事没事。
What?
什么？
Yeah, it keeps talking.
是的，它一直在说话。
Make it stop.
让它停下来。
Okay, OK, let me just.
好吧，好吧，让我来吧。
I'm going in. There's another.
我要进去了。还有一个。
Oh, there's another note.
哦，还有一个注释。
It says narrator shouldn't
be running this hard either.
它说叙述者也不应该如此努力。
Johnny's got something more hard in this
or the wiring's worse
约翰尼在这方面遇到了一些更难的事情，或者线路比约翰尼比尔球场的该死的对冲标准更糟糕。
than the damn hedge par
for the course with Johnny Bills.
Just charge him an arm and leg and look.
What the. Fuck?
只要给他一条胳膊和一条腿，然后看看。 什么的。 他妈的？
Who the fuck is Johnny? OK, whatever.
强尼到底是谁？ 好吧，随你便。
I have no idea. OK, why are you so ugly,Vox?
我不知道。 好吧，你为什么这么丑，Vox？
You don't need to.
你不需要。
Complain about the bell.
抱怨钟声。
I'm going inside
oh, once it's my throat, there
我要进去哦，一旦它是我的喉咙，那里
for staff to hear my current objective.
让员工听到我目前的目标。
Wait. How do you run?
等待。 你怎么跑？
You hold. Hold. Don't shoot.
你坚持。 抓住。 别开枪。
I'm going to throw rocks
through your window, you bitch.
我要把石头扔进你的窗户，你这个婊子。
It's time to see your current
available money.
是时候查看您当前可用的资金了。
Wait.
You can. Go into the. Trees. Oh, my God.
等待。 你可以。 进入。 树木。 我的天啊。
Look, I'm a tree.
看，我是一棵树。
Oh, wait. No, I'm not.
等一下。 不我不是。
I got. You.
我有。 你。
That's so creepy.
这太令人毛骨悚然了。
I'm a bush.
我是灌木。
If I'm not a bush, I'm no one.
No one in the works. I'm a bush.
如果我不是灌木丛，我就不是人。 没有人在工作。 我是灌木。
I'm a bush.
我是灌木。
I'm a bush. If I'm not a bush, I'm no one.
我是灌木。 如果我不是灌木丛，我就不是人。
How do you
how do you know every reference I made?
你怎么知道我做的每一个参考？
OK, that's  so culture
that one is exceptionally British.
好吧，这太有文化了，以至于一个人非常英国。
That's a very British video.
这是一个非常英式的视频。
Have you seen the one
你有没有看到那个家伙一模一样的，你有几根烟？
where the guy is just like,
how many cigarettes have you got?
Yeah.
是的。
So many cigarettes.
那么多烟。
Yeah. Mom.
是的。 妈妈。
And he just smashes his head into another.
他只是把头撞到另一个。
So is so.
也是如此。
Your. Opinion it's OK. I already kind of.
您的。 意见没问题。 我已经有点。
Have you seen the one that works?
Like where it's like.
你见过有效的吗？ 就像它在哪里一样。
Can't believe I drunk you all.
不敢相信我把你们都喝醉了。
I thought you're going to say,
I can't believe he's on this.
我以为你会说，我不敢相信他在这件事上。
Yes, you all.
是的，你们。
Can you tell the time? Yes.
你能告诉时间吗？ 是的。
He turns toward the clock and he tells it,
I am not fucking drunk.
他转向时钟，告诉它，我他妈的没喝醉。
I'm going to slap you
with my flashlight and keep this up.
我要用我的手电筒打你一巴掌，然后继续。
I'll try it.
我会试试。
You're going to you're going to
你要去你要去你要去打我的舌头很多妙语。
you're going to smack your flashlight on
my tongue.
On your tongue.
在你的舌头上。
I'm gonna suck your beard
and suck your silly little beard.
我是足球胡子，看到了你那傻乎乎的小胡子。
Oh, my boy is waiting for my beer
to be passed down.
哦，我的孩子正在等待我的啤酒被传下去。
notice.
很好的通知。
Oh, hey. Look, it's not for generations,
this beard.
噢！嗨。 看，这胡子不是世代相传的。
It's nice delivery, OK?
交货很好，好吗？
The the Joe, pick up the the flashlight.
乔，拿起手电筒。
I picked up a flashlight.
我拿起手电筒。
I have a flashlight.
我有一个手电筒。
How do I. How do I look?
我怎么样。我看起来怎么样？
Laura? Laura, Laura? Laura.
劳拉？ 劳拉，劳拉？ 劳拉。
Laura? Yeah, or not? Not really. Laura.
劳拉？ 是，还是不？ 并不真地。 劳拉。
But it's a collectable.
It's like. Hello, internet.
但它是一个收藏品。 它像是。 你好，互联网。
Welcome to Game. Theory.
欢迎来到游戏。 理论。
Oh, this is like the third one.
I saw this.
哦，这就像第三个。 我看到了这个。
I can see my legs.
我可以看到我的腿。
Welcome to the maze survival guide.
欢迎来到迷宫生存指南。
A complete guide of getting out of a maze
and survival tips of surviving enemies.
走出迷宫的完整指南和幸存敌人的生存技巧。
I met my by Matthew Patrick.
我遇见了我的马修·帕特里克。
You ever watch where you're lost
in a maze?
你有没有看过你在迷宫中迷路的地方？
You're watching this classified
don't panic.
你在看这个分类不要惊慌。
Have you guys ever seen Hitchhiker's
Guide on the front?
你们有看过前面的Hitchhiker's Guide吗？
Don't panic. Number two,
I'm. Just a runaway.
不要恐慌。 第二个，我。 只是一个逃跑者。
Number three, I don't want to.
第三，我不想。
Oh, my God. This is
this is fucking amazing.
我的天啊。 这真是太他妈了不起了。
That number. Three,
那个号码。 三，
we just left vox.
我们只是喜欢盒子。
We just locked it.
我们只是锁定了它。
Well, it's a flashlight out.
好吧，它是一个手电筒。
Something funny
I was reading something funny.
一些有趣的东西我正在阅读一些有趣的东西。
Press one
按一个
where you can cycle stuff.
在那里你可以循环的东西。
Press one to. One.
按一个到。 一。
Wait, hold on. I don't know.
等等，等等。 我不知道。
What's the flashlight button.
什么是手电筒按钮。
On the back of the book?
The English is a little broken.
在后面？ 书的？ 英语有点破。
It said that there are no number three.
它说没有第三个。
You arescrewed.
你们都搞砸了。
I Yeah.
我是的。
So I hear they scream already.
所以我听到他们已经在尖叫了。
Yes. It's my.
是的。 这是我的。
One. Now.
一。 现在。
I don't know.
我不知道。
I mean, this is, like
spooky house of jump scares.
我的意思是，这就像。 恐怖的跳跃恐惧之家。
I love that game.
我喜欢那个游戏。
I have.
我有。
I cleared it, by the way.
顺便说一句，我清除了它。
You did good for.
你做得很好。
This is a small beat.
这是一个小节拍。
How do you like how do I.
你喜欢我怎么样。
Pull out my flashlight
and tell me I to pull out the. Flashlight?
拿出我的手电筒，告诉我我要拔掉。 手电筒？
Whine why?
呜呜为什么？
Nobody read.
没人读。
It. Is a dead
end. Reading's annoying. Yeah.
它。 是一个死胡同。 看书很烦 是的。
Pick it up.
捡起来。
Pick what up?
捡什么？
现在一个
you. Bitch you get.
你。 婊子你得到。
No, I didn't. That was no, I didn't.
不，我没有。 那是不，我没有。
You don't knowshit. You didn't heer that.
你不知道她在这里，现在在这里。
You did't hear anything.
任何事物
I guess I'm going down this way.
我想我会沿着这条路走下去。
Oh, we should stick together, guys?
哦，我们应该团结在一起，伙计们。
I guess I was that way. Guys.
我想我就是这样的。 伙计们。
I saw that too.
我看见。 那个也是。
Yo, I stop. I can stop going.
哟，我停下来。 我可以停下来了。
Guys, guys, guys.
伙计们，伙计们，伙计们。
We got to stick together, otherwise.
我们必须团结在一起，否则。
Ike can you hear me? Stop running.
你好？ 停止运行。
ike vox， get back here.
我想回到这里。
What do you mean, go?
什么意思，走？
Yeah, we saw it.
是的，我们看到了。
We saw, like, a demon or something
running through the maze.
我们看到，就像一个恶魔或什么东西在迷宫中奔跑。
The juice about that by the saw.
锯子上的果汁。
Just. Oh, like. No, no, no, no, no.
只是。 哦，喜欢。 不，不，不，不，不，不。
You were behind me when it happened.
事情发生时你在我身后。
Yeah,
I like how you're. I like how your butt.
是的，我喜欢你的样子。 我喜欢你的屁股。
Wiggles now I feel emasculated.
现在摇摆不定，我感到被阉割了。
Ooh, yellow.
哦，黄色的。
Like you see it.
就像你看到的那样。
Do you see a bite
wiggles? Collectable？
你看到我咬人的样子了吗？ 收藏品。
Look back.
回望。
You go the wrong way.
你走了。 错误的。
I'm I'm. I'm looking at how.
我就是我。 我在看怎么做。
I. Shot the lesson.
I. 拍摄课程。
I put out a reference sheet like the.
我拿出了一个参考表。
Oh, yeah, your flat is five and.
哦，是的，你的公寓是五岁。
Zero k motherfuckers.
零k混蛋。
Zero K when you have no no was like
I do not appreciate everybody
当你没有零 K 时，就像我不欣赏每个人一样只是盯着看。
like just staring.
It was just like last longer.
就像上次一样。
This. Way.
在。 这。 方式。
I made it look, dude, if I put a
if I put a balance on the.
我让它看起来，伙计，如果我把平衡放在上面。
It would be like a whole 180 degrees.
这就像一个完整的 180 度。
Oh, did you guys see that?
哦，你们看到了吗？
Yeah, I sold out.
是的，我卖光了。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Shut the fuck up.
闭嘴。
Take a break.
休息一下。
Whoever is running around with.
跟谁跑来跑去。
Everybody going.
大家去。
Creepy, you how about we don't do that?
毛骨悚然，我们不这样做怎么样？
Thanks. Who wrote. That?
谢谢。 谁写的。 那？
You should take a break. Let's squat.
你应该休息一下。 让我们蹲下。
Oh, you want a squat.
哦，你想要一个深蹲。
To whoever is running around in the dark?
给在黑暗中奔跑的人？
It's creepy. How about we just don't?
好吓人啊。 我们不这样做怎么样？
I just don't.
我只是不知道。
Yeah, it is kind of weird.
是的，这有点奇怪。
You're so. (Reimu: it's a mushroom.)
你是如此. (Reimu: 这有一个蘑菇。)
So the demon thing,
that's the shade of a shadow
恶魔一样的东西，那是阴影的阴影或任何在四处奔跑的东西。
or whatever it is that's running around.
It's not a clue because I saw it
just run straight into a deep end
这不是一个线索，因为我看到它只是直奔死胡同。
and straight to a dead
end. And then it disappeared.
然后它就消失了。
Let's teabagging the mushroom.
让我们把pp坐在蘑菇上。
Yeah, OK. Anyway, well.
嗯。 无论如何，好吧。
I'll teabag your mushroom in a minute.
我要来坐一会儿蘑菇。
Oh, boy. You guys catch me.
好家伙。 我无语了。
Fucking catch me first. Me, get in here.
进来吧。
You know
你知道
all I know.
据我所知。
And I'm
而我是
why is there so many ducks?
为什么有这么多鸭子？
Like the duck is, like, everywhere.
就像鸭子无处不在一样。
Is this a theme, man?
这是一个鸭子主题吗，伙计？
(quack quack quack )
嘎嘎嘎
(quack )wait
嘎嘎嘎嘎嘎. 等下，你们在干啥。
might not like you do that way too long.
你们够了啊。
You. Well, you know that.
你。 嗯，你知道的。
Oh, not that you guys.
哦，不是你们。
Guys, I think we left Ike
伙计们，我想我们弄丢了艾克
I think we left ike.
我想我们丢下了艾克。
I, i, i i i-ke.Hello? (Ike:I'm sorry.) ok?
艾克？(Ike:对不起)
I just I had to sneeze
我只是不得不打喷嚏
well.
好。
Oh, nice. Ron.
不错哦。 罗恩。
Vox. Like what?
Vox。 像什么？
I had to sneeze.
我不得不打喷嚏。
I'm not allowed to sneeze?
不允许我打喷嚏吗啊？
That's right.
没错。
I'm doing it on this court again.
This motherfucker. Give me a second.
我又在这个球场上这样做了。 这个混蛋。 你稍等一会儿。
Where are we? We wait.
我们在哪？ 我们等。
Are we actually
are we not using ingame voice?
我们真的没有使用游戏内语音吗？
We we're using in-game voice.
我们正在使用游戏语音。
We're using in-game voice.
No, never mind, guys.
He is not muted. Stop.
不，别介意，伙计们。 他没有静音。 停止。
Yeah, it's double.
是的，它是双倍的。
It's doubled up.
If I mean, this goes something you gave.
它是双倍的。 如果我的意思是，这是你给的东西。
Update it.
更新它。
Glowsticks made it out.
荧光棒成功了。
We already
put your volume to zero, though,
不过，我们已经将你静音了，因为我们希望富士灯亮起来。
because we want the Fuji thing
to light up.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Oh.
耶耶耶。 哦。
Oh, I get it.
哦，我明白了。
I'll tell you, you're. A smart boy.
我会告诉你，你是。 一个聪明的男孩。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
I was down here
this is like a little
我在下面，这就像一个小。。不知是什么，但这就像我们可以爬进去一样。
but it is this like a we can crawl inside.
I don't know. What the fuck.
我不知道。 什么鬼。
I'll crawl inside you.
Vox:我会爬进你的身体。
crawl inside oh.oh what.
Shoto:爬进我...，啥？
That's that's a lot to fit inside. OK?
那我的肚子要容纳好大一只啊。 是吧？
Yeah. Yeah, I know, I know.
是的。 是的，我知道，我知道。
I get that a lot amount.
毕竟我的(身体)很大嘛。
What is this, like a underground mine?
这是什么，像地下矿井？
Are we going to the mines?
我们要去矿场吗？
No, I believe it's just.
All right. We have officially entered the.
不，我相信它只是。 好的。 我们正式进入了。
This is our last two.
This feels like our last two.
这是最后的我们俩。 这感觉就像最后的我们俩。
All right,
so it's not scary, then. Gotcha.
好吧，那就不可怕了。 明白了。
Yeah. What, you weren't that scared by it?
是的。 什么，你没有被 最后的我们俩 吓到吗？
Nah. Last two is mostly
just kind of gross.
不。 那游戏大多只是有点恶心。
It was.
它是。
It's very gory and dark.
它非常血腥和黑暗。
It's very gory, very gross.
But it wasn't really that scary.
非常血腥，非常恶心。 但这并没有那么可怕。
My favourite part was at the beginning,
我最喜欢的部分是一开始，有一个家伙从人群中逃跑，就像他在追我一样。
there was one dude who ran away
from the crowd like he was after me.
And then suddenly he turned around
and he ran away,
然后突然他转身就跑了，他就有点，就像，蹲下然后跑了。
and he just kind of, like, crouched over
and ran away, like, smuggle it.
Maybe it made me laugh quite a bit.
这让我笑了半天。
In the first part, they were there.
在第一部分，他们在那里。
The word was on the statues, deeper
in the maze.
这个词在雕像上，在迷宫的更深处。
It's L, so begins with E.
它是 L，所以以 E 开头。
Are ha got it?
明白了吗？
Had to shift some stones. With E.
不得不移动一些石头。 与 E。
And there is. What the hell's
the password?
有。 密码是什么鬼？
Giant maze open for me.
巨大的迷宫为我打开。
Maybe there's a clue somewhere
也许某处有线索
like open sesame.
像芝麻一样。
Also, I believe we've lost our friends.
Well, yeah.
另外，我相信我们已经失去了我们的朋友。 嗯，是的。
I thought there.
我在那里想。
Oh I hear them. Reimu, Reimu.
哦，我听到了他们。Reimu,Reimu
Hello？ Bitch, you left me behind.
你好吗？ 我在你们后面。
Yeah. I've just progressed.
是的。 我刚刚进步了。
We're hazing you. This is how you get used
to this experience.
哪里欺负你。 这就是你习惯这种体验的方式。
OK, also congratulations for beating 52.
好的.
That's a difficult game.
那是一场艰难的游戏。
Oh, you bet.
哦，你打赌。
Yeah, I was there one and a half
and I was, I was like cheering.
是的，我在那里待了一年半，我就像在欢呼一样。
It was great. It was. Amazing.
You did so well.
太好了。 它是。 惊人的。 你做得很好。
Honestly, I was so proud.
老实说，我很自豪。
That game night
while that game took me a while to be.
那个游戏之夜，而那场比赛让我花了一段时间。
The sixth night, though.
不过，第六晚。
Oh, my God. Oh, my. God.
我的天啊。 天啊。 上帝。
I had to shift some stone plates
around to get this thing working.
我不得不移动一些石板来让这个东西工作。
Now, what the hell's the password?
现在，密码是什么鬼？
Giant maze open for me.
巨大的迷宫为我打开。
Maybe there's a clue. Some it somewhere.
也许有一个线索。 有些地方。
We had to look for clues. I am the best.
我们不得不寻找线索。 我是最好的。
I know.
我知道。
We can't move it right now,
but the code begins with E and ends an s.
我们现在不能移动它，但是代码以 E 开头并以 s 结尾。
Eggs.
蛋。
You're a funny fucking guy.
你真他妈牛逼。
No, no. We got a real fucking comedian
不，不。 我们有一个真正的喜剧演员。
Oh, it's one,
two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
哦，是一、二、三、四、五、六、七、八。
Yes, it has a q. It's nine letters long.
是的，一个q。 它有九个字母长。
Has a Q after that.
之后有一个Q。
What was the first and last letter again?
第一个和最后一个字母又是什么？
Equality is the first letter and then the
second letter, but we can't read.
平等是第一个字母，然后是第二个字母，但我们看不懂。
So a share.
No, it's just. Uh.
不，只是。 呃。
What? Oh. Oh, Ike.
什么？ 哦。 哦，我。
Oh, no.
不好了。
What? Oh, my God.
什么？ 我的天啊。
What happened ?
发生什么了？
Hey, guys, I'm scared.
What happened over here?
嘿，伙计们，我很害怕。 这里发生了什么事？
Well, by.
嗯，靠。
Itself, it was through my screen and went.
本身，有个藤曼出现在我的屏幕上然后。
Boom,
一下子绽开，吓到我了。
no one boom vine boom.
藤曼轰炸？
Like a vine. Boom.
就像一个藤蔓轰炸吗。
Yeah, like a vine boom.
是的，就像藤蔓轰炸。
Oh, my. Oh, I didn't save it.
天啊。 哦，我没保存。
I don't know.
我不知道。
I got to I put the phone app to
sound of my dogs la
前几天我把手机应用程序放到了代做列表
the other day, and I forgot to save it.
但我忘了保存它。
I think I got jump scared by tik-toker.
我想我被抖音用户吓到了。
I'm not going to allow. What
我不会允许的。 什么
hey, guys.
大家好。
I see.
我懂了。
Oh, wait. You guys hear that?
等一下。 你们听到了吗？
I just heard someone breathing.
Something is breathing around me.
我刚刚听到有人呼吸。 有什么东西在我周围呼吸。
I don't. Know.
Why are we heading towards the ghost?
我不。 知道。 我们为什么要走向幽灵？
Why are we wanting to. Face.
为什么我们想要。 脸。
I heard of creepy.
There's a fucking tricycle there.
听说很毛骨悚然。 那里有一辆他妈的三轮车。
Hey, you left me,ok?
guys. I'll be it.
伙计们，走慢一点我跟不上了。 我会的。
Is the shining.
是闪耀的。
Yo, I don't think we should head
towards. The ghost.
哟，我不认为我们应该走向 鬼。
Noise. Oh, my God.
噪音。 我的天啊。
Somebody. Somebody ran to the side.
They went ooga booga.
某人。 有人跑到一边。 他们去了ooga booga。
Somebody went down that way.
有人就这样倒下了。
Somebody will
有人会
it's like, well, that's.
就像，嗯，就是这样。
Close to an adult male.
接近成年男性。
Adult male male.
成年男性男性。
Seven has removed all the teeth.
七已经拔掉了所有的牙齿。
Everything's just. OK.
一切都刚刚好。 好的。
They had a man that's information.
他们有一个人就是信息。
Mark Oh, this way,
this way, this way. This.
马克哦，这边，这边，这边。 这。
This is where they went, though.
This is where the ghost ran to.
不过，这就是他们去的地方。 鬼魂跑到了这里。
Yeah, exactly. So we're chasing the.
是的，正是。 于是我们就追了。
Ghost thing, which.
鬼东西，哪个。
How do I use the flashlight
I mean, how do I use.
我这手电筒咋用。
I don't think this is, like, fisma phobia.
我不认为这是，像，fisma phobia。
Oh?
哦？
Let me in the in the.
让我试试这个。
I think we're supposed to use the ghost.
They will find our way back.
我认为我们应该使用幽灵， 他们会找到我们回去的路。
Yeah. Yeah,
I think. My God, wait. oh thank you.
是的。 是的.上帝，等下，哦，感谢你。
Thank you. Yeah,
I forgot about the guys. Guys, it's guys.
谢谢你。 是的，我忘记了那些家伙。 伙计们，这是伙计们。
I found the. Oh,
my team were full of idiots.
我找到了。 哦，我的团队里全是白痴。
Well, it's a big bone, really.
嗯，真的是一根大骨头。
This thing. This thing does. It's a bone.
And it also it does that kind of stuff.
这东西。 这件事可以。 它是一块骨头。 它也做那种事情。
It looks.
它看起来。
Like.
像。
Oh, hi,shh. This is Officer Frank Mills.
哦闭嘴，听。 我是弗兰克米尔斯警官。
My boy Robert's been missing
for nearly two days now.
我的儿子罗伯特已经失踪近两天了。
We're not moving fast enough.
我们的行动不够快。
I'm taking it on myself
to get through this damn gate.
我自己承担着通过这该死的门的责任。
Find where is hiding in this fucking maze?
找到这该死的迷宫中的藏身之处？
This should help me keep evidence.
这应该有助于我保留证据。
Anyways.
无论如何。
That's a
这是一个
boner.
大骨头。
It's ominous.
这是不祥的。
Did you guys heard the audio tape right.
你们没听错录音带吗？
Yeah, I heard it.
I didn't hear any of that.
是的，我听了. vox:我什么都没听到。
Oh, you didn't really?
哦，你真的没有？
Oh, no.
不好了。
Yeah, no,
I heard something, but it was super quiet.
是的，不，我听到了什么，但非常安静。
Oh, wow.
哦，哇。
So a boy got lost.
于是，一个男孩迷路了。
You know, and got lost.
你知道，然后迷路了。
Then he's in these fields. Shit.
然后他在这些地方。
So fields of.
所以领域。
Green opening up here.
绿色在这里开放。
At least
至少
oh, there's a shad.
哦，这有个小屋子。
This is the safe house.
这是安全屋。
Oh, like this.
哦，像这样。
Oh, I hear music come from it.
哦，我听到有音乐。
Creepy arse. Music. There's music.
令人毛骨悚然的音乐。 有音乐。
And like, a lot of religious things,
then it's a safe house.
就像，很多宗教的东西，那么它就是一个安全的房子。
Nice. It sounds like little nightmares.
好的。 这听起来像小噩梦里的音乐。
Kind of.
有点儿。
Somebody's having a bad day down here.
有人在这里度过了糟糕的一天。
Reminder to self.
提醒自己。
Give them some space.
给他们一些空间。
This is a creepy arse folk music. Yeah.
这是一首令人毛骨悚然的民间音乐。 是的。
It reminds me of the little nightmares
theme.
它让我想起了小噩梦的主题。
You know, I'm
你知道，我是
on some sort of.
关于某种。
Method of mechanism.
机制的方法。
So dark hair
and you get the whole thing glowing.
这么黑的头发，你会让整个东西发光。
What if controls anything
如果控制任何东西怎么办
OK? Oh, checkpoint.
好的？ 哦，检查站。
Checkpoint. Hey, we got a checkpoint.
检查站。 嘿，我们有一个检查站。
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
等等等等等等等等等等等等。
Mechanism is
机制只是让整个事情运转起来的一种机制机制。
just sort of mechanism mechanisms
to get the whole thing going.
One of the controls, anything?
控制之一，什么？
Nothing else. You
没有其他的吗。
gain here is tweaking, working.
这里的增益正在调整，工作。
Thought he was looking now.
以为他现在正在寻找。
Tweaking, but he was looking right at me.
正在调整，但他正看着我。
But I just froze up and he wandered away.
但我只是僵住了，他走开了。
Note to calls called someone to come
get this guy when I saw this,
当我看到这个时，请注意打电话给某人来接这个人，
and I just froze up and he wandered away.
我只是僵住了，他走开了。
So that's highlighted.
所以突出显示。
So if you guys see anybody.
所以，如果你们看到任何人。
Don't move.
不要动好吗。
All OK? Why?
Oh, that's all. Well, that's a hint.
一切都好？ 为什么？ 哦，仅此而已。 嗯，这是一个提示。
OK, so if we see a.
好的，所以如果我们看到一个。
Ghost I don't. Know.
鬼我没有。 知道。
I didn't get the hint.
我没有得到提示。
If we see a ghost,
do not move and don't see anything.
如果我们看到鬼，不要动，什么也看不见。
Am I the only one
that's using the glow sticks?
我是唯一一个使用荧光棒的人吗？
Yes. Oh, yes. Walls and.
是的。 哦是的。 墙壁和。
Oh, it says a. Bunch of statues.
About this find the.
哦，上面写着一个。 一堆雕像。 关于这个找到。
Labels are ruined, but a few of them
still have letters remaining.
标签被毁了，但其中一些还剩下字母。
Hello?
你好？
Oh, pow, pow. Wow.
哦，救命救命。 哇。
Wait, what.
哦等下，什么？
Am I, dead
我，死了吗
Ahhhh
啊？
I'm dead. I'm dead, too.
我死了。 我也死了。
I am on the ground. Ike,
you got to pick me up. Oh, someone.
我在地上。 艾克，你得扶我起来。 哦，来人帮我一下。
Oh, don't don't . pick me up, Ike.
Ike pick me ip.
哦，不要不要吵，嘘。vox:扶我起来！艾克。
You'll get it.
你别急。
Get the fuck out of here first.
先他妈的离开这里。
Ike, pick me up.
好的，来接我。
Hello? I'm about to die.
你好？ 我快死了。
I'm bleeding out. I'm bleeding out.
I'm bleeding out. I'm bleeding.
我流血了。 我流血了。 我流血了。 要流完了。
Oh, my God. I'm dead.
我的天啊。 我死了。
He always got me I'm revived now I'm dead.
他总是让我复活，现在我死了。
All thank you.
都谢谢你。
Sorry. I thought I could.
对不起。 我以为我可以。
I couldn't speak.
我说不出话来。
I did speak either.
我也讲过。
This bitch is still screaming like hell.
这婊子还在尖叫。
All I think vox has dead
我认为vox刚才挂掉了。我们可以回去把它们放在安全屋里。
that we can go back
and get them in there on the safe house.
Oh, so I guess so
I just so I just wait. You die.
哦，所以我想所以我只是等着。 你死了。
You just kind of come back.
你们就会回来的。
Yeah, we turned off her body.
是的，我们关闭了她的身体。
Just a bit after that.
就在这之后。
After I was.
在我之后。
I was right back.
我马上回来了。
That, like,
the fact that both vox and shoto
就像，vox和shoto都只是纸上的手一样完全消失了。
are just the hand on the paper
just went completely out the window.
So I just stood there and watched
you two get mangled.
所以我只是站在那里，看着你们两个被毁坏。
No, I just.I went scared. Yeah, you know what happened?
不，我只是。 我当时吓坏了，是的，你知道发生了什么吗？
I wish she was, like,
helping us like this motherfucker.
我希望她能像这个混蛋一样帮助我们。
No, look.
不，看。
I heard whispering,
我听到耳语，就像，就在我的左耳道深处，我吓坏了。
like, right deep into my left
ear canal, and I panicked the fuck out.
I thought something was on my arse
so I was dead anyways,
我以为有什么东西在我的屁股上，所以我死定了，但我就站在我们面前。
but I was right in front of us.
And Vox like a bomb.
vox就像一颗炸弹。
Oh. I did, I did.
哦。 我做到了，我做到了。
I saw the I saw, like,
the dude, like, kissing your soul out
我看到了我看到的，就像，那个家伙，就像，吸出来了你的灵魂
oh. Well, OK.
哦。 好吧，好吧。
So now we know what to do, at least.
所以现在我们至少知道该怎么做了。
Yeah, let's not let's not scream.
是的，我们不要让我们不要尖叫。
Not whatever you guys did.
不是你们做什么。
I'm sorry.
对不起。
I think there's a.
我认为有一个。
Bunch of statues back this way.
一堆雕像往这边走。
Labels are ruined, but a few of them
still have some letters remaining.
标签被毁了，但其中一些还剩下一些字母。
OK, so this one says e q u,
but imagine this is the first clue.
好的，所以这个人说你，但想象这是第一个线索。
This is the first three letters
of the three guys.
这是三个家伙的前三个字母。
Yeah. Oh,
是的。 哦，去吧。 救命救命！ 哦！
go. Help, help, help! Oh!
Oh, no.
不好了。
Oh, God.
天啊。
The guys.
My bleed out timer ,my bleed out timer.
我的出血计时器，我的出血计时器快没了。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Oh, he was.
哦，他是。
I'm very pretty.
我很确信。
Probably guys. Im going to aid oh.
我来救你。
I could be OK.
我可以的。
I think it's because of his socks.
我想是因为他的袜子。
Oh, no, I'm dead.
哦，不，我死了。
I'm dead.
我死了呜呜。
The end endgame voice.
游戏结束的声音。
I was like in between Ike's legs there.
我就像在艾克的双腿之间。
What the fuck was that?
那是什么鬼？
Oh, OK.
哦好的。
oh, We're liver
我们现在又活了
I'm alone now, I think.
我现在一个人，我想。
No, you're not.
不，你不是。
Oh, hey, what's up, demons?
哦，嘿，怎么了，恶魔们？
It's me.
是我。
Yeah, boy.
是的，男孩。
It got.
它得到了。
OK, which one's the lights? Sticks.
好的，哪个是灯？ 棍子。
I got to use the light sixes.
我必须使用轻型六号。
Well, number two is to be
好吧，第二个是
You're going to get us killed.
你会害死我们的。
So you just got killed.
所以你刚刚被杀。
Oh, wow.
哦，哇。
We're back.
我们回来了。
Speaking.
请讲。
Audio.
声音的。
Audio jungle time.
音频丛林时间。
You turn your rules away.
你改变了你的规则。
Shut the fuck up, British.
闭嘴，英国人。
Shut up, British.
Because of what Virginia all spoke.
因为弗吉尼亚都说了什么。
Where? The spoons in here.
在哪里？ 茶勺在这里面吗。
Shut up, British.
闭嘴，英国人。
I like that one .
我喜欢这个梗。
I know how to deal with ghosts.
我知道如何对付鬼。
I found out. I found a little.
我发现。 我发现了一点。
I found a puzzle area.
我找到了一个拼图区。
Why was this puzzle. Huh?
为什么会出现这个谜题。 嗯？
Oh, no.
不好了。
There's just me and you guys now.
现在只有我和你们。
What is this?
这是什么？
This mechanism looks old.
这种机制看起来很旧。
I thought Johnny set this up with a fair
can afford this kind of budget.
我认为约翰尼以公平的方式设置了这个，可以负担得起这种预算。
A Jason. What.
一个杰森。啥
Oh, hello.
哦你好有人吗？
Hello.
你好。
Oh, it's like it's one of.
哦，这就像它是这些谜题。
These puzzles
其中之一。
ok. OK, ok.
行。 好的好的。
All right.
好的。
Well, I think I need my friends
for this one, so I'm going to go back
好吧，我想我需要我的朋友来解决这个问题，所以我要回去找我的朋友，或者我可以自己解决。
and get my friends,
or I could just solve it on my own. Why?
为什么？
I don't want to do that.
I will look for them.
我不想那样做。 我会去找他们。
Hey, it's my first time.
嘿，这是我第一次。
Reimu said that to me?
听到Reimu对我说过这样的话？
I found a. Puzzle.
我找到了一个。 谜。
You a puzzle? Yeah. And bass.
你是个谜？ 是的。 还有贝斯。
If you ever play heroes of or watch,
it's like it's similar.
如果您曾经玩过或观看过英雄，就好像它是相似的。
It's like you press one symbol,
and then the surrounding symbols light up.
就像你按下一个符号，然后周围的符号亮起。
So you got to like, oh.
所以你必须喜欢，哦。
Like you to use my glow stick.
喜欢你用我的荧光棒。
Oh, I get it. I get. It. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
哦，我明白了。 我明白了。 它。 耶耶耶。
I don't.
我不。
You have to, like, look, glow them all out
glow them all out, I think.
我认为，您必须像，看，将它们全部发光，使它们发光很多。
I think you got some either Jago them
all out is what I'm thinking right now.
我认为你得到了一些 Jago 他们全部是我现在的想法。
OK, so give me a second.
好的，请稍等。
I happen to be standing here
which set off enough stuff.
我恰好站在这里引发了足够的东西。
Or maybe you all glow.
或者，也许你们都会发光。
I don't. Johnny set this up.
我不。 约翰尼设置了这个。
No way.
没门。
And the fair
can afford this kind of budget.
展会可以负担得起这样的预算。
We can change
the colours of our Glowsticks.
我们可以改变荧光棒的颜色。
See a Jason.
见杰森。
OK, I get how it works.
好的，我知道它是如何工作的。
Now, when you step on a tile,
it highlights everything
现在，当您踩到瓷砖时，它会突出显示相邻的所有内容，例如
that is adjacent
on, like the X and y axis.
X 和 y 轴。
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
So not diagonal.
Yeah, only z, our x and y.
所以不是对角线。 是的，只有 z，我们的 x 和 y。
So we have to, like,
make it all glow. I think
所以我们必须，比如，让它发光。 我认为
seems right.
似乎是对的。
Yeah, we can go. Yeah.
是的，我们可以走了。 是的。
Hold on, everybody step off them.
等等，所有人都从他们身上走下来。
And, like, let's think about this.
而且，就像，让我们考虑一下。
I want to. It's OK. So wait.
我想要。 没关系。 所以等等。
And if I fill them off,
that are mine.(Ike:Reimu?)
如果我把它们填满，就把它们放进去。
So OK.
那么好吧。
So now most of them are off.
所以现在他们中的大多数都关闭了。
Yeah, most of them are off now.
是的，他们中的大多数现在都关闭了。
OK, let's pick this one.
好，就选这个吧。
That turns that one off.
这会关闭那个。
Know you play a bunch of puzzle
games earlier.
知道你之前玩过一堆益智游戏。
I think you have the, you know, the
the brain folds for this one, right?
我认为你有，你知道，一个专门对付这种游戏的大脑，对吧？
I that's why. Perhaps.
我这就是为什么。 也许。
I heard something
我听到了什么
was I.
我是吗？
Know that's me stepping on the.
知道是我踩的。
Fucking vox doing weird sounds.
他妈的是vox发出奇怪的声音。
Right?
对？
I thought it was a ghost.
我以为是一个鬼呢。
Somebody
walking around on the puzzle pieces.
有人在拼图上走来走去。
Sorry. I yeah.
对不起。 我是的。
That's what's.
就是这样。
Happening.
正在发生。
Is blowing vox me too.
捣蛋的vox。
T y you
mean main stream, the way you named it.
你的意思是主流，你给它命名的方式。
You are terrifying
when you walk up in from my face.
当你从我面前走进来时，你很可怕。
You know that.
你知道的。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
If I go too close to you
like your eyeballs,
如果我像你的眼球一样离你太近，
I can see I can just cut through your head
and see your eyeballs.
我可以看到我可以切开你的头，看到你的眼球。
I can smell your hair.
我能闻到你的头发。
If I do that. It should turn up.
如果我这样做。 它应该出现。
It smells like. Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
它闻起来像。 等，等，等，等，等，等，等，等，等。
What is it about these inexpensive steam
ghost.
这些便宜的蒸汽幽灵是怎么回事。
Left.
Have such funny characterised.
有这样有趣的特点。
Some form of phobia to use as a glitch.
某种形式的恐惧症用作故障。
Ghost?
鬼？
I think.
我认为。
I think Ghost Hunter Core is my favourite
one with the way that they just kind of
我认为 Ghost Hunter Core
have their arms hanging by their sides.
是我最喜欢的一个，他们只是把手臂挂在身边。
And they walk slowly.
They just look really funny.
他们走得很慢。 他们只是看起来很有趣。
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
呜呜呜呜
I see the equation.
我看到了等式。
No, I don't. Oh, you're so close.
不，我没有。 哦，你离得太近了。
Are we?
我们是吗？
Are we ok? OK. OK.
我们还好吗？ 好的。 好的。
This is. All. One.
这是。 全部。 一个。
This one out.
这一出。
I think we have to be such here
我认为我们必须在这里
and here.
和这里。
Here and here and then.
这里和这里，然后。
Oh, you're close.
哦，你很近。
You're close.
你很近了。
Middle one middle one middle one middle,
one middle one.
中间的。
You got a middle one.
你有一个中间的。
But no, no.
但是不，不。
I'm different weight. I'm stupid.
我体重不一样。 我很蠢。
Ignore me. Ignore me.
不理我。 不理我。
I'm a minute.
我是一分钟。
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
等，等，等，等，等，等，等，等。
And and then
然后
after that. We have to.
之后。 我们必须。
Turn them all on.
将它们全部打开。
If we can highlight
only the corners we win
如果我们只能突出我们赢得的角落
wait.
等待。
I think I have an idea. I have an idea.
我想我有个主意。 我有个主意。
Oh, OK.
哦好的。
Shit.
卧槽
No, wait, wait, wait.
不，等等，等等，等等。
Do you see it? You see it?
你看到了吗？ 你看到了吗？
No, not quite.
不，不完全是。
If I do
that, then we get to those corners.
如果我这样做，那么我们就会到达那些角落。
And if I do this,
如果我这样做，我们会得到那些角落
we get those corners
it's just that thing in the middle.
就是中间那个东西。
Where's Vox?
vox在哪里？
Oh, my God. He's here. Three.
我的天啊。 他在这里。
Yeah, he said.
是的，他说。
I. I'm chilling in the corner because
this puzzle is genuinely beyond me.
I. 我在角落里不寒而栗，因为这个谜题真的超出了我的范围。
I'm really bad at these.
我真的不擅长这些。
We got to get the ones
to light up in the corners first.
我们必须先让那些在角落里亮起来的。
Yeah. Prioritise that. Yeah.
是的。 优先考虑。 是的。
1000, oh.
1000，哦。
Wait, wait, wait.
等等，等等，等等。
Hold on. I think I know, I know.
坚持，稍等。 我想我知道，我知道。
Yeah, yeah.
是啊是啊。
Can somebody step in the middle.
有没有人能插到中间。
Of the middle? Hold on, hold on, hold on.
中间的？ 坚持，坚持，坚持。
No, no, never mind.
不，不，没关系。
It was a good idea.
这是个好主意。
Oh, OK.
哦好的。
Not now. We're all stepping on them.
Hold on, hold on.
现在不要。 我们都在踩他们。 等一下，等一下。
Well, I'm so sorry.
好吧，我很抱歉。
Yeah, yeah. Hold on for a second. OK.
是啊是啊。 等下。 好的。
Uh, I just want to see if I can.
呃，我就是想看看能不能。
How do I.
我如何。
I want to get this.
我想得到这个。
OK. OK, and then
好的。  OK，然后才等等。 踩到了中间。
only and so on. Stepped on the middle.
Hold on. Fuck.
坚持，稍等。 他妈的。
I'll step on you.
我会踩到你的。
I think I saw it for a second.
我想我看到了一秒钟。
Because I want these to light up.
因为我想让这些亮起来。
And then no.
然后没有。
It was close.
它很接近了。
Fuck. OK, I have an idea. Hold on.
他妈的。 好的，我有个主意。 坚持，稍等。
If everybody could, like,
如果每个人都可以，比如，远离瓷砖，我想看看我是否可以尝试一些东西。
step away from the tiles,
I want to see if I can try something.
OK. Well.
好的。 好。
Ok. So
行。 所以
I figured out that these
我发现这些角落是这样工作的。
the corners work that way.
Oh, oh, oh, that's it.
哦，哦，哦，原来如此。
Oh, yeah. That was all.
哦耶。 这就是全部了。
I was nice hey, smart car.
我很好，嘿，聪明啊
Smart.
聪明的。
Smart cookie.
小聪明
Oh, my god.
我的天啊。
I was pretty good.
我很好。
Know I was about of girl
that when the teacher says
知道我是关于那个女孩的，当老师说
find a duet partner
for this work a bit like I.
为这项工作找一个像我一样的二重唱搭档。
Don't.
不。
And then we
just have to pick out with someone stupid.
然后我们只需要选择一个愚蠢的人。
I guess I'll just go with shoto.
我想我会和Shoto一起去。
I'm stupid. Yeah.
我很蠢。 是的。
Yeah, you are.
是的，你是。
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的。
Where the fuck we
我们他妈的在哪里？
do they leave.
他们离开。
What?
什么？
Well, OK.
好吧，好吧。
OK, then.
好吧。
I guess we are, huh?
我想我们是吧？
Guys, what the fuck?
伙计们，他妈的是什么？
Why'd you leave us? Come on, keep up.
你们为什么离开我们？ 来吧，跟上。
Keep on trying and trying.
来了来了。
Trying. Right?
试。 对？
That's a really dark like.
那是一个非常黑暗的。
And this one. Also.
和这个。 还。
It's a long and dark.
它是漫长而黑暗的。
I really. Like.
我真的。 像。
So why? Why?
所以为什么？ 为什么？
I heard something.
嘘 我听到了什么。
Or something,
but it was not in front of my face.
或者别的什么，但它不在我的面前。
Low facts that, like,
when you when you go into the trees,
低级的事实，例如，当您进入树木时，您仍然可以像完全不受阻碍的移动速度一样移动。
you can still move like
a completely unencumbered movement speed.
So it's like you just like. Yeah, yeah.
所以就像你一样。 是啊是啊。
When you're talking.
And then you walk into the, oh.
你说话的时候。 然后你走进去，哦。
Yeah.
是的。
I'm going to be the first time
you walk into a bush wooded box.
我将是你第一次走进灌木丛生的盒子。
Oh, we're back now. Now, listen, Michael.
哦，我们现在回来了。 现在，听着，迈克尔。
What do you mean? Easy. Wait.
你什么意思？ 简单的。 等待。
So important lesson put the glowsticks.
所以放了荧光棒。
Over back here, OK?
回到这里，好吗？
Oh, no, thank you.
哦，不，谢谢。
E q u is a e-q-u. Yeah.
E q u。 是的。
I'm his. Equations.
我是他的。 方程。
Is that it? Equations?
是这样吗？ 方程？
Oh, I thought it was equations,
but it's one letter short. Oh.
哦，我以为是方程式，但它少了一个字母。 哦。
Equestrian.
马术。
A hunger.
一种饥饿感。
Equal equal.
平等平等。
Equal y.
等于 y。
Equals equal.
等于等于。
You're the one that ask
what's the who's a lie?
你是那个问什么是谎言的人？
Oh, he was misled.
哦，他被误导了。
Never mind that young demon slayer.
别管那个年轻的杀魔人。
He grew on me like he was E.coli.
他像大肠杆菌一样在我身上长大。
And I was British beef at room
temperature.
我是室温下的英国牛肉。
Equinox guy.
春分。
You know, stupidity, though.
你知道，虽然愚蠢。
Alba Knox.
阿尔巴·诺克斯。
Albert Knox.
阿尔伯特·诺克斯。
Are you sure you can do this
你确定你能做到吗
at trying to find a cure for like.
试图找到治疗类似的方法。
What was the letters on the statue again?
雕像上的字母又是什么？
I don't remember.
我不记得。
Listen, listen.
听，听。
I'm slightly I'm slightly tipsy
and my eyes are full of tears.
我有点醉了，我的眼睛里充满了泪水。
I'm doing my best.
我正竭尽全力。
So I'm going to give you a clip.
所以我要给你一个剪辑。
I missed it again. Yeah.
我又错过了。 是的。
And you want to wipe your tears
on top of your shirts?
你想用你的衬衫擦你的眼泪吗？
Or wipe your tears with my shirt.
还是我的衬衫。
What? You.
什么？ 你。
Ew. Ew？
Vox:恶心 Shoto:恶心？!
Ew. What the fucking
Ew. 你他妈的是有什么毛病。
wrong with you? I'm offering.
我在为你提供服务。
What's what's that?
那是什么？
Why is it always at all
kind of, like, patchy in some places.
为什么它在某些地方总是有点像，零散的。
I've had dried semen.
我有干的精液。
But? Ewww You are.
但. 啊好恶心。你是。
You are.
你是。
You know what, that's the last time.
你知道吗，这是我最后一次决定给你安慰。
I'm offering you.
You are such a Bastard. Man.
你就是这样一个 混蛋。 男人。
You know what you're facing at this point?
你知道你现在面临什么吗？
We have me and I. Got the exact same shit.
What the hell are you talking about?
你他妈在说什么？
Well, fine.
好吧，好吧。
You want me to.
你想让我。
Oh, it's with.
哦，它是。
Oh, OK. Give me a second.
哦好的。 你稍等一会儿。
I think I messed up with this one. Yes.
我想我把这个搞砸了。 是的。
I was doing that.
我正在这样做。
Why did you why did you eat this?
你为什么吃这个？
So equal sign equally.
所以 equal sign ...。
E and u. Okay.
E和u。 好的。
Oh, my goodness.
哦，我的天啊。
Oh, we should go back inside.
哦，我们应该回到里面。
I don't like the little wiggle
that you deal when you're like.
我不喜欢你喜欢的时候做的小动作。
Yeah, why is. It like, I'm slow?
是的，为什么。 就像，我很慢？
Why is it why is it working?
为什么它为什么工作？
Like my camera
when I was doing my cooking,
就像我做饭时的相机一样，它在我的厨房柜台上慢慢弹跳，嗯。
which is slowly bouncing over my kitchen
counter, hmm.
OK, ok. OK. We're done with this.
好的好的。 好的。 我们已经完成了这个。
No, don't move anything.
不，不要移动任何东西。
I just want to see.
我只是想看看。
OK, I'll be right back.
好的，我马上回来。
I'm going I'm going to head back into
the maze real quick and just take a look.
我要去 我要很快回到迷宫里看看。
Are you trying to put in?
你是想插吗？
So I'll be there.
所以我会在那里。
I just want to. See the way.
我只想。 看路。
You maybe spelled it now. OK,
你现在可以拼写了。 好的，
my chat it's just me and you.guys missing.Muah.
我的聊天室，只有我和你们了。亲亲。
Yeah,
是的，
I'm just kidding.
我只是开玩笑。
I actually.
其实我。
Do you want to go back into the maze
and look for any other clues?
你想回到迷宫中寻找其他线索吗？
Because it seems like
we're missing something
因为我们好像错过了什么
it feels like it might not be a word.
感觉可能不是一个词。
Like if it feels like
it might not be a word
就像感觉它可能不是一个词，它可能只是一堆乱七八糟的字母，
and it might just be like
a jumble of letters,
and it's just trying to give us
the illusion.
它只是想给我们一种错觉。
It's an actual word.
这是一个实际的词。
So that's why we're going to head back
over here and take a look
所以这就是为什么我们要回到这里看看
this is a solo mission.
这是一个单独的任务。
I think I can still hear
the voices of the gamers,
我想我仍然可以听到游戏玩家的声音，这将优化它的音频名称
and that will optimise with the
what's it called with the audio it's
it seems
它似乎
this thing's looking at me.
这东西在看着我。
Why are you looking at me?
你为什么看着我？
Hello, Oh,
你好哦？哦哦哦呜呜。
oh, OK.
哦好的。
Well.
好。
Ah, well,
呃，好吧，
it might be about time
可能是我们他妈的出去的时候了。
while we get the fuck out.
I think? OK.
我觉得可以。
OK, we're fine.
好的，我们很好。
We're fine. Right.
我们都很好。 对把。
Don't move.
不要动。
No, it's ok.
不，没关系。
It's OK.
没关系。
No, there's nothing.
不，什么都没有。
I got nothing out of this.
我没有从中得到任何东西。
What the fuck?
什么鬼？
Actually got.
其实得到了。
Nothing.
没有。
Sounds outside that as well.
外面的声音也是如此。
Oh, my God. Wait. I think I'm lost.
我的天啊。 等待。 我想我迷路了。
Oh, no, wait. How do I.
哦，不，等等。 我如何。
Is it blocked off?
是不是被屏蔽了？
Wait, is it blocked off?
等等，是不是被屏蔽了？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
It's blocked off.
它被封锁了。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Guys, I'm actually .wait.
伙计们，我实际上,等等。
Oh, fuck.
哦，操。
That's bad.
那很不好。
Help!
救命！
Help! Someone!
救命！ 来人啊！
Someone send help!
来人帮忙喊人！
Guys, guys. Somebody's going to. That.
伙计们，伙计们。 来人去找人救我。
I need help.
我需要帮助。
I don't know.
我不知道。
Is he is he going to
他会不会
Oh, no.
不好了。
I said not to move, so I didn't move. Oh,
我说不要动，所以我没有动。 哦，
no, no, no.
不不不。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
Oh, my God. That's bad.
我的天啊。 那很不好。
Fuck! No.
他妈的！ 不。
Oh, I dead.
哦，我死了。
Too. There was no good clues.
也。 没有好的线索。
I'm so confused.
我感到很困惑。
I got wrecked by the monster.
我被怪物击倒了。
I .
我.
I don't like the way he looks.
我不喜欢他的样子。
Creatures terrifying.
可怕的生物。
You are
你是
maybe I go down this way instead, right?
也许我会走这条路，对吧？
Oh, my God. I'm lost. I'm so lost.
我的天啊。 我搞不清楚了。 我走丢了。
I'm so lost.
我迷路了。
我很迷茫。
And I get the fuck away from him
而且我他妈的远离他我所在的地方。
where I'm at.
I actually， Ah
其实我，啊
flew.
I found another clue. Oh, my God.
我发现了另一个线索。 我的天啊。
It was worth it.
这是值得的。
Holy shit. It was worth it.
天啊。 这是值得的。
It was worth it.
这是值得的。
X, x x.
X，xx。
Yes, ok. OK.
好的。 好的。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I got to help him, dude.
我得帮他，伙计。
I got to go back and tell them
我得回去告诉他们我
that I
please.
请。
Please don't die. Please don't
I please don't. I need. I have.
请不要死。 请不要我请不要。 我需要。 我有。
To. This is a vital it's a vital clue.
到。 这是一条至关重要的线索。
What the hell, man?
什么鬼，伙计？
You know,
你知道，
oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I hate it. I hate it so much.
我恨它。 我非常讨厌它。
I hate it so much.
我非常讨厌它。
Maybe there's another clue back here.
也许这里还有另一个线索。
E q u and x e s
E q u 还有xes
if both.
如果两者兼而有之。
Oh! Ow!
哦！ 哦！
Oh, it hurt me.
哦，它伤害了我。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
The ghost the fucking ghost heard me talk.
那个该死的鬼听到我说话了。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I'm so dumb oh.
我真是该死的哦。
Oh, my fault uses them.
哦，我的错使用它们。
They use. I forgot it uses my microphone.
他们使用。 我忘了使用我的麦克风。
A jar.
God damn itMan.
我敲。
Oh, all right.
哦那好吧。
All right. OK, ok, ok. OK.
好的。 好好好。 好的。
All this.
这一切。
If I can make it back,
I need to make it back.
如果我能回去，我需要回去。
Hello.
你好。
There he is. I found the clue.
他在那。 我找到了线索。
I found another clue.
我发现了另一个线索。
Where is it? I've.
它在哪里？ 我有。
Ah, it's the last part of the.
啊，是最后一部分了。
It's X.
是 X e s。
Yes, it's the last three letters are x s.
是的，它的最后三个字母都是 x s。
Yeah.
是的。
It has to be for the latter. Or something.
它必须是后者。 或者其他的东西。
I think so. Yeah.
我认同。 是的。
So the first 23 letters are
所以前 23 个字母是
I. Yeah,
我，是的，
why me?
为什么是我？
All right.
好的。
What !I didn't do anything.
我什么也没做。
I didn't do anything.
Well, I can crawl.
嗯，我能爬哎。
I can crawl
我可以爬行。
all right.
好的。
I think I got
我想我得到了
oh, fuck me.
哦，操我。
Fuck me. My
操， 我的
I can't believe I just said all right.
我不敢相信我刚才说的好。
I think we're good in that.
我认为我们在这方面做得很好。
I got it.
我得到了它。
Listen, sometimes
听着，有时候在生活中，我们会觉得没有出路，好吗？
in life,
we can feel like there's no way out, OK?
You're a sheep trapped in a maze.
你是一只困在迷宫里的羊。
You're back. Oh.
你回来了。 哦。
Designed by wolves.
由狼设计。
OK, I got you on
好的，我来救你
oh. Fuck me.
哦。 操。
But in a maze like that,
there's always two doors to choose from.
但在这样的迷宫中，总有两扇门可供选择。
And behold, one of those doors is all the
sweets and confectionary you can imagine.
看哪，其中一扇门就是你能想象到的所有糖果和糖果。
Fantastic.
极好的。
How come you bring this oh, no.
你怎么带这个哦，不。
Oh.
哦。
fan to McDonald's.
麦当劳的粉丝。
Burger King
but there's also another burger block.
汉堡王，但也有另一个汉堡块。
A Burger King Doyle.
Not a fan, not a friend.
汉堡王道尔。 不是粉丝，不是朋友。
The door is another door.
门是另一扇门。
Another door is harder to get through. Oh,
另一扇门更难通过。 哦，
if you want
如果你想冒险猜测，那扇门的另一边是什么？
to hazard a guess,
what's on the other side of that door?
You know,
I think it's alerted by the flight
你知道，我认为它是被手电筒惊到的
oh. Backing up.
哦。 备份。
I'm backing up.
我正在备份。
I'm backing the fuck up.
我支持他妈的。
Anyways,
I think it got alerted to anything.
无论如何，我认为它对任何事情都有警觉。
Do you
do you do anything except back it up?
除了备份之外，你会做任何事情吗？
I thrust forward.
我向前冲。
Oh, really? When, when, when?
哦真的吗？ 什么时候，什么时候，什么时候？
Right now.
现在。
You look who's in front of me right now.
Look who's in front me right now.
你看看现在谁在我面前。 看看现在谁在我面前。
I think I like that.
我想我喜欢这样。
Whatever, OK?
不管怎样，好吗？
I think that somebody has to activate
because I managed to get past him,
我认为必须有人激活，因为我设法超越了他，但我听说你们被屠杀了。
but I heard you guys getting slaughtered.
It's I came back for you.
是我回来找你了。
I had. To recite an entire passage
from one to the.
World of the. Soul. OK.
Another five if vox show four times.
I'm not going to lie
here's what I was doing.
我不会在这里躺着，虽然这是我正在做的事情。
I was standing behind Vox
and I was flickering my flashlight on
我站在 Vox 身后，手电筒忽明忽暗，我听到了。
and off,
and I heard that. And he attacked.
而他发起了攻击。
Oh, god.
天啊。
Oh. So
哦。 所以
you see, the first time.
你看，第一次。
The first time I approached that door,
I thought it must be Jesus.
当我第一次走近那扇门时，我想那一定是耶稣。
On the other side, it's
not Jesus, it's another door.
另一方面，不是耶稣，而是另一扇门。
Where He wants to take the guests away
他想把客人从那扇门的另一边带走。
from the other side of that door.
I'm dead.
我死了。
Yes. It's Jesus.
是的。 是耶稣。
OK. OK.
好的。 好的。
Well, hello.
嗯，你好。
OK, good.
好的，很好。
We got it. Seems like we're good.
我们得到了它。 好像我们很好。
I think so.
我认同。
I know I am.
我知道我是。
Are you guys hanging in the trees?
你们是在树上挂吗？
Hello?
你好？
Hello. I'm
你好。 我是
I know.
我知道。
Where I am.
我在哪里。
Standing cowardly.
怯懦地站着。
Welcome back.
欢迎回来。
Is there anyone I might. Come back. To?
有没有人我可以。 回来。 到？
Uh, ok.
嗯，好的。
I think we need to go over here.
我想我们需要过去。
We never made a pass here.
我们从来没有通过这里。
If you go down there, I think you find xes.
如果你去那里，我想你会找到x-e-s的线索。
I'm pretty sure that's where I found it.
我很确定那是我找到它的地方。
Yeah, if you head down here, I think.
是的，如果你往这里，我想。
I don't know if there's any other.
我不知道还有没有其他的。
Paths
路径。
is there another path.
有没有另一条路。
And see us?
见我们？
Yeah. And there's these statues.
是的。 还有这些雕像。
Yeah. Yeah,
是的。 是的，
that one got me to
那个吓我了
hell. Yeah.
是的。
A little jump
一点跳跃
all right, you little.
好吧，你这个小家伙。
Man. I'm dead.
Vox:我死了。
I can't pay electric bill.
我付不起电费。
Isn't fucked up.
是不是搞砸了?
I'm laughing. I don't know
我为啥在笑。 我不知道
where are they?
他们在哪？
Oh, no.
不好了。
Like they told you.
就像他们告诉你的那样。
Tell you to, like, stand still,
but doesn't
告诉你，比如，站着不动，但实际上并没有用。
really work.
Like, works when it feels like it.
喜欢，当它感觉像的时候工作。
Oh, crawl to me.
哦，爬到我身边。
I can't see anything.
我什么都看不见。
I don't know where you are.
我不知道你在哪里。
Man. I'm dead
Ike: 我死了
or I got less.
或者我得到的更少。
I gotcha, gotcha and less.
我来救你。
And unless.
除非。
Yeah, you're not dying on me.
是的，你不会死在我身上。
Oh, dude, you're huge. Huge.
哦，伙计，你好大。
Are you in the eye? I am sorry, folks.
你在眼里吗？ 对不起，伙计们。
Welcome back.
欢迎回来。
I'm sorry.
对不起。
Like, are you in the bushes right now? I
比如，你现在在灌木丛中吗？ 一世
a friend for years in the bushes.
在灌木丛中多年的朋友。
That's not got someplace else.
那是没有别的地方的。
Like, a long way.
就像，很长的路。
That's a very bad idea.
这是一个非常糟糕的主意。
Let's go back how we go back. OK.
让我们回到我们如何回去。 好的。
Do you guys know the way back?
你们知道回去的路吗？
Where do we go?
我们去哪里？
I'm just going to go this way.
我只是要走这条路。
I think it might be fun.
我想这可能很有趣。
Yeah, sounds good to me.
Sounds good to me.
是的，对我来说听起来不错。 听起来不错。
I really. I really enjoyed the first one.
我真的。 我真的很喜欢第一个。
I really enjoyed that experience
because we just walked out and we saw
我真的很喜欢那种体验，因为我们刚刚走出去，我们看到你们两个走出去，你们的角色模型又开始了。
you two walk out and your character model
just begins again.
Oh, this is the axis area for
哦，这是轴区域。
you guys.
你们。
Just scared me, so. Yeah, no, that was.
只是吓到我，所以。 是的，不，那是。
Nothing in this game. It scared me so far.
这场比赛什么都没有。 到现在都吓到我了。
Oh, my
天啊。
dear one.
亲爱的。
I got scared by. He did.
我被吓到了。 他做到了。
She did a little jump.
她做了一个小小的跳跃。
But when he saw I was so adorable.
但是当他看到我时，我是如此可爱。
I said I didn't even know
you could jump in this game.
我说我甚至不知道你可以参加这个游戏。
The XY is at the end.
XY 位于末尾。
We already were here.
我们已经在这里了。
No, it's just me to get past the dude,
you know.
不，只有我才能越过这家伙，你知道的。
Really?
真的吗？
It's like the moment you hear him,
就像你听到他的那一刻，你真的别无选择。
you don't really have a choice.
wait I got you.
没事我来救你。
Oh, poor Vox.
哦，可怜的vox。
The zam ification.
All right, grandpa, where are you?
好的，爷爷，你在哪里？
What do
做什么
oh, this is bad.
哦，这很糟糕。
Oh, that's not good.
哦，那不好。
It's damned if you do.
如果你这样做，那就该死了。
Damned if you don't.
如果你不这样做，那该死的。
If you don't move
and he walks into you, you're dead.
如果你不动，他走进你，你就死定了。
And if you move to get stand
out of the way,
如果你移动到让路，你就死定了。
you're dead.
That's all I have, like, 3 seconds.
等我来扶你起来，3 秒。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Holding. Oh.
保持。 哦。
Love oh,
爱哦，我的上帝。
my God.
We are three people.
我们是三个人。
Hello?
你好？
ok ok.
好像还行。
OK. Where the wait.
Where's where's the way out?
好的。 哪里等。 出口在哪里？
Where's the way up on the sound?
声音的上升方向在哪里？
Here is not the way
这不是办法
you would go down.
你会倒下的。
We let's to go down this way.
我们就这样下去吧。
That's where you went. Exactly.
那是你去的地方。 确切地。
That's where we have to go, though.
不过，那是我们必须去的地方。
And we turn here.
我们转向这里。
I think.
我认为。
You and I don't think.
你我都不觉得。
This is look familiar.
这是似曾相识的。
I think
I think you need to hide in the bushes
我想我觉得你需要躲在灌木丛里。
yeah.
是的。
I think you're supposed
to stand off to the side here.
我认为你应该站在一边。
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. I
是的，是的，是的，是的。 我。
you're right.
你说的对。shoto
Shoto oh.
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
She caught me.
她抓住了我。
I didn't see him.
我没有看到他。
Oh, motherfucker.
哦，混蛋。
I told you, my right.
我告诉你了的对吧。
You mean my right
or your right? No, right.
你是说我对还是你对？ 没有吧。
oh my God.
像上帝一样。
Wait. Yeah.
等下 是的。
This is the way out here.
This is the puzzle.
这是这里的出口。 这就是谜题。
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's the way out is the way out.
耶耶耶。 就是这样。这是出口。
You want it out, you want to end.
你想要它，你想要结束。
You want to go back in.
你想回去。
But we have we have six letters, right?
但是我们有六个字母，对吧？
Oh, really?
哦真的吗？
Oh, yeah. We need the middle three, right?
哦耶。 我们需要中间三个，对吧？
Yeah. Oh, yeah, that's true.
是的。 哦，是的，这是真的。
Oh, my God.
Where are the middle? Three letters.
我的天啊。 中间在哪里？ 三个字母。
Do that. Squeezebox?
去做。 挤压箱？
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Where is he? Heard him.
他在哪里？ 听到他了。
I think I heard him yelling.
我想我听到他大喊大叫了。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Yeah.
是的。
I'll go back and get on
我会回去继续
I miss.
我想。
I miss him.
我想他。
I'll go back for the boy.
我会回去找那个鬼的。
The demon needs
恶魔需要恶魔杀手的帮助。
the help of the demon slayer.
Imagine that.
想象一下。
Vox Vox
Vox, are you there?
vox，你在吗？
VOX Well, if he's already back
Vox 好吧，如果他已经回来了
oh,what if he's already back, like,
he just slipped by.
对了，如果他已经回来了，就像，他只是溜了过去。
There's no way did he go check
他没办法去检查
he could already
他可能已经回来了，而我只是，就像，你知道的，看起来像个白痴，所以。
be back, and I just, like,
you know, look like an idiot, so.
But it's the thought that counts, right?
但重要的是思想，对吧？
The thought that counts
重要的是想法
all hello.
大家好，有人吗
Hello.
有人吗？
I'll wait.
我将等待。
Why is it so long?
为什么这么长？
Oh, my God, you.
哦，我的上帝，你。
The cornfields.
玉米地。
Ah, these aren't even cornfields.
啊，这些甚至不是玉米地。
These are just trees.
这些只是树。
I feel so lost right now.
我现在感觉迷路了。
This is insane.
疯了吧。
Yeah. Yeah, it definitely is.
是的。 是的，绝对是。
Yeah. All along, the three. Hi.
是的。 一直以来，三个。 你好。
All I want.
我所想要的。
I want back to.
我想回到。
Look for Vox, and he was already back
here, OK?
寻找 Vox，他已经回来了，好吗？
Yeah, yeah, yeah. He that he died.
耶耶耶。 他说他死了。
Or you were looking for Me.
Vox:你刚刚在找我吗？
Yeah, I thought your back of the cavern
by your cell phone.
是的，我通过手机想到了你在洞穴的背面。
I was. I was thinking some quick facts.
我曾是。 我在想一些简单的事实。
But that's a company.
但那是一家公司。
Equifax.
Equifax。
Tim English.
英语。
You you equate how do you say Equinox?
equate?或者春分
You're like in English.
用英语咋说。
Where. What is it?
在哪里。 它是什么？
And what even is like Equinox.
甚至像春分一样。
Know it. When?
知道。 什么时候？
When the sun. Equinoxes.
当太阳。 春分。
Yeah. Yeah, it might be that.
是的。 是的，可能就是这样。
Let me try.
That. I've never even heard of that. Word.
让我尝试。 那。 我什至从未听说过。 单词。
Oh, wait.
等一下。
I heard it in Avatar on it series.
我在《阿凡达》系列中听到过。
Yeah, it's like you ever heard of the
spring equinox and the summer solstice?
是啊，就像你听说过春分和夏至一样？
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
是的。 哦耶。
If everything is going to die
because of the fire station.
如果一切都会因为消防局而死亡。
OK, ok, ok. I've heard it in Swedish.
好好好。 我听说过瑞典语。
Non English.
非英语。
Everything changes.
一切都变了。
It, isn't he?
不是吗？
EQU  the duties of fire mission.
EQU，消防员的职责。
So that kind of makes sense.
所以这是有道理的。
You know, fire nation, the dude has like
five tattoos in his body.
你知道，鬼身上有火一样的纹身。
Kind of makes sense. Yeah.
有点道理。 是的。
Yeah.
是的。
EQUnox's and N.
equnox，有个N是吗？
Oh, yeah, that would that would
kind of make sense, wouldn't it?
哦，是的，那会有点道理，不是吗？
And so I'm so is my.
我也是。
Yo, we did it! Let's go oh.
成功了，让我们走吧！
Let's go fire a .
让我们庆祝一下.
Fuel gas.
燃气。
Also.
还。
Apparently the books are collectable,
显然这些书是可以收藏的，所以我们应该拿起书或类似00的东西。
so we should pick up the books
or something like 00.
What are the loading screen jumps Skip.
什么是加载屏幕跳转跳过。
Yeah, that's. True to me.
是的，就是这样。 对我来说是真的。
What we have a. And go.
我们有什么。
Lancer now.
现在的蓝瑟。
Oh yeah. We got a lot of pain.
哦耶。 我们很痛苦。
Oh this is so much better.
哦，这好多了。
I mean my radio is not working either.
我的意思是我的收音机也不工作。
It can move further into the maze
if I can get a signal.
如果我能得到信号，它可以进一步进入迷宫。
Joanne
信号是Joanne。
Joanne, Joanne.
乔安妮，乔安妮。
Joanne from June one wrong.
Fear.
恐惧。
My one.
我的唯一。
I like it, but I can make you
guys laugh with one of yours.
我喜欢它，但我可以借用它让你们笑。
Imagine imagine unironically being called
Juan and just.
想象一下，想象一下被称为胡安和正义。
Just being that horse.
就当那匹马。
One point
一点
was this a potato or no slot potato?
这是土豆还是没有槽土豆？
I love how it is.
我喜欢它的样子。
Like, slowly getting to know Spanish means
I love it here.
就像，慢慢了解西班牙语意味着我喜欢这里。
Well.
好。
It's something you don't get lost.
这是你不会迷失的东西。
All right, all right. I'm coming.
好吧，好吧。 我来了。
Up. Let's get us. Lost.
向上。 让我们得到我们。 丢失。
Why are the paths so much wider now?
为什么现在的路径这么宽？
This is not a scary.
这并不可怕。
It might narrow out.
它可能会缩小。
It may be the new monster
was like a different mechanic.
可能是新怪物就像一个不同的机械师。
Yeah, maybe he maybe he's a thick boy.
是的，也许他也许是个粗壮的男孩。
We'll have those six.
我们将拥有这六个。
Oh, yeah, we did.
哦，是的，我们做到了。
A thick boy.
一个粗壮的男孩。
Oh, I said, no.
哦，我说，没有。
I go. I think there's.
我去。 我认为有。
Something behind the gates.
I can hear it breathing.
大门后面的东西。 我能听到它的呼吸声。
One. One.
One, one. Oh.
哦。
Fuck you.
去你的。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
That's my fucking guy. But
那是我他妈的家伙。
you laugh.
你笑。
You really should stop here.
你真的应该停在这里。
Now, you do realise you're asking a bunch.
现在，你确实意识到你在问一堆。
Of people
that are traumatised by that nice.
那些被这种美好伤害的人。
Guy huh?
伙计吧？
It's definitely of all the fun and games.
这绝对是所有的乐趣和游戏。
Definitely out of the gate.
肯定是走出了大门。
It's definitely the funniest jump scare
noise.
这绝对是最有趣的跳跃恐慌噪音。
Like, it just sounds like someone
getting flattened by a car.
就像，听起来就像有人被汽车压扁了。
My guy.
我的家伙。
Who is the animatronic,
that gave me the most trouble.
谁是电子动画，给我带来了最大的麻烦。
I'm betting it's either like it's
oh, it's always balloon boy.
我敢打赌，要么就像哦，它总是气球男孩。
It's always. Balloon boy. Balloon shit.
总是如此。 气球男孩。 气球狗屎吧。
And what else?
还有什么？
Balloon boy?
气球男孩？
Oh, yeah, that's a be quiet.
哦，是的，那就是安静。
Shut the fuck up.
他妈的闭嘴。
That new guy I think it's a new guy.
那个新人，我觉得是个新人。
I'm different.
我不一样。
Yeah.
是的。
What was that?
那是什么？
Ew dropped it still.
恶心。扔掉吧。
What's he doing?
他在做什么？
Why is he dropping the dump?
他为什么要丢垃圾？
We got to stop him.
This is a public place.
我们必须阻止他。 这是一个公共场所。
He can't do. That. I don't think.
他做不到。 那。 我不这样认为。
I think I thought he was pooping.
我想我以为他在拉屎。
And me, not one. Ain't anything. Pooping.
而我，一个也没有。 不是什么。 拉屎。
Oh, it's so dark down here.
哦，这里太黑了。
It's behind the gates.
它在大门后面。
I guess we're face faced. Safe for now.
我想我们是面对面的。 暂时安全。
Yeah,
I think. I think he's behind the gates.
是的，我想。 我认为他在大门后面。
If anyone else finds themselves
locked in here.
如果其他人发现自己被锁在这里。
I'm sorry. I'm closing the gate behind me.
对不起。 我正在关上身后的门。
That thing has been travelling me
through the maze
自从我拉动控制杆以来，那东西一直在迷宫中穿行，我能听到它重重的脚步声，而且是刺耳的呼吸声。
ever since I pull the lever, I can hear it
thumping steps and it's raspy breath.
I need to get away from it.
我需要远离它。
I'm not sure I can keep going.
我不确定我能否继续前进。
That's following me.
那是跟着我。
One. Guys, the other tape, I got to say
一。 伙计们，另一盘磁带，我得说是解锁的。 解锁正门。
unlocked. Unlock the main gate.
Get him in the maze.
让他进入迷宫。
Farm field, take greenhouse
cages, take playground.
农田，拿温室笼子，拿操场。
Oh, managed to get.
哦，设法得到。
Through the first gate.
通过第一道门。
So to go to the greenhouse and around
playground, whatever but this second.
所以去温室和操场周围，除了这一秒。
Gate now.
马上关门。
There's
open space that I can see behind it.
我可以看到它后面的空地。
Which I'm willing to take.
Doesn't really say much.
我愿意接受。 真的不多说。
He's just like, I solved a puzzle and
I got him, but I can't get any further.
他就像，我解决了一个难题，我得到了他，但我无法继续前进。
OK, now, Felicity.
好的，现在，费利西蒂。
How can I get the damn thing open.
我怎样才能打开这该死的东西。
I hear the tape is over, but the tape
didn't really didn't share anything.
我听说磁带结束了，但磁带并没有真正分享任何东西。
Like, he was just like, Oh, Dwight.
就像，他就像。
He sounds constipated.
他听起来便秘。
The tape is overrated.
磁带被高估了。
You hear that?
你听到了吗？
There comes
来了
sounds like a mummy.
像木乃伊一样的声音。
Sounds like.
听上去像。
It. Sounds like it's right in front of us.
它。 听起来它就在我们面前。
Yeah, he's probably walking
through the corridor, past the trees,
是的，他可能正在穿过走廊，经过树木，
one on the right
右边一个
come on.
来吧。
Reason why they gave us lanterns
instead of flashlights.
他们给我们灯而不是手电筒的原因。
They're so much worse.
他们要糟糕得多。
I don't know.
我不知道。
If you like the way more. It's just maybe.
如果你更喜欢这种方式。 只是也许。
It looks like lanterns.
它看起来像灯笼。
I see.
我懂了。
I see the person
more like the actual person better.
我看到的人更接近真实的人。
I see. I see more with the lantern.
我懂了。 我看到更多的灯笼。
I feel like we connect better
when I use a lantern.
当我使用灯笼时，我觉得我们的联系更好。
Oh. Collectable.
哦。 可收藏。
Collectable.
可收藏。
All right.
好的。
It's highly collectable.
它具有很高的收藏价值。
All right, Glowsticks.
好吧，荧光棒。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
You guys have a watch guys
watch Jemmy Neutron.
你们有一块手表，看杰米中子。
I, i it's breathing down my throat.
我，我它在我的喉咙里呼吸。
I mean, my, my, my neck.
我的意思是，我的，我的，我的脖子。
Why? My throat?
为什么？ 我的喉咙？
My neck.
我的脖子。
I meant. Yeah.
我的意思是。 是的。
Was breathing. What it's like.
正在呼吸。 它是什么样的。
Who is fucking Carl Weasley?
谁他妈的卡尔韦斯莱？
Is he wheezing down your throat?
他在你的喉咙里喘息吗？
I Jimmy's mom.
我是吉米的妈妈。
What's wrong? Shoto. That shouldn't be.
怎么了？ Shoto。 那不应该。
You're craving my cat.
你渴望我的猫。
So she do want a cross honouring.
所以她确实想要一个十字勋章。
Shut the fuck up.
快闭嘴吧。
Ike, whare are u.
Ike,你搁哪呢？
There's a monster.
这里有个怪物。
Wait, I just have one more and then.
等等，我就再来一张。
That'll be it.
就是这样。
Hey reimu,Reimu
嘿蕾姆蕾姆？
yeah.
是的。
Where the fuck do you go
你他妈去哪儿了
I'm searching for?
我在寻找？
Think she went to the forest?
以为她去了森林？
I wasn't.
我不是。
That bad.
那么不好。
Fuck off your scared me,stop
滚开你吓人啊你，停下来
bastard. OK.
混蛋。 好的。
Push British man you British man get back
here,
英国人，你这英国人回到这里，
please. Ike
请。 ike
I partner.
我搭档。
I lost my life partner I cannot canin
我失去了我的伴侣，Ike。
my essay I.
Like.
像。
He's off.
他下线了吗。
OK, here. Hold on My goal.
好的，这里。 坚持我的目标。
Mike All.
迈克·奥尔。
The game loves winning
I thought What the fuck is that?
游戏喜欢赢我想那他妈的是什么？
More I It's not back here
更多我不回来了
take it back now it's not back there.
现在把它拿回来，它不回来了。
I think he turned out
he want my one down this way.
我想他原来是这样想我的。
Professor,
教授，我的实验室搭档无处可寻。
my lab partner is nowhere to be found.
We found exposed stick.
我们发现了暴露的棍子。
Oh, blue.
哦，蓝色。
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
是啊是啊。 耶耶耶。
Wait, I did go down this way.(Reimu:where's ike)
等等，我确实是这样下去的。(Reimu:Ike人呢？）
Left a trail.
留下了踪迹。
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
耶耶耶。
what was that?
那是什么？
Look behind you.
看看你身后。
We we got locked up.
我们被锁住了。
Is that what happens to Ike?
I think he got locked.
这是Ike遭遇的事情吗？ 我想他也被锁住了。
Shit.Oh no.
不。
I think in late, I heard a guy.
我想晚了，我听到了一个人。
All in all, we're stuck.
总而言之，我们被困住了。
Do just take the stay off me yourself. Me?
不要离开我。 我？
I don't want to get locked away
behind some roots over here.
我不想被锁在这里的一些根后面。
I think
我认为
I do those creepy.
我做那些令人毛骨悚然的事情。
You are super creepy.
你超级吓人。
And remind me of Harry Potter.
让我想起哈利波特。
You remind me of everything.
你让我想起了一切。
What's it called?
这叫什么？
One. I'm in
一。
the one of a part of EB.
EB的一部分。
When Gary and
当加里和
Gibbon Mary got separated.
长臂猿玛丽分开了。
The trail stops here.
小径在此停止。
Which will stay here.
哪个会留在这里。
I don't think it would have said a
player has died.
我不认为它会说一个玩家已经死了。
I found the house.
我找到了房子。
Hello?
你好？
Someone locked in here.
有人锁在这里。
Oh, is that Ike?
哦，是艾克吗？
Hello.
你好。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Guilties
友友们。
hello.
你好。
Ah, I think I'm.
啊，我想我是。
I'm the all.
我是一切。
All. That's not good.
全部。 这是不好的。
I just put my glowsticks
to let people know I was here.
我只是放了我的荧光棒让人们知道我在这里。
Is pretty bad.
很糟糕。
Blow.
吹。
Why not find my glowsticks
为什么找不到我的荧光棒
i think he might have died.
我想他可能已经死了。
I think the monster got remote. OK,
我认为怪物走远了。 好的，
I'm the only one here at the moment.
我是目前唯一在这里的人。
The mixture evaporates.
混合物蒸发。
What mixture?
什么混合物？
Odds and vines reacts.
奇数和藤蔓反应。
The common pesticides just to make my own.
普通的杀虫剂就是自己做的。
Is this.
这是。
Chloride?
氯化物？
hello hello?
你好你好？
The fuck was that.
他妈的就是这样。
Chloride reacting of yellow and green dye?
黄色和绿色染料的氯化物反应？
Need to swap it with another bottle.
需要换另一瓶。
Need some move.
需要一些动作。
What is that?
那是什么？
C-H seven from red to yellow
C-H 七从红到黄
sulphate.
硫酸盐。
I sell sulphur oxygen in green chickens
nationally.
So far the valve on red leaking
do not use a cell or stage seven
到目前为止，红色泄漏的阀门不使用电池或第七级。
blue dye holding up
well should be ok to leave
蓝色染料保持良好应该可以离开。
C chloride in their
C氯化物在他们。
CB breaking down an all balls except red
CB 击破除红球外的所有球。
guys.
伙计们。
Give me an update.
给我一个更新。
What's happening
with the others right now.
其他人现在正在发生什么。
And ah is Voxs is Vox  and reimu are good?
呃Vox和Reimu还好吗
I do chemistry
我在做化学相关的任务。
Vox died.
Vox又死了。
Ah wow.
啊哇。
That's bad.
那很不好。
While the game split us up
当游戏把我们分开时
it's mixture evaporates what's.
它是混合物蒸发了什么。
What goes off blue.
什么变蓝了。
What I start with
我从什么开始
yellow and green
黄色和绿色
yellow
黄色和绿色 我的目标更新了我做了什么？
and green my objective updated
what did I do?
I do something.
我做点什么。
I don't know if I did anything or not.
我不知道我做了什么。
It's a swap off another bottle
这是换掉另一瓶
mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
All right.
好的。
I'm really confused.
我真的很困惑。
I need their help right now
because I know if I need more bottles
我现在需要他们的帮助，因为我知道我是否需要更多的瓶子或什么，我会回去的。
or a what I'm just going to head back.
Like, please hope I can find them.
希望我能找到他们。
They found each other.
他们找到了彼此。
OK, good, good, good, good, good.
好，好，好，好，好，好。
Oh, now
哦，现在
I feel so lost.
我感到迷路了。
It's here.
是这里。
I feel so goddamn lost.
我觉得我该死的迷路了。
In this maze
在这个迷宫中
oh, no.
不好了。
Should I just die
我应该死了，这样我才能和他们重新会合吗？
so I can regroup with them?
Where is it
它在哪里
where is the creature oh.
那个生物在哪里。
Hello.
你好。
What is this clue?
这是什么线索？
Oh, yeah, they've been here before.
哦，是的，他们以前来过这里。
It's like there's like Glowsticks
gone into this direction.
就像有荧光棒一样朝这个方向发展。
But well.
不过还好。
This is a dead end.
这是一个死胡同。
OK, I'm going to.
好的，我要去。
Yeah, I'll quickly die so I can regroup
with them since I don't know.
是的，我会很快死去，这样我就可以和他们重新会合，因为我不知道。
Right now, being separate feels
现在，分开的感觉
not so good.
不太好。
It's probably not the best idea right now.
现在可能不是最好的主意。
Uh, where is the.
呃，在哪里。
Hollow. Creature?
空洞的。 生物？
Do you hear me?
你听到我了吗？
Hello?
你好？
I'm a human close by, but.
我是附近的人类，但是。
I don't or
我没有或
what the.
什么。
Fuck was that?
他妈的是吗？
Oh, my God, guys, I lost you.
哦，天哪，伙计们，我失去了你们。
I got you
我救你
you got me.
你救了我。
I found you.
我找到你。
Where is everybody?
大家都去哪了？
I lost them like I was by myself for
the longest time, so I had to come back.
我失去了他们，就像我一个人呆了很长时间一样，所以我不得不回来。
Yeah, find somebody to me to all the shit
I saw.
是的，找到我看到的所有事情的人。
You get clobbered. By him
from the distance.
你会受到打击。 由他远方。
That was crazy. What is that?
那太疯狂了。 那是什么？
Does he have a clone?
他有克隆人吗？
No. He's
some kind of a terrifying tree spirit.
不，他是某种可怕的树精。
All right,
I guess it's just you and me now.
好吧，我想现在只有你和我了。
Yeah, they're really far in. They're.
是的，他们真的很远。他们是。
I'm apparently, I think one of them
or a couple of them died.
我显然是，我认为他们中的一个或几个死了。
Unless I was you that died multiple times.
除非我是你，死了很多次。
I I've re spawned manually.
我已经手动重新生成了。
One think he would help me
find people, but.
有人认为他会帮我找人，但是。
OK, so I think that means that I think
Ike died.
好的，所以我认为这意味着我认为Ike死了。
And Reimu also died.
reimu也死了。
Oh, now, I don't know, brah.
哦，现在，我不知道。
I saw a couple deaths.
我看到了成对的死亡。
Yeah. Did you ever die?
是的。 你有没有死过？
No. I avoided him there all.
不，我全都避开了他。
Way if we can just go back.
如果我们能回去就好了。
We should just go grab him.
我们应该去抓住他。
Yeah, I grab everybody.
是的，我抓住每个人。
What happened. Though.
发生了什么。 尽管。
Was, like,
是，就像，我和雷米正在穿过迷宫，就像，一个藤蔓
me and Raymie were going through the maze,
and there was like, a vines
that grew up behind us and separated us
from everybody else, and then.
它在我们身后长大，将我们与其他人分开，然后。
Oh, OK.
哦好的。
I'm OK. They both died.
They both dead. OK.
我很好。 他们都死了。 他们都死了。 好的。
So the game like, wants to separate us.
所以游戏就像，想把我们分开。
I think it should be a round about here.
我想这应该是一个回合。
Or there back at the. Ah.
或者回到那里。 啊。
Hello.
你好。
Hello?
你好？
Hello.
你好。
Hello? Hello.
你好？ 你好。
You guys hear
你们听到
Reimu Ike?
Do they have a new save point?
他们有新的存档点吗？
Did they find it like a different area?
他们发现它像一个不同的区域吗？
There's no way.
不可能。
Hello.
你好。
Tre, go.
走。
I'll. No, I'm here.
患病的。 不，我在这里。
Ominous sound effects.
I feel like this is the wrong way.
不祥的音效。 我觉得这是错误的方式。
Yeah, stuff.
是的，东西。
Definitely the horn with the fuck out.
绝对是他妈的喇叭。
Wait, that's them.
等等，就是他们。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Friends we thought we found one steal,
and then I found another puzzle room.
朋友们，我们以为我们找到了一个关卡点，然后我又找到了另一个拼图室。
Yeah.
是的。
I found the chemistry area. Hmm.
我找到了化学区。 唔。
They said Nick is a. Naked.
他们说有一个裸女跑向你。
Lady runs towards you.
Yeah. And I got beaten up.
是的。 而且我被打了。
I got beaten up by a naked man.
我被一个裸男殴打。
Yeah, I watched it happen.
是的，我看着它就这么打我。
It was pretty terrifying.
这太可怕了。
He's huge.
他是巨大的。
I think. I think. I think there would be.
我认为。 我认为。 我想会有的。
If this is not a face,
you can stand still.
如果这不是一张脸，你可以站着不动。
I'm sorry.
对不起。
You guys hear that?
There she is. Oh, she's coming right out.
你们听到了吗？ 她在这里。 哦，她马上就出来了。
Oh, let's get out of here.
哦，让我们离开这里。
OK, so.
好的，所以。
I'm not ready to die again.
我还没准备好再次死去。
And it works with the flashlight.
它适用于手电筒。
I say point the flashlight at her. Oh.
我说用手电筒对着她。 哦。
God, you bitch. Oh.
天哪，你个婊子。 哦。
You shall. Not really.
你应该。 并不真地。
It doesn't work that well.
它不能那么好。
Oh, it kind of does.
哦，确实如此。
Oh, it does. One.
哦，确实如此。 一。
Oh. Oh, oh. Oh rock through.
哦。 哦，哦。 他来了。
Running vox vox.
跑啊Vox。
Back up, back up, back up.
备份，备份，备份。
She's giving everyone.
她在给每个人来一刀。
She got a triple kill.
她拿到了三杀。
What's
什么是
what is that?
那是什么？
I mean, the flashlight kind of works.
我的意思是，手电筒有点用。
Please. I guess you can all go near her.
请。 我想你们都可以靠近她。
Oh, your theory of, like,
blinded motherfucker.
哦，你的理论，就像瞎了眼的混蛋。
Would you go back? She was.
你会回去吗？ 她。
She was. Spooked by the light for a. Bit.
她。 被灯光吓了一跳。 少量。
Yeah,
she was, like, trying to cover her eyes.
是的，她就像，试图遮住她的眼睛。
Yeah.
是的。
Was it flashing it on and off?
是不是一闪一闪的？
That helps her. I don't know.
这对她有帮助。 我不知道。
I think I just. Pointed out
you just got a point. Out.
我想我只是。 指出你刚刚得到了一点。 出去。
OK, that's to you.
好的，那是给你的。
I think. I think it stops there for a bit.
我认为。 我认为它会停在那里一点。
Yeah, OK.
是的，好的。
She's there.
她在那。
There's another dude. There's another guy.
He just.
还有一个哥们 还有一个人。 他只是。
There's two.
There's two. They're coming together.
有两个。 有两个。 他们正在走到一起。
Yeah. No, no.
是的。 不，不。
Switch over to the lantern.
切换到灯笼。
That works
这样可行。
she's so fucking slow.
她真是太他妈慢了。
Look at her.
看着她。
OK, maybe it doesn't work.
好吧，也许它不起作用，嘿嘿。
OK, I'm going to go into the
好的，我要进入
ow! Ow, ow, ow, ow.
哦！ 呜呜呜呜呜呜
Hey, hey.
嘿，嘿。
I thought it worked.
我认为它有效的。
It did not.
它没有。
Guy got my balls.
它在攻击我，哦，我的蛋蛋。
She dropped them off.
她把它们放下了。
I got you.
I got you. I got you. I got you.
我接到你了。 我接到你了。 我接到你了。 我接到你了。
I got you, I got you. Oh,
我得到了你，我得到了你。 哦，
then I got. You.
然后我得到了。 你。
Oh, no,
不好了，
I grabbed your dang it.
我抓住了你该死的。
Cock and balls.
Ow, ow, ow.
呜呜呜
All of us died.
我们都死了。
Yeah, we.
是的，我们。
Got quadra killed.
被杀了.
All right, everybody, welcome back.
好的，大家，欢迎回来。
We're back in the cabin. Oh, man.
我们回到了出生点。 天啊。
That is.
那是。
That is one tough cookie.
那是一块坚硬的饼干。
I feel like.
我觉得像。
Like they're blinding.
就像他们眼花缭乱。
Thing only works sometimes.
事情只是有时有效。
Yeah. And then when it works,
it gives us enough time.
是的。 然后当它起作用时，它给了我们足够的时间。
So, you know.
所以你知道。
The access game and all that.
访问游戏等等。
Oh. We reimu all there.
哦。 我们删除那里的所有内容。
There we go. Reimu just died.
我们去吧。 Reimu刚刚死掉了
Low flying along.
一路低飞。
Oh, you just kind of folded
it folded up like a deck.
哦，你只是把它折叠起来，就像一个甲板。
Do we got?
我们有吗？
What we need to do is
you use the flashlight, not the lantern.
我们需要做的是你使用手电筒，而不是灯笼。
The flashlight, and
then you blind blender, and then you run.
手电筒，然后你瞎搅拌，然后你跑。
I think that's the only thing.
我认为这是唯一的事情。
Yeah, we got a blender
and then one she, like, cowers for a bit.
是的，我们有一个搅拌机，然后她，就像，畏缩了一下。
Yeah, we can.
是的，我们可以。
We have time to run away and make distance
我们有时间逃跑并保持距离，因为我们不能像在树里一样寒冷。
because we can't just, like,
chill inside the tree.
Know, I was pretty far away from Ike,
but she still got me, so I think we just
知道，我离艾克很远，但她还是抓住了我，所以我想我们只需要融入，然后逃跑。
need to blend in, then run.
OK, but
we got to make it back to the puzzle.
好的，但我们必须回到这个谜题。
Me and. The puzzle. Yeah. I also find.
我和。 谜题。 是的。 我也找。
My puzzle two left glow sticks things
I have.
我的谜题是我有的两个左荧光棒。
Puzzle one. You.
谜题一。 你。
Oh, I just have a sense for like.
哦，我只是有一种喜欢的感觉。
She said, I said he lied.
她说，我说他撒谎。
I see
我懂了
there they are.
他们在那里。
Here they come
他们来了。
and Run.
跑啊。
Run, run, run, run, run, run, run.
跑，跑，跑，跑，跑，跑，跑，跑。
I'm with her in this corner.
我和她在这个角落。
She left to turn left.
她离开去左转。
Yeah, but then she left.
是的，但后来她离开了。
Kind of an. Upper left.
一种。 左上。
You look at my. Look at my bike.
你看看我的。 看看我的自行车。
Hey, he's turning left.
嘿，他在左转。
Oh. When I go the I go left.
哦。 当我去的时候，我向左走。
I don't know where I went.
I went somewhere else.
我不知道我去了哪里。 我去了别的地方。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Either.
任何一个。
Oh, my God. She's chasing ice.
我的天啊。 她在追冰。
Guys, I've had a puzzle.
伙计们，我有一个谜题。
Oh, no.
不好了。
You found a puzzle.
你发现了一个谜题。
Where
在哪里
puzzle
谜题？
Ike just like trying to blame her
and then actively running away from.
Ike好像试图躲过那个鬼，然后逃走。
Yeah, he's hiding her really well.
是的，他藏得很好。
OK, guys, got to tape. Tape to tape.
好的，伙计们，开始录音了。 磁带到磁带。
Oh, there is a tape here.
哦，这里有磁带。
For I think he's doing.
因为我认为他正在做。
Is he still running?
他还在跑吗？
You can burn.
你可以燃烧。
All are you to the.
都是你给的。
Spiders.
蜘蛛。
You've been attacked by a virtual world,
你受到了虚拟世界的攻击，实际上是你自己。
literally on your own.
You have handled it like OK.
你已经处理好了。
OK, maybe this isn't a puzzle.
好吧，也许这不是一个谜。
Maybe it's just me.
也许这只是我。
I think because.
我想是因为。
It was kind of
more like a collectable area.
它更像是一个收藏区。
Rather than a puzzle.
而不是拼图。
Got a tape galore.
得到了一大盘磁带。
That's what we're here for, right?
这就是我们来这里的目的，对吧？
Oh, no.
不好了。
Vox. Vox vox.
vox
Hello? Vox.
你好？ 狐狸。
Vox. I think we got separated.
狐狸。 我想我们分开了。
Oh, no. Vox Oh, shit.
不好了。  Vox 哦，该死。
Dude, that's bad. Fuck.
伙计，这很糟糕。 他妈的。
Vox I think we got separated.
Vox 我想我们分开了。
Oh, no.
不好了。
I can't get to you.
我无法接近你。
I can't get to you. I'm separated.
我无法接近你。 我正在分离。
The vines are in the way.
葡萄藤挡住了路。
Oh, no,
不好了，
how do I get you there?
我怎样才能到你那里？
I don't. I don't think I can.
我不。 我不认为我可以。
You'll have the chemical
你会得到化学物质。
oh, this is so sad.
哦，这太可悲了。
I can we get ten gifted subs all there.
我可以在那里得到十个礼物订阅。
What do I do?
我该怎么办？
What I do, I go
我做什么，我去
What is that?
那是什么？
Who is that guy?
那家伙是谁？
I think.
我认为。
I think it's Gigi for me.
我认为这对我来说是完了。
Well,
好，
well,
I'm back
我回来了
I got crushed by that giant,
towering beast.
我被那巨大而高耸的野兽压死了。
There's two monsters
inside this labyrinth.
这个迷宫里面有两个怪物。
I didn't think that was going to be like,
two of them.
我没想到会是这样，他们两个。
I thought it was just going to be one
我以为这只是一个新的，但现在有两个我们必须提防。
new one, but now there's two
we have to watch out for.
That's really creepy.
这真是令人毛骨悚然。
I got separated again and know.
我又分开了，我知道了。
And then I was all alone.
然后我就一个人了。
You can have nice things.
你可以拥有美好的事物。
Yeah, we can have nice things.
是的，我们可以拥有美好的事物。
Oh, I hear.
哦，我听到了。
I hear people.
我听人说。
Hello, friends.
大家好。
Yeah, we're. In the puzzle room.
是的，我们是。 在拼图室。
Probably like
大概喜欢
hooking up with the lady.
勾搭上的女士。
You the the
the monsters right in front of me.
你就是我面前的怪物。
The monsters right in front of me. OK.
怪物就在我面前。 好的。
Guys, guys,
what do I do? He's he's. Right.
伙计们，伙计们，我该怎么办？ 他是他的。 对。
It's just coming from, like.
它只是来自，就像。
All they're dying.
他们都快死了。
All my friends are getting massacred
right in front of me.
我所有的朋友都在我面前被屠杀。
I can't do anything about it.
我对此无能为力。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
Let me see mhm.
让我看看嗯。
I'm. I'm quite.
我是。 我相当。
I'm kind of confused about how the vet can
make it over there in time to to revive.
我有点困惑兽医如何能及时赶到那里复活。
Maybe. Maybe. Hello? Hello? No.
也许。 也许。 你好？ 你好？ 不。
Make it in time.
及时做好。
Run! Why are you running?
跑！ 你为何跑？
Why are you running?
你为何跑？
Because I'm running to save my friends.
因为我跑去救我的朋友。
Objective. Updated. Wait.
客观的。 更新。 等待。
They. They solved something.
他们。 他们解决了一些问题。
Oh, that's pretty good.
哦，那还不错。
I got to make it over to them.
我必须把它交给他们。
Like, I'm, like, so lost right now.
就像，我，就像，现在迷路了。
I'm so lost. Player just died.
我很迷茫。 玩家刚刚死了。
Wow. Poggers.
哇。 Poggers。
Actually, that's not poggers.
实际上，并没有多pog。
Maybe I can go back and retrieve
them. Hmm.
也许我可以回去取回它们。 唔。
We'd like respond.
我们想回应。
Hi. Hi. Hi.
你好。 你好。 你好。
They expect you to do this stuff,
with permit death.
他们希望你做这些事情。
Are you serious?
你是认真的吗？
Yeah, dude,
that's why I'm. That's why they told me.
是的，伙计，这就是我为什么。
To turn off. Permits death. No way.
这就是他们告诉我关掉permit death的原因。
We would have. We would have, like, guns.
我们会有。 我们会拥有枪支。
OK, I saw. I saw the tree guy.
好的，我看到了。 我看到了树。
I think both of them work the same way.
我认为它们的工作方式相同。
They see you
from a really far away distance,
他们从很远的距离看到你，但我认为手电筒在交易中不起作用。
but I don't think the flashlight works
in the trade.
Few moments later.
几分钟之后。
Yeah, there's basically two of them.
是的，基本上有两个。
Also, they have, like, a certain rule,
而且，他们有一定的规则，他们一路回到拼图室。
and they go all the way
back to the puzzle room.
Yeah, I figured out what to do for, like,
the puzzle that me and reimu have found.
是的，我知道该怎么做，比如我和reimu发现的谜题。
It's just going to take me a while.
这只是需要我一段时间。
And I don't remember where to find
the chemistry puzzle that I had earlier.
而且我不记得在哪里可以找到我之前的化学难题。
It's. That's.
它的。 那是。
That's like throwing me off.
这就像把我扔掉一样。
The whenever Vox went.
每当 Vox 去的时候。
Ah. Vox So, I mean, there.
啊。  Vox 所以，我的意思是，那里。
Oh, boy.
好家伙。
Yeah, he's somewhere in there.
是的，他在里面的某个地方。
Did he figure it out? I'm sorry.
他想清楚了吗？ 对不起。
Did you guys have what's it called?
你们有什么叫什么吗？
A decided objective? Got updated.
一个确定的目标？ 得到更新。
Someone solves a puzzle or.
有人解决了一个难题或。
Yeah. I didn't solve.
是的。 我没有解决。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
There she is.
她在这里。
My highlights.
我的亮点。
No, she says she's coming
不，她说她会来
off you.
离开你。
Run, run. Run, run, run.
跑跑。 跑，跑，跑。
Oh, no.
不好了。
I got separated.
我分开了。
You got to be kidding. Me.
你一定是在开玩笑。 我。
You got to be kidding me.
你一定是在开玩笑吧。
No, no, you got to be kidding me.
不，不，你一定是在开玩笑。
You locked me away.
你把我锁在了外面。
Fuck off the tree, guy.
去他妈的树，伙计。
To me.
对我来说。
Where is this.
这是哪里。
Oh. Oh, God.
哦。 天啊。
I'm alone.
我独自一人。
I need help.
我需要帮助。
What are your children?
你的孩子是什么？
Oh, this is so.
哦，原来如此。
Oh, my God. This is bad.
我的天啊。 这是不好的。
This is really. Bad.
这真的是。 坏的。
Oh, oh.
哦，哦。
Oh, hey, there.
哦，嘿，那里。
Hey, buddy.
你好朋友。
Hey. Hi.
嘿。 你好。
Oh. Well, I found a different area.
哦。 好吧，我发现了一个不同的区域。
That's a that's. That was weird.
那就是那个。 那很奇怪。
That was like a playground
or some type of shit
那就像一个游乐场或某种东西
is cool, though, but
虽然很酷，但是
who else died?
还有谁死了？
I know.
我知道。
I said somebody else died, but
我说别人死了，但是
I heard children laughing.
我听到孩子们的笑声。
All the lights went out.
所有的灯都熄灭了。
It bursted in front of me.
它在我面前炸开。
That was not fun.
那不好玩。
And then locks me away again. Why?
然后又把我锁了。 为什么？
This game is fucked up.
这游戏完蛋了
It likes isolating me
它喜欢孤立我
it really enjoys isolating me.
它真的很喜欢孤立我。
I think I heard them somewhere.
我想我在什么地方听到过。
That's either
那是要么
got their own lights, sex, drive, all that
拥有自己的灯光、性爱、驾驶，所有这些。
the monsters want me to themselves.
怪物想要我去找他们。
Like it's more like
喜欢它更像
they want to are my friends.
他们想成为我的朋友。
Oh, I know. I just want back in circles.
哦，我知道。 我只想回到圈子里。
What. Bro?
什么。 兄弟？
I just want back in circles.
我在圈子里。
Holy shit.
天啊。
I didn't even realise
I went back into a whole circle.
我什至没有意识到我又回到了一个完整的圈子里。
Oh, my God, man.
哦，天哪，伙计。
OK, knuckle.
好的，指关节。
I though the tree dude looks kind of nice
like his. Ah,
我觉得树哥看起来有点像他的。 啊，
like a style
像一种风格
I ah. I miss Vox.
我啊。 我想念沃克斯。
It's been a while since we saw Vox.
我们已经有一段时间没有看到 Vox 了。
The hell he go
他去的地狱
I can smell him
我能闻到他
because like,
it seems like he would go down this way
因为好像，他好像会这样下去
oh, maybe
哦，也许
actually.
实际上。
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
坚持，坚持，坚持，坚持。
There's a Gary here.
这里有一个加里。
Very been down here till I see red
一直在这里直到我看到红色
is follow the red.
跟着红色走。
All all
全部全部
hello.
你好。
I'm lost.
我搞不清楚了。
I'm. I'm just some lost boy.
我是。 我只是一个迷路的男孩。
I don't.
我不。
I'm, I, I got a family.
我，我，我有一个家庭。
I, uh.
我，呃。
Hello, friends.
大家好。
Hello.
你好。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
That's pretty bad.
这很糟糕。
This is pretty bad.
Oh, wait on me.
哦，等我。
Maybe I can all all Ike's drill
也许我可以全部 Ike 的演习
I can re drill.
我可以重新钻。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
I think again.
我再想想。
Megan, closer.
梅根，靠近一点。
Am I going closer?
我要靠近吗？
Am I going further?
我要走得更远吗？
Dude, I honestly can't tell.
哥们，我真的说不出来。
I can't tell at all.
我完全说不出来。
Where are we going?
我们去哪？
The fuck am I going?
我他妈要去吗？
Am I am I even at it's
or it's the right direction now or. Or
我是我现在还是正确的方向。 或者
oh, fuck that.
哦，去他妈的。
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不。
Well.
好。
Cock N balls
卧槽卧槽
cock N balls
卧槽
Oh, hello. Shoto.
哦，你好。Shoto
No. Died at the exact same time.
不，在同一时间死去。
Yeah, I saw the chance of death and I was
like, OK, I don't, I don't see anybody.
是的，我看到了死亡的机会，我想，好吧，我没有，我没有看到任何人。
I was alone again.
我又是一个人了。
Yeah.
是的。
I ran into a similar problem.
我遇到了类似的问题。
I found two of the disks.
We got two disks now.
我找到了两个磁盘。 我们现在有两个磁盘。
I was out the objectives updated.
我是更新目标出来的。
Yeah, yeah.
是啊是啊。
POG you know, actually, the objective
was updated because we found, like, this.
POG 你知道，实际上，目标是更新的，因为我们发现了这个。
Grassy field.
草场。
It with the big the big moss man in it.
它与大苔藓人在里面。
Oh, did you guys find the guys
from the playground yet?
哦，你们找到操场上的人了吗？
Mm. Yeah, I found the playground.
毫米。 是的，我找到了操场。
That's where I found that. The disk. Yeah.
I was there too.
那是我发现的地方。 磁盘。 是的。 我也在那里。
It was it's pretty creepy.
这是非常令人毛骨悚然的。
There's kids laughing and everything
有孩子在笑什么都有
don't like that.
我不喜欢那样。
Think they excited to go back to Resident
Evil.
认为他们很高兴回到生化危机。
Resident Evil seven. Yeah. I saw you.
生化危机七。 是的。 我看见你。
I've seen the little girl running around,
but she hasn't done anything
我见过那个小女孩跑来跑去，但她什么也没做，这让我很害怕。
and it freaks me out.
So you finished you beat up
what's her Margret beat Marguerite.
所以你打完你打了她玛格丽特是什么。
Yeah, I really fucking love
dramatic villain.
是的，我真的很喜欢戏剧性的恶棍。
Deaths like that make me very happy.
这样的死亡让我很开心。
Like when you just had it
with the flame thrower,
就像你刚刚用火焰喷射器一样，然后她就有点，就像，喷出来，转身吐出他妈的灰尘。
and then she just kind of, like,
splutters out and turns did fucking dust.
I was like, yeah.
我当时想，是的。
Yeah.
是的。
I was like, Oh, Ike Reimu.
我当时想，哦，艾克 reimu
He got another seal thinks.
他得到了另一个印章的想法。
He'll need two more SEALs.
他还需要两名海豹突击队员。
Reimus. Hello.
Reimu 你好。
The other place.
另一个地方。
There's a monster near you, I think.
我想你附近有一个怪物。
Watch out.
小心。
We. Yeah, the the the tree guy.
我们。 是的，那个树人。
Oh, this is a dead end.
哦，这是一个死胡同。
I think vox is dead end here, here.
我觉得,vox,这里是死胡同，这里。
All children shall watch out, watch out,
watch out.
所有的孩子都应该小心，小心，小心。
Oh, yeah, my glow.
哦，是的，我的光芒。
Oh, hey. Hello.
噢！嗨。 你好。
I gang's all together again.
我又聚在一起了。
OK, where's the altar?
好的，祭坛在哪里？
Where's the altar?
祭坛在哪里？
The altar. Like, which altar?
祭坛。 比如，哪个祭坛？
Where I put the seals.
我放印章的地方。
It's really, really close to here.
真的，真的离这里很近。
I'm not 100% sure where, but we'll find it
我不是 100% 确定在哪里，但我们会找到的，伙计。
dude.
The mount of like, I don't know, euphoria
喜欢的坐骑，我不知道，
I get when we all finally regroup together
God is so.
当我们终于重新在一起时，我明白了，上帝就是这样。
Yeah I had such an amazing moment
where I was completely lost in the maze.
是的，我有一个如此美妙的时刻，我完全迷失在迷宫中。
And then all of a sudden
I see reimu. I'm like.
然后突然间我看到了reimu。 我就像。
How did you find me? And she just said.
你是怎么找到我的？ 而她只是说。
I found your. Glowsticks.
我找到了你的荧光棒。
You haven't found the glowsticks I'm here.
你还没有找到我在这里的荧光棒。
But then it's just like we.
但是，它就像我们一样。
Got we got two discs in here already.
我们这里已经有两张光盘了。
Oh, yeah. Here. Yes. Ta da!
哦耶。 这里。 是的。 达达！
OK, ok, now we just need some more.
好的，好的，现在我们只需要更多。
We can ok.
我们可以的。
We can not get into the greenhouse
because we need a place in.
我们不能进入温室，因为我们需要一个地方。
Yeah, that's the thing. I don't.
是的，就是这样。 我不。
I was trying to figure out the
the what's it called?
我试图弄清楚它叫什么？
The pesticide formula.
农药配方。
It doesn't make any sense. To me.
Do we need to get something else?
这没有任何意义。 对我来说。 我们需要得到别的东西吗？
We need to get to that
chemistry room, so, like,
我们需要去那个化学室，所以，就像，这样我们才能理解她在说什么。
so we can understand
what she's talking about.
Yeah, I tried. Yeah,
I didn't understand it. My.
是的，我试过了。 是的，我没看懂。 我的。
Hold on. Is it? I know it's.
坚持，稍等。 是吗？ 我知道是。
Remember how you got there? Shelter.
还记得你是怎么到那里的吗？ 庇护所。
I know it's this way.
我知道是这样的。
I know it's
definitely this way of ghosting,
我知道这绝对是这种重影的方式，
but be careful.
不过要小心。
The game might separate us.
这场比赛可能会让我们分开。
And this is like where?
这就像在哪里？
I don't know, like,
which. Way to go. The vines.
我不知道，喜欢，哪个。 好样的。 葡萄藤。
The vines just, like, pop up sometimes
藤蔓有时会弹出。
yeah.
是的。
And it forces us to just stay separate.
它迫使我们保持独立。
So I think we should stick together
really close.
所以我认为我们应该非常紧密地团结在一起。
So it can't, like,
所以它不能，比如，
keep us from getting cut off.
防止我们被切断。
Oh. I'm will get.
哦。 我会得到。
I'm over door.
I've been building.
我一直在建造。
Yeah.
是的。
Anyway.
反正。
OK, what's this?
好的，这是什么？
This looks familiar.
I've been here before. This is close by.
这看起来很熟悉。 我以前来过这里。 这是附近。
This really lights of the chemistry.
这真的很化学。
Yeah, I think.
是的，我想。
OK, I'll take my glowsticks from here.
好的，我会从这里拿走我的荧光棒。
Ahh ohh.
There it went. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
它去了。 我的天啊。 我的天啊。
We all.
我们都。
But we're all together.
但我们都在一起。
We're all together. Again this time. Good.
我们都在一起。 这次又来了。 好的。
(SINGING)Oh, we're all in this together.
Reimu&Shoto歌声
What does that sound?
这啥声音？
I think it's just us singing.
我想只有我们在唱歌。
No, woo, you are so mean.
不，你也太刻薄了，我不允许唱歌吗
What the fuck?
什么鬼？
OK, now I don't know where to continue.
好的，现在我不知道从哪里继续。
But I love you singing.
但我爱你唱歌。
Ike:Oh, great.Reimu: Leave it to me. Sho:I love u too.
Ike:好极了。Reimu:哦我来带路。Sho：我也爱你~
You might end up with what
I'm on a bit of.
Reimu在小公鸡点到谁我就选谁
I don't know what you know.
If I follow this, I horse it.
You said I need your plastics
to .Right！
往右边走！
(Shoto的神奇咒语,听不懂)
Reimu.
蕾姆你，
Honestly,
that sounded like a fucking incantation.
老实说，你听起来像在念一个他妈的咒语。
I thought as a demon, I would have been**.(SCREAM)
我想，作为一个恶魔，我会是**。(啊啊啊)
What is this shit?
这是什么？
Oh, hello.
哦你好。
Bounce. Hello, gamers.
你好，游戏玩家。
Guys, guys.
伙计们，伙计们。
Well, say hi to the clown. Oh, hi. There.
好吧，跟小丑打个招呼。 啊，你好。
That was one of the freakiest things
I've seen in a game in a long time.
这是我这么久以来在游戏中看到的最诡异的东西之一。
Oh, I hated that.
哦，我讨厌那个。
They all were getting ingredients
for potions.
他们都在获取魔药的原料。
They all like.
他们都像是。
I got the tape.
我拿到了磁带。
Fucking froze up on us. It's weird.
在我们面前冻结住了。 真奇怪。
OK, that's good. We found one.
好的，那很好。 我们找到了一个。
Now we off on the last one,
which is at the greenhouse, right?
现在我们开始找最后一个，在温室里，对吧？
Human skin on these motherfuckers.
这些混蛋身上的人皮。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
So creepy.
好恐怖。
OK, I can't take these guys seriously.
好吧，我不能把这些家伙当回事。
They're doing the facial expression of,
you know, the to, like, whoa.
他们正在做面部表情，你知道，对着，像是，whoa。
Jack's, like, pointing behind them.
杰克的，就像，指着他们身后。
Yeah, look.
是的，看。
Yeah, yeah, I know exactly.
是的，是的，我很清楚。
What you're talking about.
你在说什么。
Like, oh, my God, it's this.
就像，哦，我的上帝，就是这个。
I don't know. I'm not at a tea party.
我不知道。 我应该不是在参加一个茶话会。
That's it.
这就对了。
The tape just cut out.
胶带刚刚剪下来。
We don't know who own the video,
我们不知道这是谁的录像。
OK, so I think that clown around cheese.
好的，所以我认为这些小丑围着的这些奶酪。
I think that's one ingredient
for the poison. That must be it.
我认为这是毒药的一种成分。 一定是这样的。
You found cheese?
你找到奶酪了吗？
What's.
什么是。
Yeah, I don't know.(Ike: Cheese vs.)
是的，我不知道。(Ike: 奶酪 vs)
It looks like really ugly cheese.
长得真是很丑的奶酪。
yeah OK, well, I guess that's an ingredient
for the poison.
好吧，好吧，我猜那是毒药的成分。
How about we go the other way?
我们走另一条路怎么样？
We go the other way.
They'll because there's another.
我们走另一条路。 他们会因为还有另一个。
It's off.
它走不通啊。
No, it was that cheese. It was.
I think that was it.
不，是那个奶酪。
That was a seal.
我原来想着那是一个印章。
Oh, that.
哦这个。
No, that was a seal? You dumb ass.
不，那个是一个印章。 你真是大聪明
Have you thought
that was a wheel of cheese?
你以为那是一个奶酪做的轮子吗？
Yeah. It is.Guys， guys Yes.
是的。 这是。 是的。
I heard them.
我听到了。
Always coming from this side. Right.
总是从这边过来。 对吗。
We go back. We go back where we came from.
我们回去。 我们回到我们来的地方。
Yeah. Yeah.
是的。 是的。
Vox:Run!Shoto:Follow me,follow me,um.
I think. I thought that was cheese.
快跑。跟上我。 我以为那是奶酪。
Vox:Reimu.
Shoto:I think we can go down this way.
我想我们可以这样下去。
Yeah, it looks like cheese.
是的，它看起来像奶酪。
And then it look at the objective. Said
it was like four out of five.
然后看看目标，那就像五分之四。
Wait.
等下。
You think it was? Yeah.
你以为那是？
Let me ask you something.
让我问你一件事。
Do you think it was cheese
or was a teemb.
你认为这是奶酪还是teemb。
Guys, guys, guys. Reimu:Cheese.
伙计们，伙计们，伙计们。 Reimu:奶酪啊。
I need to run out.
我需要跑出这个地方。
this place. It's coming.
鬼要跟过来了。
Oh, my God. He's going.
我的天啊。 他要去。
To shine the light shine the light shine.
要发光，要发光，要发光。
Right.
对。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Hold on, guys, guys,
等等，伙计们，伙计们，
I shit.
卧槽。
I had to run. I had to run.
我不得不跑。 我不得不跑。
I think I found it
我想我找到了
oh, this is just.
哦，这只是。
It's just the fucking trees again.
又是那该死的树。
All my friends are dying.
我所有的朋友都快死了。
我所有的朋友都快死光了。
Oh, I thought I could slip faster.
哦，我以为我可以滑得更快啊。
Fuck, no, dude.
操，不，伙计。
I thought we could just.
我以为我们可以。
Slip faster after, like,
flashing her with the lights on. It's
滑得更快，比如开着灯闪她。 它是
and on.
等等。
Oh, my gosh.
天啊。
I tried to flash her
than, like, slide by by.
我试图拿灯闪她而不是像滑过她一样。
Couldn't do that.
没能成功。
Yeah, I got jumped by the big dude,
and I don't think that there's.
是的，我被那个大家伙吓到了，我不认为有。
Others die from.
其他人死于。
Yeah, everyone died. Hey,
that's good, though.
是的，所有人都死了。 嘿，不过，这很好。
I don't think you can stop him.
我不认为你可以阻止他。
We did find something new.
We found a table we.
我们确实发现了一些新东西。 我们找到了一张桌子。
We did find a table with a rib cage on it.
我们确实找到了一张上面有肋骨的桌子。
A rib cage.
一个肋骨。
Where? Yeah. Huh.
在哪里？ 是的。 嗯。
I think we need.
我想我们需要一个。
Vox, are you OK?Vox are u Good. Yes.
大丈夫？ Nice.
你还好吗，Vox？ Vox你还好吗，没事不。 Vox:是的我没事。Nice。
I'm always 大丈夫.Shoto:bruuuuh.
我一直没事。
I yawned and I almost like I yawned really
hard, and I almost went like.
我打了个哈欠，我几乎像打哈欠一样用力，我几乎像过去一样。
Oh, oh. Oh.
（猴叫）
Oh, oh, I like that.
哦，哦，我喜欢这样。
And I miss that noise I do.
我想念我发出得这种怪叫了
Oh.
哦。
The cheese.
奶酪。
You got to go over them now. We only got.(Reimu:Remember me~)
你现在必须越过它们。 我们只有得到。
One to break from the Ads.
我现在可以看广告休息一下。
Acuérdate de mí
Shoto:请记住我（西语）
They want a break.
他们想要从..哦。
From the... Oh.
Oh
哦。
My God.Vox.
我的上帝。Vox.
Was like your grunts very aggressive.
你的咕噜声非常具有攻击性。
That's right. That's right.
没错。 没错。
Just watch a short
ad and get 30 seconds of ad-free [growl].
只需观看一个简短的广告，即可获得 30 秒的无广告猴叫声。
Right.
对。
Considered to be sold.
考虑全部卖掉。
It sound like a dog with my.
这听起来好像狗啊
Cuz my favourite sound effect is the one
which is like wooh to break from the ads.
因为我最喜欢的音效是像一样从广告中蹦出来的wooh那种音效。
One of my favourite things.
我的广告最爱之一。
is as like a clip.
许多剪辑。
It's a video I called Pan talked before
and it's just like a pair of hands
这是我之前叫潘聊过的一段视频，就像一双手飞向镜头，
flying towards the camera
and then it fades to white with the.
然后随着镜头逐渐变白。
Weird sound effect.
奇怪的音效。
But you cheese here.
但你在这里奶酪。
Put it in and put the cheese.
把它放进去，把奶酪放进去。
I got one.
我得到了一个。
Yeah, but the cheese.
是的，但是奶酪。
And it looks like a cheese. Yeah.
它看起来像奶酪。 是的。
I mean. She's.
我是说。
A cheese. Do you.
一块奶酪。 你。
What kind of fucking cheese.
什么他妈的种类的奶酪。
Hold on. Fucking cheese.
坚持，稍等。 该死的奶酪。
Cheese. Cheese, cheese, cheese.
奶酪，奶酪，奶酪。
I'm kind of concern now.
我现在有点担心。
cheese.cheese.
奶酪。
Fucking cheese.
该死的奶酪。
Next week we'll be looking at egg.
下周我们将研究鸡蛋。
Thanks, yeah.
谢谢哦，是的。
I know exactly what he's referencing.
我确切地知道他在说什么梗。
Is there another European thing?
Cuz I don't know.
还有其他欧洲的东西吗？ 因为我不知道。
No, I mean.
不，我是说。
You know.
你知道。
Technically, I guess.
从技术上讲，我猜。
OK, just James, maybe oh.
好的，只有詹姆斯，也许哦。
My God.
我的上帝。
We need to find the greens with the sweet.
我们需要找到有甜味的蔬菜。
All right, go to the greenhouse house.
好吧，去温室。
I will.
我会。
I will be the ah... Ike:Where’s the green house?
我将成为。Ike:温室在哪里？
I've never even seen it.
You never seen the green house?
我甚至从未见过它。 你没见过绿房子吗？
Haven't I?
我不是吗？
Oh. Has gone there. Before. Yeah, I don't.
哦。 之前已经去了那里。 是的，我没有。
I don't remember.
我不记得。
OK, we went down this way like the one.
好的，我们在所有干草的领域。
In the field with all the dry grass.
像以前一样走这条路。
No, no, no. That's where I got the seal.
不不不。 那是我得到印章的地方。
And you are walking over the trees.
I know.
而你正在穿过树林行走。 我知道。
Yeah.
是的。
The first time I got to the greenhouse
我第一次到温室的时候，就像，每个人都分开了，超级他妈的害怕。
was when, like, everybody separated
and got super fucking scared.
It was like
I was trying to look for Ike, and then.
就像我试图寻找艾克，然后。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Oh, you were with me,
and then you disappeared.
哦，你和我在一起，然后你就消失了。
And then I just saw a player
that I was like, oh.
我只是看到一个玩家然后我就像，哦。
Wait a second down here. Oh,
在这里等一下。 哦，
One of the few places where I'm.
我所在的少数几个地方之一。
Like, breathing.
呼吸。
Trying to communicate.
试图沟通。
Yeah, I remember
I was falling asleep, all gone.
是的，我记得我睡着了，一切都过去了。
All right.
好的。
I remember I was following Ike's thing
because I was like, oh, shit.
我记得我在跟着艾克，因为我就像，哦，卧槽。
I see his his lights on.
我看到他的灯亮着。
We follow it,
and then I think I split off here.
我们跟着它，然后我想我在这里跟你分开了。
No, not here. We hear
不，不在这里。 我们听到
because, like, I didn't
因为，就像，我最终没有在某个时候跟好那个光。
end up following the lights at some point.
Folks.
伙计们。
Sorry. Sorry.
对不起。 对不起。
I think
我认为
OK, now I don't know where to go.
好的，现在我不知道该去哪里。
I'm going to lose my glowstick.
我会失去我的荧光棒。
Big chunk. This is very close.
大块。 这非常接近。
Yeah.
是的。
This is a big boy.
这是一个大家伙。
Big, big I.
大，大。
Hate this game.
我讨厌这个游戏。
We I can't even get in.
我们连进去都进不去。
This is playground.
这是游乐场。
It's wall place again.
又是墙的地方。
Where do we go from here?
我们从这里去哪里？
Because we found your places.
因为我们找到了你说的地方。
Follow me follow me. Follow me.
对于我们的跟随我跟随我。 跟我来。
I think I saw another area.
I'm not sure it's a dead end.
我想我看到了另一个区域,
I'm not sure if it's a dead end or not.
我不确定这是否是死胡同。
This monster's over there.
这个怪物在那边。
look at the big guys.
或者大怪物。
Like he's
on. He's on the other side of the trees.
就像他在。 他在树的另一边。
It's OK. It's ok.
没关系。 没关系。
Oh, this is a dead end.
A fuck. Oh, lovely.
哦，这是一个死胡同，卧槽。 哦，很好很好。
Oh, we need to go to the big guy,
then mm hmm.
哦，我们需要去找那个大家伙，然后嗯嗯。
Or? He's gonna kill You.
或者?然后他会杀掉你。
Oh, Kon ni chi wa.
哦你好呀。
Hiding the master.
I'm not. You need to run.
我不是你。 你需要跑。
We just gotta the fuck, right?
我们现在就是要开始跑路，对吧？
Yeah. Yeah, I guess. I guess so.
是的。 是的，我猜。 大概吧。
Yeah, down here.
是的，在这里。
He's been.
他刚刚在.
Down here.
下来这里。
My God, this game is hard.
我的天，这游戏好难。
I wish we had, like, a map.
He was. Really there.
我希望我们有一个地图。 他是。 真的在那里。
Ow, ow.
呜呜呜
Ow. Ow, ow, ow, ow.
哦。 呜呜呜呜呜呜
Well, what is this is? this, like, baptism?
嗯，这啥玩意？洗礼吗？
What that tells me, Daddy?
这告诉我什么，爸爸？
I mean, the.
我的意思是，。
Opposite of what whoa.
对面什么哇。
Waffle.
胡扯。
Daddy.
爸爸。
Father. Excuse me.
父亲。 打扰一下。
Excuse me. It's baptised me father.
打扰一下。 它为我施洗，父亲。
I said father.
我叫了父亲。
So I'll check the vod, guys.
所以我会检查录屏的，伙计们。
We all heard what she said.
我们都听到了她的话。
Forgive me, Daddy, for I have sinned.
原谅我，爸爸，因为我犯了罪。
Oh, you are a bitch.
哦，你是大坏蛋！
Vox akuma you fucking bitch.
Vox akuma 你他妈的。
I really hope
this is the way I see my girls.
我真的希望这是我看待我的女孩的方式。
Yooh, let's go. Let's go.
耶我们走吧。 我们走吧。
We found it.
我们找到了。
Yeah. Ok.
是的。 行。
We like some sort of acid.
我们喜欢某种酸。
There's, like, a body inside.
就像，里面有一具尸体。
We shit. Yeah.
卧槽。
Now we got to, like, make the make
the pesticide solution somehow.
现在我们必须以某种方式制造杀虫剂溶液。
Yeah, it's on the other side.
是的，它在另一边。
There's a there's a chemistry table,
有一个化学表，然后你必须按照说明将这些东西混合在一起。
and then you have to follow the
instructions and mix the shit together.
OK. Ok, let me see
好的。 好的，让我看看
sam behind.
We have to come on. Pesticides
just make my own.
我们必须加油。 药剂只是我自己做的。
The fuck is this?
这他妈是？
I feel chemistry twice. Yes,
我感觉化学了两次。 是的，
I see.
我懂了。
Oh. Yeah.
哦。 是的。
I took.
我拿了。
I took AP Chem, and I don't even remember
any of this shit.
我拿了AP化学品，我甚至不记得这东西了。
It's a blur.
好模糊。
I, like, threw it out my head.
我，就像，化学知识从我的脑海里当作垃圾倒掉了。
It was over.
结束了。
Canvas and jet.
帆布和喷气机。
Yeah.
是的。
Any chemists and jet？
有化学课代表吗？
guys?
伙计们？
How do we how do we how do we make liquid?
我们如何制造液体？
What is cb
什么是cb
CI we had these yellow and green dye
CI我们有这些黄色和绿色染料，你只需用另一瓶扔掉它。
and you just drop it with another bottle.
It just kind of reminds you like.
它只是提醒你。
CBT. Like resident evil.
CBT。 就像恶灵古堡一样。
Hey, know, key yogi.
嘿，知道，关键的瑜伽士。
If this game was
if this game was forgiving
如果这个游戏是如果这个游戏是宽容的，我们可以像这样跳过天花板。
we could just hop through the ceiling
like this.
If it honestly, I feel like I would
I would rather just do that.
老实说，我觉得我宁愿这样做。
Just jump up and no, we have like is zero
athletic abilities apparently.
只是跳起来，不，我们的运动能力显然是零。
have to move the h-7 from red to yellow
need a bottle from another can
需要将h7从红色变成黄色，还另一个罐子里的一瓶药水
so we need to find bottles.
所以我们需要找到瓶子。
Oh let's divide colour bottles.
哦，让我们分开颜色瓶。
We have to find more
we have to find more shit.
我们必须找到更多，我们必须找到更多的东西。
Yeah of course
we need to find the chemical anatomy.
是的，我们当然需要找到化学解剖结构。
Hide, hide, hide company.
躲起来躲起来。
Come with me. Hide, hide, hide.
跟我来。 躲起来躲起来。
Shhshh. No, he see ,he see some
嘘，嘘。哦他看见了。
He saw us. Oh my God.That's bullshit.
他看见我们了。 我的天啊。荒谬。
It's all in my purse.
意料之中。
I heard his little aohh.
我听到了他的嗷嗷叫声。
reimu reimu reimu
Oh, I think he's gone.
哦，我想他已经走了。
He's gone. Yeah.
他已经去了。 是的。
I think the trick is just say Ryan
and then just let one die.
我认为诀窍就是说瑞恩，然后就让一个人送死。
When we know the different coloured
bottles are right here.
当我们知道不同颜色的瓶子就在这里时。
These are the bottles contain.
这些是装着...的瓶子。
It's all in Green shaking occasionally so far,.
它全是绿色的.偶尔还会颤抖。
is that a mixture of evaporation.a mixture of evaporates.
这是一个挥发物的混合物吗。 挥发物混合物？
that mean you do. It
evaporates, it becomes gas.
你意思是它会蒸发，变成气体。
You know what evaporate means? Yes,
I know what it means.
你知道蒸发意味着啥吗？ 是的，我知道这意味着什么。
Do you know what. Then why you are asking?
你知道一些。那你为啥还要问
You know what sublimation means.
你知道升华啥意思吗？
Oh, wait.
等一下。
We don't need to find anything.
我们不需要找到任何东西。
All the ingredients
are right in front of us.
所有的成分都在我们面前。
That's what.
那是我们一直在说的。
we've been saying.
What the hell.
我勒个去。
I ain't notice it basically here this.
我没有注意到它在这个地方。
Stuff.
东西。
The volume bottles are literally right in
front of us.
容量瓶就在我们面前。
And I need to swap it with another bottle.
我需要把它换成另一瓶。
Yeah, coverage nine from red, yellow.
是的，覆盖九个红色，黄色。
I don't.
我不。
One person that's not here, dude.
一个不在这里的人，伙计。
All the solutions keep evaporating
所有的解决方案都在不断蒸发
this blood.
这血。
C, c b breaking down in all.
C、c b 全部分解。
But is it separate this a lot?
但是，它分开了很多吗？
I think I need to, like, write them
all down in, like, a big notepad.
我想我需要，比如，把它们都写下来，比如，一个大记事本。
So I don't forget.
所以这样我不会忘记。
I can't believe.
我不信
Oh, I love cock and ball torture.
哦，我喜欢鸡巴和球的折磨。
Where is this? You stay here.
这是哪里？ 你留在这里。
Oh, shit. Run.
妈的。 跑。
I've got a solution.
我有一个解决方案。
This lady. Oh, no, I don't. Come here.
Come here.
这位是女士。 哦，不，我没有。 过来。 过来。
I don't think. Lady screams
when you see us. We can hide.
我不这样认为。 当你看到我们时，女士会尖叫。 我们可以躲起来。
Little lady is going to.
She sees us. There's no way to.
小姑娘要来了。 她看到了我们。 没有退路。
we get.
我们
Shine the light.
拿光闪她
Shine the light shine.
闪她
OK, OK.
好的好的。
Damn, I've been worried.
靠，我一直很担心。
I think
我认为
damn.
该死。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
He caught me.
他抓住了我。
I can't hide from her. No.
我不能躲着她。 不。
Damn it.
该死的，是我死了。
Oh. Ha ha ha ha.
哦。 哈哈哈哈。
God damn it, man.
该死的，伙计。
All three people died.
三个人都死在她手上。
What happened to Iky .
Ike咋样了。
That? Like, fuck.
那？ 就像，他妈的。
Do we solve any of this?
我们能解决这些问题吗？
How the fuck do we do that chemical thing?
我们他妈怎么做那种化学的任务？
I don't know that that makes any sense.
我不知道这有什么意义。
Everything else has made complete sense.
That one just doesn't.
其他一切都完全有意义。 那个没有。
Think it's a crime.
I should speak with that manager.
认为这是犯罪。 我应该和那个经理谈谈。
You don't say. All you want to.
可不是嘛。 所有你想要的。
All you want to sell them
like we asked for.
您想按照我们的要求出售它们。
No pickles.
没有泡菜。
Excuse me?
打扰一下？
Shoto ask for no pickles.
Shoto说不要泡菜。
You are.
你是。
Are you the type of person to just tell
them, like, hey, I don't want pickles?
你是那种只会告诉他们，嘿，我不想要泡菜的人吗？
Or, like, you know, you order it, but then
you take it off after you've ordered it.
或者，您知道，您订购了它，但在订购后将其取下。
Yeah, it depends. I mean.
是的，这取决于。 我是说。
I mean, if I'm in, like, a restaurant,
then I'll just be like, oh,
我的意思是，如果我在餐厅，那么我会说，哦，是的，我真的很喜欢这个。
yeah, I'd really like this.
Oh, fuck, can I have this instead of that?
哦，操，我可以用这个代替那个吗？
And in a restaurant, because it takes so
long to prepare the food, then they don't.
在餐馆里，因为准备食物需要很长时间，所以他们不会。
They usually it's like, not, it's like,
really not, not a problem for them.
他们通常就像，不是，就像，真的不是，对他们来说不是问题。
Whereas in, like, fast food,
I will just be.
而在，比如，快餐，我只是。
I'll just take it off.
我会把它取下来。
Yeah.
是的。
I just take it off as a matter. I don't.
我只是把它作为一个问题。 我不。
I really don't like pickles.
我真的不喜欢泡菜。
Oh, you don't like pickles?
哦，你不喜欢泡菜吗？
Nah, you'll like like pickled, like,
不喜欢。你会喜欢，那种腌制的或者没咋腌的辣椒那种
not even pickled
like jalapenos or like. No.
不喜欢。
Like pickled radish. Pickles just loose.
比如腌萝卜。 泡菜就是不喜欢。
I just don't like pickle.
我只是不喜欢泡菜。
Just the. Texture.
只是。 质地。
Dichotomy. Mostly the texture of a pickle.
主要是泡菜的质地。
Like when I bite into it, you're
not expecting it to be there in a burger.
就像我咬它的时候，你没想到它会出现在汉堡里。
It's like, look.
就像，看。
Have you
ever had, like, other pickled stuff
你有没有吃过其他腌制的东西，你知道，黄瓜，像萝卜或泡菜？
that's not like, you know, the cucumbers,
like, daikon radish or like kimchi?
I don't know
我不知道
what kind of pickle.
什么样的泡菜。
I think
我认为
wait Reimu has died
等下Reimu死了吗
oh Reimu didn't Die.
哦她没有死。
And she's still communicating.
而她还在交流。
All right.
好的。
My favourite thing about the voice chat in
我最喜欢这款游戏中的语音聊天的一点是，
this game is the fact that you can hear it
just cut through.
你可以听到它将要切进来的那一点点声音。
Yeah, we hear them like ba a pa a.
是的，我们听到他们就像。啪 啊 啪 啊
What's the fuck is this, bro?
这是什么鬼，兄弟？
What is. This?
什么是。 这？
Wait, what the fuck is this?
等等，这是什么鬼？
What is this?
这是什么？
I've never seen this part before.
我以前从未见过这部分。
Apparently it's already solved
because like, I think they got it via
显然它已经解决了，因为我认为他们是通过
already, but.
已经，但是。
Oh. Interesting.
哦。 有趣的。
It was another.
这是另一个。
in the cage.
在笼子里。
Nah. That
不。 离我很近，或者只是有点幻想得到我。
close behind me or just kind of
just kind of fantasise about getting me.
I'm like getting back by about having
my back against the wall for one second.
我就像背靠在墙上一秒钟就回来了。
We're both in the cage now.
我俩现在都在笼子里。
Oh shit. We're both in the cage now.
妈的。我俩现在都在笼子里。
Are we going to do.
What are we going to do?
我们要不要做。 我们会做什么？
But they're not here.
They're not listening. They don't know
但他们不在这里。 他们不听。 他们不知道
they're not.
他们不是。
We're in the cage.
我们在笼子里。
They don't know and all the time
the monsters aren't even here either.
他们不知道，怪物也一直不在这里。
The moon's high in the sky at all time.
月亮一直高高挂在天上。
All the time in the world.
世界上所有的时间。
Yeah, yeah.
是啊是啊。
No rush, right?
不急，对吧？
Yeah, yeah.
是啊是啊。
We're never going
我们永远不会去
to leave.
离开。
That's just the gentle swaying of a cage
upon the branches of a tree.
那只是笼子在树枝上轻轻摇晃。
But the way you articulate things, it's
very sexy.
但是你表达事物的方式非常性感。
You know, like the gentle
swinging of the trees and the
你知道，就像树木轻轻的摇摆和
land and buzzing on high
着陆并在高处嗡嗡作响
wealth of branches dangling
through the the bars of the cage.
大量的树枝在笼子的栅栏上晃来晃去。
And your beard is like brushing
against my head.
而你的胡须就像刷过我的头。
Brush brush.
刷——刷——
It's like I'm getting, like, you know,
就像我得到了，就像，你知道的，那些头部按摩器，像那些奇怪的长的。
those those head massagers, like,
those weird long ones.
You just, like,
go in and out of your head. No.
你只是，就像，进进出出你的脑袋。 不。
Oh, yeah. It's like a spider. Like.
哦耶。 这就像一个蜘蛛。
When you use them on a cat
in the Catholic.
当你在猫猫头上使用过它们吗。
You've used on a cat before.
你以前在猫身上用过。
Yeah, you can.
是的，你可以。
Yeah,
that's what I thought I was talking about.
是的，这就是我以为我在谈论的是。
Like this note
like the sort of the metal prong thingy
就像这张纸条，就像金属叉子一样，当你把它推到某人的头上时，它就会散开。
that when you push it on someone's
head, it kind of spreads out.
OK Anyway, stick your pants off
无论如何，把你的裤子脱了。（光速开车）
Jesus.All right.
天啊。但是好的。
Ha ha ha ha ha.
哈哈哈哈哈。
You're. Like, flabbergasted for a long second there.
你就像，大吃一惊并且愣住了好几秒。
I was really talking, like,
I was expecting it earlier.
我真的在说，就像，我早些时候就在期待你说这种话。
And then we got into this cat massage
discussion, and I was really aggressive.
但然后我们进入了这个用灵魂提取器给猫按摩的讨论
我当时真的很激进。
Oh, hey, this is the rib cage
that they're talking about it.
哦，嘿，这是他们正在谈论的肋骨。
Is that a pun?
这是双关语吗？
Oh, it's a rib cage.
哦，那是一个笼子里面的肋骨。
Inside a cage.
You know, that's pretty clever.
你知道，这很聪明。
I see. I see. That's a felony. Yeah.
我懂了。 我懂了。 那是重罪。 是的。
You got to take credit for those.
Very good. Very good.
你必须承认这些功劳。 很好。 很好。
Months and months.
几个月和几个月。
Not something I associate with you
on the best of days.
不是我在最好的日子里与你联系的东西。
Well, come on, bro. We like have you.
好吧，来吧，兄弟。 我们好像，你有过，呃
We played through the entirety
of it takes two together.
我们玩遍了双人成行的全部关卡。
The other, it takes of, like,
a considerable amount of grey matter.
另一个，它需要大量的一种东西。
Yeah. You know, chief, such a feel.
是的。 你知道，领导能力，这种感觉。
Like you did have me. You did have me.
你有我。 你确实有我带着你。
What the fuck it was?
那是什么鬼？
It was a dual effort.
这是双重努力。
I mean, you had to.
我的意思是，你必须这样做。
It was like. Yeah, it's like saying. Well.
这就像是。 是的，就像在说。 好。
I mean, yeah, it's like saying.
You're the one.
我的意思是，是的，就像在说。
The only ones in the entirety of the show
probably.
好像都是你一个人在整场直播当中发挥作用一样。
Isn't allowed to do, but, you know,
不允许这样做，但是，你知道，
all they got the chains.
他们都得到了锁链。
All they were back here.
他们都回到了这里。
Back here with arse neighbourhood.
回到了屁屁基地。
Yeah.
是的。
They're facing their arses
towards each other.
他们正用屁屁对着对方。
You give them.
你给他们。
Both bottles because they're facing
their arses towards each other.
两个受，因为他们正用他们的屁屁对着对方。
I might be right.
我可能是对的。
And the how that works.
但是我不知道那样咋能做起来呢。
I don't know
我不知道
I don't know.
我不知道。
The back of your shirts'
你衬衫的背面
a staff
是一名工作人员
and a staff.
你是不是一名工作人员。
Are you?
you got to check in my pants for that.
那你需要检查一下我的裤子。
Oh, it's impressive.
哦，令人印象深刻。
I seems kind of flaccid right now.
我现在似乎有点松懈。
I think so.
我认同。
kinda flaccid.
有点飘飘的。
Is probably cause I'm around you.
可能是因为我在你身边。(好甜救命)
Ah. You are your bitch. OK, goodbye Vox.
你是混蛋。 好，再见,vox。
Welcome back.
欢迎回来。
Fuck you. What the hell?
去你的。 我勒个去？
Get back here. Hello?
回到这里。 你在吗?
you little bitch.
你这个小婊砸。
I see you.
我看见你了。
You all right?
你没事吧？
Oh, you finally decided to come
crawling back?
哦，你终于决定爬回来了？
No, I decided. To come crawling back.
不，我决定了。 爬回来。
I just don't want to be alone.
我只是不想一个人。
Oh, poor little Shoto.
哦，好可怜的Shoto呀。
You should shut the fuck up, Vox.
你他马闭嘴，Vox。
I just don't wanna be alone. All.
我只是不想成为一个人。
That fucking thing.
那该死的东西。
Don't look at me, dudes.
别看我，伙计们。
I'll look around you lot of people.
我会看看你周围很多人。
Oh, well, that was a close one.
哦，好吧，那是一个接近的鬼。
Yeah, I would have been really bad,
especially after I said, Oh,
是的，我可能会很糟糕，尤其是在我说，哦，
I think they figure it out. You did it. Yeah,
they figured it out.
我认为他们做到了。 是的，他们解决了。
I think they did it while I was trying
get back to the main place.
我想他们是在我试图回到主要地点。
Yeah, that's.
是的，就是这样。
Well, we decided to just fuck around
inside a cage for, like, 10 minutes.
好吧，我们大概在笼子里乱搞了10分钟。
They solve the puzzle
I guess we have our own little story.
他们解决了谜题， 我们有我们自己的(调情)小故事。
OK? OK. Yeah,
好的？ 好的。 是的，
it's like in the until dawn.
就像在直到黎明。
There were plans.
有计划。
Although I did. Yeah, I've played.
虽然我做到了。 是的，我玩过。
I mean,
I don't think I've played it myself.
我的意思是，我不认为我自己玩过。
I think I watched somebody play it, like,
three years ago.
我想我看过有人玩它，就像三年前一样。
This is the right way.
这是正确的方法。
I think it is. Yeah, it's familiar.
我认为是这样。 是的，很熟悉。
All this, I think, is the way back to the.
这一切，我想，都是回归的路。
Scenes from me.
我的场景。
OK, Morgan Freeman
好的
to the thing again.
再说一遍。
I do believe
we've gone the wrong way, my boy.
我相信我们走错了路，我的孩子。
Yeah, I think there's probably not
the Morgan Freeman.
是的，我认为可能没有。
Oh, I found it.
哦，我找到了。
What's that one out of 75 young men
75个年轻人中的那个是什么人
down this way, wait.
从这往下走吧？ 等等。
Haven't we already been down this way?
我们不是已经这样下去了吗？
We just come down here.
我们刚下来。
One out of two young men is a bottom.
两个年轻人中就有一个是受。
I'm Morgan Freeman.
我是摩根弗里曼。
One out of 2.
2个中的一个?
Hello, hello. Hello.
你好你好。 你好。
All good thing neither of us are that one.
好事是我们都不是那个。
out of two, right?
二分之一的受，对吧？
We're like a statistical anomaly
我们就像一个统计异常案例。
or like an alley. Yes
像一条小巷。 是的。
it's like that fucking thing
我们的情况就像三个人中间有一个是受。
of, like, you know, about one in three
people are a bottom.
And we look at chat.
我们看看chat咋说。
We look at them either,
and they just stare.
我们也看着他们，他们只是盯着看。
We just look at the screen. Yeah.
我们只看屏幕。 是的。
And the in this case,
I just you to look at them.
在这种情况下，我只是让你看看他们。
Mm hmm. You know,
one out of two people are bottoms.
嗯嗯。 你知道，两个人中有一个是受。
I'm not a bottom.
我不是受。（疯狂暗示）
I'm not a bottom either.
我也不是受啊。（强装一下）
No, no, just don't look anywhere.
不，不，只是不要看任何地方。
One in two. Mmhum
Vox:二分之一的概率哎。Shoto: 嗯哼？
I couldn't even see your face.
我甚至看不到你的脸。
It was, like,
obscured by the fucking shot.
就像被那该死的枪声遮住了一样。
No, no, the joke's ruined. Fuck
不，不，笑话被你毁掉了。 他妈的。
and we're actually the lost boys.
我们实际上是迷路的男孩。
Well.
好。
This is back at the.
这又回到了。
No, this is the.
不，这是。
This is just one point. Yeah, what's.
这只是一点。 是的，什么。
I'll cabin in the woods.
我会住在树林里。
Oh, my goodness.
哦，我的天啊。
I'm going.
我要去。
So I'm going to I, you know, I feel like
所以我要去我，你知道，我现在感觉就像撕掉一只烤鸡。
like just ripping out a rotisserie chicken
right now.
I'm just, like, eating it with my bare
hands.
我只是，就像，赤手空拳地吃它。
I like you being.
我喜欢你就像。
Like, the dude on that Australian
news thing where he's like,
就像，那个澳大利亚新闻里的那个家伙，是的，你知道，那个生物刚出来就像，
yeah, you know, that creature
just kind of came out was like,
you know, can you eat it like that?
你知道，你能这样吃吗？
I wish I could.
我希望我能够。
Mr. Fox, you know, where he just sits down
to kind of fold his newspaper.
福克斯先生，你知道，他只是坐下来折报纸。
He's all dressed, all smart.
他衣冠楚楚，聪明伶俐。
It's like, Darling,
this dinner looks fantastic.
就像，亲爱的，这顿晚餐看起来棒极了。
And he just looks at he goes, Well,
他只是看着然后变得，嗯，
has to, to shreds like that,
不得不，像一只真正的狐狸一样撕碎，然后他就有点喜欢。
like an actual fox and goes,
and then he just kind of like.
Mops his mouth.
擦他的嘴。
Oh, oh, nah, nah.
噢噢噢噢噢噢。不。
Our friends just died oh no
我们的朋友刚刚死了。
Hermione. Ron
赫敏。 罗恩.（指Ike和Reimu）
Is this the right way?
这走的对吗？
All this does
this do look like the bloody right way.
所有这一切看起来确实是该死的正确方向。
Oh, my goodness. Holy shit.
哦，我的天啊。 天啊。
Harry, oh pog.I did it.I did it.
Did they call me the Harry Potter?
他们刚刚叫我哈利波特吗？
Wait. Did you find Ike?
等待。 你找到艾克了吗？
Do you know where Ike was?
你知道Ike在哪里吗？
I think Ike died.
我想ike死了。
I was with me, and then we got separated.
我和我在一起，然后我们就分开了。
And then I opened this, and then.
然后我打开了这个，然后。
Bomb.
bang
I was with Vox.
我跟Vox在一起。
Like. We.
像。 我们。
I just found Vox, like,not too long ago.yeah umhum.
我不久以前才找到Vox，嗯哼（明明没有离开过他好咩）
Yeah, he just got.
是的，他刚刚才。
So I guess I was the one that died. Yeah.
所以我想我是那个死去的人。 是的。
I think he'll be back soon.
我想他很快就会回来。
We chill here.
我们在这里放松。
Waiting for the boys.Yeah we can wait here. Ike?
我们可以在这里等。Ike?
Ike. I think I see him coming.
Ike 我想我看到他来了。
Oh, yeah, that is him. OK.
哦，对了，就是他。 好的。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
Oh, I'm so.
哦，我就是这样。
I looked away for a split second,
and you vanish.
我看了一会儿，你消失了。
Things like that.
像这样的东西。
So I guess I have the blessed child
of this game who aren't you.
所以我想我有这个游戏的幸运之子，但不是你。
A blessed child?
一个有福的孩子？
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
耶耶耶。
Thank God for our
感谢上帝为我们
and God for our ghost.
上帝为我们驱除鬼魂。
What is that achievement?
那是什么成就？
What was.
什么是。
What treatment?
什么治疗？
Did you. Get one? Is it green?
你是否。 得到一个？ 是绿色的吗？
50 shades of green.
50 度绿吗。
It's 50 Shades of Grey,
but it's starring Shrek.
它是《五十度灰》，但由怪物史莱克（绿色的怪物）主演。
Oh, boy.
好家伙。
I mean, are you doing in my vox shorts?
我的意思是，你穿着我的平角短裤吗？
Yeah, I are.
是的，我是。
We got
I don't know, it looks like a swamp.
我们得到了我不知道，它看起来像一个沼泽。
We might actually be on to a swamp.
我们实际上可能是在沼泽上。
I love Shrek. I love Shrek. So much.
我爱怪物史莱克。非常喜欢。
I had all of the DVDs. Oh.
我有所有的 DVD。 哦。
I see.
我懂了。
Oh, there's another house.
哦，还有一个房子。
Hello. Salem is a safe house.
你好。 塞勒姆是一个安全的房子。
It's another thing.
这是另一回事。
Checkpoint. Did we finish the chapter?
存档点，我们完成这一节了吗？
Stick symbols
whispering to me on the phone.
贴在电话里对我耳语的符号。
Oh, my God, my poor head.
哦，我的上帝，我可怜的脑袋。
When I grabbed it, disintegrated
in my hands.
当我抓住它时，它在我手中解体了。
Oh. I have a question.
哦。 我有个问题。
How did you guys solve the puzzle?
你们是怎么解开这个谜题的？
How do you solve the pesticide puzzle?
你如何解决农药难题？
I wrote each puzzle down,
and then I figure with the
我把每一个谜题都写下来，然后我用每一个笔记来计算，
with each note, we're like,
which chemist and which chemist?
我们就像，哪个化学成分和哪个化学成分一起？
Which solution was in which.
哪个溶液放在哪个里。
You pulled out your notes for this?
你拿出你的笔记本，就为了这个？
Oh, my God, you're insane.
哦，我的上帝，你疯了。
Yeah. Dude, I'm so proud of you.
是的。 伙计，我为你感到骄傲。
I'm so proud of you.
我很为你感到骄傲。
All this was a job.
这一切都是一份工作。
My phone.
我的手机。
I thought I was alone for
当我在篝火旁热身时，我以为只有我一个人，但那东西，它只是忽略了我。
when I was warming up near the bonfire,
but that thing, it just ignored me.
Like I wasn't even there.
就像我甚至不在那里一样。
Guys, guys, guys, gather up, gather tape.
伙计们，伙计们，伙计们，聚集起来，收集磁带。
If you're reading
如果您正在阅读本文，请待在火源附近或室内。
this, stay near fire or indoors.
Oh. Stay near fire indoors.
哦。 在室内靠近火源。
OK. OK.
好的。 好的。
Noted
注意了。
guy died
because another guy set in his face
一个人死了，因为另一个人站在他的脸上
sitting on face down yeah.
脸朝下坐着是的。
When I was working up near the bonfire,
I stay near fire or indoors.
当我在篝火附近工作时，我会待在火源附近或室内。
OK, that's. Why.
好的，就是这样。 为什么。
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
对不起。 对不起。
Oh, this is Dr. Franklin.
哦，这是富兰克林博士。
I'm Sergeant with the Hapsburg
Illinois Police Force.
我是哈布斯堡伊利诺伊州警察部队的中士。
At least they have a shifter
and coming me.
至少他们有一个变速杆来找我。
What time?
几点了？
What about you?
那你呢？
Willing to bet that there's the plumbing.
我愿意打赌那里有管道。
Leaks that are somewhere, right?
泄漏在某个地方，对吗？
Busting all bitches.
破坏所有的婊子。
No bitches.
没有婊子。
Nobody's and don't be near bitches
没有人，也不要靠近母狗。
and you'll be OK.
你会没事的。
What do you what do you guys want to do?
你们到底想做什么？
I think.
我认为。
Do you want to you want to solve this one
你想你想解决这个问题，然后在我们解决这个问题后打电话给晚上吗？
and then call the night
after we solve this one?
Am I the only
one like, OK, so if you look at the grass
只有我一个人，好吧，如果你看看这里的草图形和所有的树，
graphics and all the trees here, doesn't
this look like slender, the eight pages?
这八页看起来是不是很纤细？
Oh, my. Oh,
my God. You're right. The tree.
天啊。 我的天啊。 你说的对。 那个树。
Holy shit. You're right.
天啊。 你说的对。
What a classic. Oh, my God.
多么经典。 我的天啊。
Did you just give me a nostalgia?
你只是给我留恋吗？
Footsteps even sound similar.
脚步声甚至听起来很相似。
All we need is the ambience,
like the boom, boom.
我们需要的只是氛围，就像炸弹一样。
Boom, boom, boom, boom.
轰，轰，轰，轰。
Boom.
轰
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Where are we going?
我们去哪？
I wish I was talking my friends around.
我希望我是在谈论我周围的朋友。
My favourite guy, you know, Slender Man.
我最喜欢的人，你知道的，Slender Man。
Would you fuck Slenderman?
你会操Slenderman吗？
Yes. Tentacles.
是的。 触手。
What is that kind of question?
什么样的问题？
I mean, he has. He has, he has.
我的意思是，他有。 他有，他有。
He does have tentacles.
他确实有触手。
I know that's.
That's a pretty Bay State to be honest.
我知道那是。 老实说，这是一个漂亮的海湾州。
Yeah, he has multiple angles.
是的，他有多个角度。
Oh, can we just jump over?
哦，我们可以跳过吗？
All we know, there's a gate here.
我们都知道，这里有一扇门。
There was an entrance, right?
有一个入口，对吧？
I thought I figured something
revolutionary.
我想我想出了一些革命性的东西。
This where we came from.
这是我们来的地方。
Yeah. This is he from. Oh, yeah.
是的。 这是他从。 哦耶。
We went around in circles.
我们转了一圈。
Oops.
哎呀。
Jesus.
耶稣。
Oops.
哎呀。
Well, hey,
嗯，嘿，
you know, I thought I was on to something.
你知道，我以为我在做某事。
OK, come on, Isaiah.
好吧，来吧
Did we go here? Maybe down here.
我们去过这里吗？ 也许在这里。
There's another.
还有一个。
20. Anything.
任何事情。
This flashlight is kind of garbled.
这个手电筒有点乱码。
Oh, yeah. OK, there's a bonfire.
哦耶。 好的，有篝火。
Oh, the lantern.
哦，灯笼。
Oh, I love this.
哦，我喜欢这个。
But I wish I would have been here
但我希望我是非自愿的。
involuntary.
Oh, hell,
I computer does not like this
哦，见鬼，我电脑不喜欢这样。
I know, I know.
我知道我知道。
I'm flying around the campfire.
我在篝火周围飞来飞去。
And singing a campfire song.
和唱着篝火之歌。
Oh, see, I'm sorry. A song.
哦，看到了，我很抱歉。 一首歌。
Oh, now, I was known
for how much it turned from SpongeBob.
哦，现在，我知道它从海绵宝宝那里变成了多少。
I could just. Oh. Man.
我可以。 哦。 男人。
Whoo ho.
嗬嗬。
Follow the bonfire.
跟着火走。
Follow the bonfires?
跟着篝火?
All there's more. All your right.
还有更多。 你的权利。
There are more.
还有更多。
The whole of all
of all of all of the voting bonfire
全体全体全体全体全体跟着篝火
there.
那里。
Well, this one's a. Lot more earthy.
嗯，这是一个。 更接地气。
Oh, no. It's this exact same because.
不好了。 这是完全相同的，因为。
Because because
because one of our friends.
因为因为因为我们的一位朋友。
I just know, like, if there's a monster,
we have to stand by this.
我只知道，就像，如果有怪物，我们必须坚持这一点。
Folks, just. Like our studio.
伙计们，只是。 就像我们的工作室。
We're off to see the wizard
the wonderful Wizard of Oz.
我们要去看看神奇的绿野仙踪。
That did not work.
那没有用。
I ain't seen no bonfires.
我没有看到没有篝火。
I hear an owl.
我听到猫头鹰的声音。
I hear a owl. Owl.
我听到猫头鹰的声音。 一只猫头鹰。
Friends
朋友们？
friends.
Oh there they are.They are now lost for a second.
哦他们在这里。他们消失了一秒钟。
No, leave that for good luck.
不，祝你好运。
What is that?
那是什么？
Fire.
火。
I was at the monster.
我在怪物身边。
All that's the monster. You
一切都是怪物。 你
made was based off.
制造是基于。
This is not the first play.
这不是第一部戏。
This might be the first one.
这可能是第一个。
I'm oh, my God. Oh.
我是哦，我的上帝。 哦。
I think I heard the
我想我听到了
creature come by.
生物走过来。
I think I heard something, too.
我想我也听到了什么。
But then I thought that was vox.
但后来我认为那是vox。
Well, what was that noise? Oh.
嗯，那是什么声音？ 哦。
An abandoned house.
一座废弃的房子。
This count as indoors.
这个算作是室内吗。
I think it does count as indoors. Yeah.
我认为它确实算作室内。 是的。
So we could probably go inside here
and stay away from.
所以我们可能可以进入这里并远离。
Going to the attic.
去阁楼。
It says. A man. Attic.
它说。 一个男人。 阁楼。
This guy looks like some science
some sort of writer.
这家伙看起来像某种科学某种作家。
Keep. OK.
保持住。 好的。
oh this is a .
这是个。
You know what I look like?
你知道我长什么样吗？
All these guys having glasses.
所有这些人都戴眼镜。
He doesn't
但他不，
this is like your father.
这像你的父亲。
Father? Oh.
父亲？ 哦。
Is that a foetus?
那是胎儿吗？
What is your father's name?
你父亲叫什么名字？
Is it Spike Island?
是斯派克岛吗？
No. This is, I believe, Popeye.
不，我相信这是。 大力水手。
Yeah.
是的。
Pike's like.
派克的样子。
Popeye. Popeye. That's cute.
大力水手。 大力水手。 那很可爱。
Sure, son.
当然，儿子。
I can check inside the drawers
我可以检查抽屉里面
again.
再次。
I turn that shit off.
我关掉那个狗屎。
I'm not.
我不是。
Yes. Turn around. Oh, my God.
是的。 转过来。 我的天啊。
The British guys turned down.
It's a rave.
这是一场狂欢。
Did the people in the 1900s have raves.
1900 年代的人们来说，他们有狂欢吗。
There's a locked door.
Everybody turned to me
有锁着的门。所有人看向我。
To me. Bulabala da
但我不擅长。
Every time it rains it rained as.
每次下雨，那雨下的就像。
Is that vox. Surely. Good.
那是Vox声音吗？ 肯定啊。 好的。
Yeah, I thought that was the actual radio.
是的，我以为那是真正的收音机。
I think. I think we were laughing.
我认为。 我想我们在笑。
Oh, that rain fell from heaven.
哦，那雨是从天堂上掉下来的。
shoobie doobie.
Shoobie Doobie.
AhhhAohh~
That's not funny Vox.
这可不兴玩啊Vox。
Nothing.
没有。
And what happened.. Shoto:Was that Vox.
发生的事情。 Shoto:刚刚那也是Vox吗？
Something done no, no, wait. I was.
不，等等。 曾是。
Vox's singing. Oh.
Vox在唱歌。 哦。
Oh, that was a monster. OK.
哦，我以为那是一个怪物。 好的。
I don't think.
我不这样认为。
No, I already opened everything in there.
不，我已经打开了里面的所有东西。
Eat something.
吃了点东西。
We need to go outside. I don't get this.
我们需要到外面去。 我不明白这一点。
God, I love the cake.
天哪，我喜欢蛋糕。
That was not any of us, that's for sure.
那不是我们中的任何人，这是肯定的。
Sorry. I think I forgot.
对不起。 我想我忘记了。
I found a key.
我找到一把钥匙。
Oh. No way. The one Jordan, Shaq.
哦。 没门。
You just picked it up already.
你刚刚捡起来了。
I picked it up.
我捡起来了。
OK. Let's try it on one of the doors. Hmm.
好的。 让我们在其中一扇门上试一试。 唔。
Another door over there.
那边的另一扇门。
I might be the one for the upstairs.
我可能是楼上的那个。
Yeah.
是的。
Get him open this one.
让他打开这个。
Maybe the one upstairs.
可能是楼上那个。
Yeah, the one up here.
对，就是上面那个。
It's like we're playing.
就像我们在玩一样。
I'll kill me if I open the door. Yeah.
如果我打开门，我会杀了我。 是的。
It's like I only.
就像我一样。
We we we we. Wee.
我们我们我们。
There's a lot of bearded man
有很多大胡子的人。
yeah.
是的。
I'm washing me in my clothes.
Vox唱歌：我正在我的衣服哭泣。
What I.
我什么。
There's a . There's a bed.
有一个。 有一张床。
And there's a bed.
还有一张床。
I'm I'm just being an idiot.
我只是一个白痴。
Oh,my god. a bed.
哦，有床了。
I found a key, though.
不过，我找到了一把钥匙。
You're very, like,
I don't know, enamoured by the bed.
你很喜欢，我不知道，被床迷住了。
It was. That sounds amazing.
它是。 听起来很神奇。
I want to see one of those gifts,
which is that
我想看看那些礼物之一，那就是它只是说床跳恐慌。 它有。
which is it
just says bed jump scare. And it has.
I just kind of walking around
that a bed appears and it goes back.
我只是走来走去，一张床出现了，然后它又回来了。
So my God.
所以我的上帝。
It's a very
crunchy bed, if you like, walk around it.
这是一张非常松脆的床，如果你喜欢，可以在它周围走走。
It sounds like you're.
听起来你是。
Cleaning the grass. Sound effects. Yeah.
清洁草地。 声音特效。 是的。
That's funny.
这是有趣的。
Why the hell? is bathroom?
为什么? 浴室？
Kind of nasty?
有点恶心？
You know, just
你知道，只是
I I think this is just.
我认为这只是。
Basically hearing somebody breathing
like, oh.
基本上听到有人呼吸，哦。
No one.
No one should be coming inside this house.
没有人。 任何人都不应该进入这所房子。
I doubt it.
我对此表示怀疑。
No, I think. Don't you have a key? Like.
不，我想。 你没有钥匙吗？ 像。
Yeah, I do.
是的。
I think it's for the one downstairs. Wait.
我想是给楼下的。 等待。
Who turned out?
谁出来了？
No, no, it would have been from the one up
here, right?
不，不，应该是从上面的那个，对吧？
Who turned that turned on.
谁打开的。
That was on. The first floor. Oh.
那是开着的。 一楼。 哦。
One someone closed the door
有人关了门
The door is shut.
门被摔上了。
Shut close.
摔着关的。
Locked.
锁了。
OK, this place is haunted.
好吧，这个地方闹鬼了。
Yeah. The surprise, the fucking nobody.
是的。 惊喜，他妈的没人。
It's a horror game. Damn, son, speed up.
这是一个恐怖游戏。 该死的，儿子，加快速度。
I mean, they. Run into a fucking
我是说，他们。 碰上一个他妈的
running block
萨马拉从森林中的环跑区。
in Samarra
from the ring in the forest. Man.
Where's is other door so bad?
别的门哪里这么差？
This door.
这扇门。
That's the one.
那就是那个。
Nice. You know.
好的。 你知道。
Which one is it?
哪一个？
Oh, there's, like, spices
and and like, tinctures in there.
哦，里面有香料之类的酊剂。
Oh, it's another locked door.
哦，那是另一扇锁着的门。
Wow. Amazing.
哇。 惊人。
I found a key. Oh, you found it.
我找到了一把钥匙。 哦，你找到了。
Oh, I'm happy for the store.
哦，我为这家商店感到高兴。
For this store.
对于这家店。
Oh, no.
不好了。
It must be for something else.
一定是为了别的。
Really. The other door
that was locked on the first floor.
真的。 另一扇门被锁在一楼。
We're going to.
我们准备去。
We're going to go back upstairs
or maybe this one back here.
我们要回到楼上，或者这个回到这里。
I'm just going to say.
我只想说。
Ah, I think I heard something outside
the house.
啊，我想我在屋外听到了什么。
I'm pretty sure it's, like
stuck in the. Vox?
我很确定是这样的。 Vox?
Yeah. Was that you?
是的。 那是你吗？
Oh, yeah. I'm still upstairs.
哦耶。 我还在楼上。
The sound is confusing me.
I thought you guys were up.
声音让我很困惑。 我以为你们都起来了。
Did you just hear that super loud noise?
你刚刚听到那超级响亮的声音吗？
Yeah, I saw someone else is. Yeah.
是的，我看到别人是。 是的。
Something's outside the house right now.
现在房子外面有东西。
Yeah, that was loud as heck.
是的，那声音太大了。
I think it can't.
我认为不能。
It can't come inside.
它进不来。
So did you try it on the door
down downstairs?
那你在楼下的门上试过吗？
Like the house is like
the house is like a condom.
就像房子就像房子就像一个避孕套。
It can't really come inside, so.
所以它不能真正进来。（？？什么比喻鬼才）
Or any in the room. Oh.
或者房间里的任何一个。 哦。
These guys.
这些家伙。
The boys.
男孩们。
Oh, this. One's a white new.
哦，这个。 一个是白色的新。
New room. Oh.
新房间。 哦。
In here.
在这里。
This room.
这个房间。
For a second,
I thought that because of the way.
有一秒钟，我认为是因为方式。
The drawers.
抽屉。
Lock and the drawers, the phones,
it looked like he was bold.
锁和抽屉，电话，看起来他很大胆。
And I thought that they were just
我以为它们只是这所房子里的图像，只是他逐渐失去了头发。
images in this house was just him
gradually losing his hair.
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh, he's. Pissed. Already. Use
the key was was.
哦，他是已经很生气了。
This was the room that I found was a key
that I found at this room.
这是我发现的房间，是我在这个房间找到的钥匙。
There's other locked doors over here.
这里还有其他上锁的门。
I tried already,
and none of the doors open.
我已经试过了，没有一个门打开。
The ghost really wants us, by the way.
顺便说一句，鬼真的想要杀我们。
Holy shit. All
天啊。
right, fuck off.
对，滚蛋。
Boom, boom.
轰，轰。
Boom.
轰。
The doors just keep closing abruptly.
门只是不停地突然关闭。
In front of us.
在我们的前面。
No, I think we already in this.
不，我想我们已经在这了。
I see your dumb arse outside.
我在外面看到那些鬼蠢驴。
Use my key to someone to.
用我的钥匙给别人。
See your dumb arse walking around.
看到你这蠢驴四处走动。
Only the person who picked it up
can use it.
只有捡到它的人才能使用它。
Now, do you open the new
现在，你打开新
boom?
繁荣？
You open the new.
你打开新的。
Room.
房间。
Where is this DMCA music?
这是 DMCA 音乐在哪里？
I hope it's on.
我希望它已经开启。
No, I doubt it.
不，我怀疑。
OK, now it's super old.
好的，现在它已经超级老了。
We should be good. OK, cool.
我们应该很好。 嗯不错。
You have to
你必须
a bit.
一点点。
Yeah.
是的。
Would you do this thing?
你会做这件事吗？
Yeah, happy birthday.
是的，生日快乐。
Mr President,
总统先生，
happy birthday to you.
祝你生日快乐。
I swear to you,
我向你发誓，
I think you guys use my key.
我想你们用我的钥匙。
Don't even see my inventory.
甚至看不到我的库存。
I think you can.
我想你可以。
Hello. Luckily, Tora Korea. Tora!
你好。
Tora!
You're out there.
你在外面。
Oh. Happy birthday, Mr President.
哦。生日快乐总统先生。
Oh, I think I see him.
哦，我想我看到他了。
Oh. Sorry.
哦。 对不起。
I was yawning. I'm sorry.
我在打哈欠。 对不起。
Sorry. Sorry.
对不起。 对不起。
I'm very, very woozy at the moment.
我现在非常非常头晕。
The alcohol's getting so big.
酒劲越来越大了。
I found a key.
我找到了一把钥匙。
Nice. OK, I'll close the door.
I think I'll feel now.
好的。 好的，我会关上门。 我想我现在会感觉到。
I can't even close the door.
我连门都关不上。
I'll close the door. I tried.
我会关上门。 我试过。
You cannot close the door.
你不能关上门。
I got you upstairs.
我让你上楼了。
Yeah. Oh,
是的。 哦，
which did you find where?
你在哪里找到的？
I found some sort of key.
我找到了某种钥匙。
I'm going to try it on the door again.
我要在门上再试一次。
Dude. It keeps getting me.
老兄。 它一直在吸引我。
Yeah. It works. Nice.
是的。 有用。 好的。
You guys heard that, right?
你们听到了，对吧？
Yeah.
是的。
He's not a happy boy.
他不是一个快乐的男孩。
Oh, there it is.
哦，是的。
Nice. OK.
好的。 好的。
OK, now we're just knocking, right?
好的，现在我们只是敲门，对吧？
There we go.
我们去吧。
That's not Vox.
那不是Vox。
It's just the game, right?
这只是游戏声音，对吧？
The ghost. Or.
鬼。 或者。
Yeah, ok.
是的，好的。
OK. It's none of these doors.
好的。 这些门都不是。
So it has to be one of them downstairs.
所以楼下一定是其中之一。
I think it's the one on the first floor.
我认为是一楼的那个。
Yeah, that's the connecting door.
对，就是连接门。
This one was really loud last time.
上次这个声音真的很大。
Yeah, this is the one. OK.
是的，就是这个。 好的。
Oh, that's nasty.
哦，那太恶心了。
That's kind of gross. OK,
but there's a key inside his mouth.
这有点恶心。 好的，但他嘴里有一把钥匙。
Oh, I use my key on this one.
He's like a. Wing.
哦，我在这个上用我的钥匙。 他就像一个。 翅膀。
He's like an when I got a key when
他就像我拿到钥匙的时候
ok, I got a key.
好的，我有钥匙。
I also.
我也。
I open the door, roll this door.
我打开门，滚动这扇门。
I open it with my key. Oh.
我用我的钥匙打开它。 哦。
You cannot see shit in this.
你看不到这里面的东西。
Where am. Ike?
我在哪里。
You know, each cloud contains, man.
你知道，每一朵云都包含，伙计。
pennies from heaven shoobie doobie
来自天堂的硬币，数比都比
I think.
我认为。
No, I just open.
不，我只是打开。
If we have another. Key here
before I just.
如果我们有另一个钥匙。 在我之前这里的。
Open the door.
打开门。
It's connecting the kitchen to the side.
它将厨房连接到一侧。
That's the thing.
事情就是这样。
I think there might be a
the key is probably for upstairs.
我想可能有一个钥匙可能是楼上的。
You're going to go back upstairs.
你要回到楼上。
Upstairs to this house
has us going running around left
在这所房子的楼上，我们打开门左右跑来跑去。 是的。
and right on the open the door. Yes.
Up, up, up, up, up.
啊啵啵啵啵啵啵
Zap is using my collar.
正在使用我的项圈。
Show you using my collar.
让你看看我的衣领。
I said, why am I putting.
我说，我为什么放。
There's only three colours for all.
所有人只有三种颜色。
You guys heard that, right?
你们听到了，对吧？
Yeah, I heard that.
是的，我听说了。
It's locked.
它被锁了。
Yeah.
是的。
That was.
那是。
I found a key
我找着一个钥匙
for this one.
用于这个的。
I I'm on my way home eventually.
我终于在回家的路上了。
Get out of this house.
离开这个房子。
Come for this.
为此而来。
Oh, shall we end it right now?
哦，我们现在就结束吧？
All right, guys, I got it.
好的，伙计们，我明白了。
All right. You're already in it.
好的。 你已经在其中了。
I feel like a different icon,
like the unlock.
我感觉像是一个不同的图标，就像解锁一样。
I was like, oh, I did it.
我当时想，哦，我做到了。
The door's open, too.
这个门也开了
I did all the time.
我一直都这样做。
Never mind all these doors
just, like, lead to this area. OK.
别介意所有这些门，就像通向这个区域一样。 好的。
There's nothing in here. Dude.
这里什么都没有。 老兄。
Imagine we just like waiting.
想象一下，我们只是，等下。
Oh, the the books.
哦，书。
The books.
图书。
It's a puzzle for the books.
这是书籍难题。
We need to go search
for the rest of the books in the house.
我们需要去寻找房子里剩下的书。
Yeah, like,
I just pulled out one of the books.
是的，就像，我刚拿出一本书。
It must have unlocked something somewhere.
它一定在某个地方解锁了一些东西。
There might be another secret entrance.
可能还有另一个秘密入口。
Oh, up here. Up here. Attic. Attic.
哦，这里。 上面这儿。 阁楼。 阁楼。
Oh, grab the attic door .
哦，打开阁楼的门
Oh, oh.
哦，哦。
OK, now what's I was just say. Oh.
好的，现在我刚才说的是什么。 哦。
Everybody. Oh, yeah, I saw that.
大家。 哦，是的，我看到了。
I saw that.
我看到了。
I will need three.
我需要三个。
African effigies made from wood to create
the hex for the crypt door in the story.
用木头制成的非洲人像，为故事中的地穴门创造了六角形。
These two get back in.
两人回去。
Eventually,
these effigies should be hung up.
最终，这些肖像应该被挂起来。
Somewhere in the forest,
I crafted a ceremonial dagger
在森林的某个地方，我制作了一把仪式匕首来配合最后的仪式。
to go with the final ritual.
I can use this to break the seal.
我可以用它来打破封印。
OK, I've seen one of those things out
in the woods.
好的，我在树林里看到了其中一件事。
Yeah, we saw one. Yeah, me too.
是的，我们看到了一个。 我也是。
Yeah, I just grabbed one.
是的，我刚抓了一个。
I think that was just, like, up here.
我认为那只是，就像，在这里。
Right on.
对了。
Let me see how touching my inventory.
让我看看我的库存是有啥用处。
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
Mm Da da da da dum.
嗯，哒哒哒哒哒。
Oh, no, never mind that.
That was an effigy.
哦，不，别管那个。 那是一个肖像。
Do we have the axe?
我们有斧头吗？
Always. We're supposed to get the axe. Oh.
总是。 我们应该得到斧头。 哦。
I guess we go out there and look for it.
我想我们要出去寻找它。
Yeah.
是的。
OK. There's all this. OK.
好的。 这就是一切。 好的。
I was going to say,
if this house had us, like,
我想说，如果这所房子让我们，就像，他妈的到处乱跑，什么都没有，我一直，就像，最糟糕的。
fucking around and running around for,
like, nothing, I've been, like, the worst.
Oh, my God. This is a crusty Ben.
我的天啊。 这是一个难搞的家伙。
Yeah, it sounds like crushed up leaves,
是的，听起来像是被压碎的叶子，就像，你
like, you
all right, let's get out this house.
好吧，让我们离开这个房子。
We're done here.
我们在这里完成了。
You're so green. Colour, bitch. Pink.
你太绿了 婊子。 粉色的。
Wish this would shut up.
希望这会闭嘴。
But I have to use the green colour.
但我必须使用绿色。
FYI, in this right flick.
仅供参考，在这个正确的电影中。
Whatever I ever bro
我无所谓了，兄弟
whatever.
已经无所谓了
Mom, you understand me?
妈妈，你懂我吗？
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
是的，是的，是的，是的。
It's not. Fake. God.
它不是伪造的。 上帝。
How do we find our way back?
我们如何找到回去的路？
You put a lot of sticks.
你放了很多棍子。
I you were the only one that passed.
Yeah, you do.
我你是唯一一个通过的。 是的，你会的。
I think we follow you
我想我们跟着你。
how are you?
你好吗？
Are you all right
to. The bonfire over. Here?
你没事吧。 篝火没了吗。 这里？
Well, I.
嗯，我。
It's my decision making so bad.
这是我的决定，太糟糕了。
I you sure you're not drunk, too?
我确定你没有像vox一样醉？
Is this where we started?
这是我们开始的地方吗？
Mm. No.
嗯 不。
Different one.
不一样的。
Put a lot of glow sticks
at the first part,
在第一部分放很多荧光棒，如果你按照其中一个
and if you follow one of those, we'll
get to one of the
，我们将到达其中一个
I think.
我认为。
I think the monster is gone.
我认为怪物已经不见了。
No, no.
不，不。
I heard something breathing upfront. Oh.
我听到前面有什么东西在呼吸。 哦。
You guys hear that, right?
你们听到了，对吧？
Yeah, I hear it.
是的，我听到了。
Yeah.
是的。
Because it's an effigy.
因为它是人像。
Oh, that was the effigy
that was making on the noises.
哦，那是发出声音的人像。
Oh, you broke.
哦，你坏了。
You broke it.
你把它弄坏了。
I think we need to run
我认为我们需要奔跑
that was.
那是。
You didn't.
你没有。
Oh. Oh, my God.
哦。 我的天啊。
Oh, what the fuck.
哦，
I love that.
我喜欢那个。
It gets Shoto, every single time.
但是，它每一次都无一例外能吓到Shoto
Everybody shut up.
大家闭嘴。
I need to listen.
我需要听。
Penis.
鸡鸡~
Like I'm not talking, sweetie.
就像我不说话一样，亲爱的。
Shut the fuck up.
他妈的闭嘴。
So here's.
所以这里。
That.
那。
Grass. That was just grass.
那只是草。
Oh, that's a no.
哦，那不是。
That's grass. Yeah.
那就是草。 是的。
Oh, my God.
We haven't gone outside in so long.
我的天啊。 我们已经很久没有在外边了。
We can all recognisable.
我们都能认出来。
I know. Oh, grass and so long.
我知道。 哦，草，这么长。
Oh, guys. Morning.
哦，伙计们。 早晨。
Oh. Oh, is it this entrance?
哦~。 哦，是这个入口吗？
Yeah, it might be.
是的，它可能是。
Oh, we went back to the entrance.
哦，我们又回到了入口。
We actually went back to the entrance. How
我们实际上回到了入口处。 那是怎么回事。
what is that.
oh it's coming, it's coming.
它来了，它来了。
Run to a bonfire, run inside
or to a bonfire a beast.
跑到篝火旁，跑到里面或到篝火旁。一头野兽。
Follow me, follow me into the house.
跟我来，跟我进屋。
We all get to the house.
我们都到了房子。
Quickly
everyone to the confines of our houses.
很快，每个人都到我们家的范围内。
Safe house what you do best, guys us
do what you do best.
安全屋你最擅长的，伙计们，我们做你最擅长的。
Stay inside.
呆在里面。
Dogs go.
Down.
向下。
I love that.
我喜欢那个。
Every time we go in here,
we get Resident Evil, save music.
每次我们进入这里，我们都会得到生化危机，保存音乐。
I mean. It's actually the safe.
我是说。 它实际上是保险箱。
It feels like the safe room music.
感觉就像安全室的音乐。
It's very reminiscence.
是很怀念的。
Here.
这里。
We can go back to the first one,
find that we didn't
我们可以回到第一个，发现我们没有找到我们
find the the effigy that we find
that was on Facebook.
找到的肖像。
Yeah,
是的，
but how did we get
但是我们是如何从这里到达第一场篝火的呢？
to the first bonfire from here?
You know, we just go to the right, like,
outside of the house.
你知道，我们只是向右走，就像，在房子外面。
I don't think we went from the backyard
to look from here.
我不认为我们从后院去从这里看。
Oh, we got run.
哦，我们跑了。
We got to run.
我们得跑了。
Ike Ike Ike get the fuck away.
Ike他妈的快躲开。
I'm going back inside the house.
我要回到屋里。
To the house.
到房子。
I'm going back in the house.
我要回屋了。
I got usually he was like, very.
我得到的通常他是这样的，非常。
He's why we do not touch grass.
他就是我们不能碰草的原因。
He's right behind
you. He's right behind you.
他就在你身后。 他就在你身后。Ike。
Oh, no, no, no.
哦，不，不，不。
Close the. Door.
关上。 门。
Close the door. Closed your fucking forest
spirit.
关门。 打消你他妈的森林精神。
Dude, you're kind of cool.
哥们，你有点酷。
I can save him.
我可以救他。
I can see. I still alive.
我可以看到。 我还活着。
I got you. I got you.
我接到你了。 我接到你了。
Oh. No.
哦。 不。
Why are you closing the door?
你为什么关门？
You fucking all like.
你傻吗。
For us e to revive.
让我们复活。
Like me.
像我这样的。
Part of me thought that there wasn't
我的一部分认为这张地图上不会有敌人，
going to be an enemy on this map
because we didn't see anybody for so long.
因为我们已经很久没有看到任何人了。
I guess it just waited for us
to get to the attic.
我猜它只是在等我们去阁楼。
This one.
这个。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
The bonfire is outside.
篝火在外面。
We went to the right.
我们往右边走。
We're going hunting down by forest.
我们要去森林打猎。
Spirit and type for spirit. Groot.
I'm pretty
我很漂亮
it's groot time.
现在是格鲁特时间。
I am Groot
我是格鲁特。
We're here.
我们在这儿。
We're groot.
我们是格鲁特。
In the.
在里面。
Fruit.
水果。
I don't
even remember where the first bonfire is.
我甚至不记得第一个篝火在哪里。
Oh, yeah?
哦耶？
You guys are making me yawn, you know?
你们让我打哈欠，你知道吗？
And this. There's the first one fight.
还有这个。 有第一个战斗地点。
Well, there's something.
嗯，有事。
Oh, ha ha. Ha.
哦，哈哈。 哈。
OK, the one fight.
好的，
We're safe here, right?
我们在这里很安全，对吧？
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
是的，是的，是的，是的。
It was so I. Can't see him.
就是这样，我看不见他。
I cannot see him. Either.
我看不见他。 任何一个。
I can just hear
我能听到
you walking.
你在走路吗。
I want to leave my glow sticks right here.
我想把我的荧光棒留在这儿。
I know that.
我知道。
Next month I think we lost.
下个月，我想我们迷路了。
I think we are lost. Bros.
我想我们的确迷路了。
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
喔喔喔喔
Oh, I'm
哦，我是
following you.Ike
跟着你。
the look on
Shoto的脸的样子
Shoto's face, like his character
model looks so tired and horrified.
就像他的角色模型一样，看起来非常疲惫和恐惧。
every time he goes wooh
每当他发出wooh的声音时候
Oh, I'm just. Stretching.
哦，我只是在拉伸啦
I'm just stretching.
我只是在伸展。
Rah, rah, rah, rah, rah, rah, bro.
啊啊啊啊啊啊兄弟
And talking, like, an Indy girl.
同时说话的方式仿佛一个印地女孩。
What do you really think? Yeah,
I feel like, oh, one way.
你真的怎么想？ 是的，我觉得，哦，一种方式。
I think that's a mistake.
我认为这是一个错误。
He's a he's over there.
他是一个，他在那边。
If you would just like to go over.
如果你只是想过去。
We just got to be better.
我们只需要变得更好。
Watch this.
看这个。
We're going to die.
我们要死了。
No. Aren't you going back to the house?
不。你不回家吗？
Is this back to the house?
这是回屋的路吗？
No, no, no. This is someplace different.
不不不。 这是不同的地方。
You know, this is a different area.
你知道，这是一个不同的领域。
ALL Let's go this way.
让我们走这条路。
Is this back to the house?
这是回屋吗？
Oh, I see.
我懂了。
Ghost like.
鬼似的。
I know. Every.
我知道。 每一个。
This. Oh, this is the aisle.
这。 哦，这是过道。
This is the other house. OK, so left.
这是另一间房子。 好，就这样离开了。
OK, so what if we just continue down
this path?
好的，那么如果我们继续沿着这条路走呢？
Like we didn't go down here.
就像我们没有去这里一样。
A bonfire. A bonfire? Oh.
篝火。 篝火？ 哦。
Yeah. I'll put some
glow sticks down, too. Oh,
是的。 我也会放一些荧光棒。 哦，
ok. I know how to use those.
行。 我知道如何使用这些。
The exam palace.
考场。
Yeah.
是的。
Now, do we are we here in effigy?
Anywhere?
现在，我们是在这里的肖像吗？ 任何地方？
I found one over here last time.
我上次在这里找到了一个。
OK, all right.
好的没问题。
Drop some sticks.
放下一些棍子。
I'm on the way to the Sistine Chapel.
我在去西斯廷教堂的路上。
Effigy. Effigy? Yes.
雕像。 雕像？ 是的。
Ah Poggers.  one more. we've been pondering that one,
which is find the one that we saw.
哦很好很好。再来一个。我在想这是不是我们看到的那个被找到了。
I mean, one more,
and then we're done. On the ground.
我的意思是，再来一个，然后我们就完成了。地上。
Yeah. Yeah, it.
Was the first one that we saw.
是的。 是的，它。 是我们看到的第一个。
We found the other ones,
but we haven't seen the first one.
我们找到了其他的，但我们还没有看到第一个。
The first one.
第一个？
Was it, like, near the house, maybe? Or.
可能是在房子附近吗？ 或者。
OK, so when we found the first bonfire,
then we went to a second one
好的，所以当我们找到第一个篝火，然后我们去了第二个，
and from there, I dropped down glow sticks
on the entire way when I found it,
从那里，当我找到它时，我在整个过程中都放下了荧光棒，
but I haven't been able
to, like, rediscover them.
但我无法重新发现它们。
All right, let's if we can go back
to, like, the big house,
好吧，如果我们能回到那个大房子，你知道，那个
you know, the one
we were finding all of the shit
that I reckon that will help us find
我们找到了所有我认为可以帮助我们找到的东西
the other bonfires. The house.
其他的篝火。 房子。
That the original
我们经历过的原来的我们原来的鬼屋。
our original haunted house
that we were gone through.
The house.
房子。
Where we found all the shit and the what.
我们在哪里找到了所有的狗屎和什么。
Is this place
是这个地方吗
oh, is this a mausoleum or graveyard?
哦，这是陵墓还是墓地？
Yeah, this is a graveyard.
是的，这里是墓地。
Graveyard mausoleum.
墓地陵墓。
These not.
这些不是。
OK. Oh, what the fuck is this
one thinking?
好的。 哦，这他妈在想什么？
The gates of hell.
地狱之门。
Oh, maybe this is where we got to go.
哦，也许这就是我们要去的地方。
The man, the myth, the legend.
男人，神话，传说。
This smoke.
这烟。
I love Glowsticks.
我喜欢荧光棒。
Gone. It.
走了。 它。
The flashlight is not doing me
any favours.
手电筒对我没有任何帮助。
Lonnie ls.
朗尼
Mm hmm. Okay,
嗯嗯。 好的，这里是巴登在一起。
here lies Baden together.
Why the fuck does that mean?
这他妈是什么意思？
Zeke again?
又是齐克？
Something about the difference
I can't tighten.
关于我无法收紧的区别。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh, stop.
哦，停下来。
Ike:Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔
Ike:Ow, ow, ow, ow.
呜呜呜呜呜呜
Oh,oh I thought that. that was Reimu.
我以为那是蕾姆。
no that was me.
不那是我。
Sorry. So.
对不起。 所以。
Oh, my apologies to both of you, then.
哦，那我向你们两个道歉。
Oh, my goodness.
哦，我的天啊。
Why not? Let's not talk about it.
Let's not.
为什么不？ 我们不要谈论它。 不要吧。
I thought.
我想。
OK, ok. Not not. Don't look at me.
好的好的。 不是这样的。 别看着我。
Don't look at me.
不要看着我。
Let's left him here.
把他丢在这吧
Let's go, Ike
我们走吧。Ike
I know. Oh, come back.
我知道错了。 回来啊。
I'm sorry.
对不起嘛。
OK? This should be close by.
好的？ 这应该就在附近。
Around this area.
围绕这个区域。
I think we just got more far away. Really?
我想我们只是走得更远了。 真的吗？
And if anybody can see anything,
because I sure as heck can.
如果有人能看到任何东西，因为我肯定能看到。
I'm blind.
我现在是盲人。
right now.
Do it my way.
按照我的方式去做。
I mean, still still still.
我的意思是，不要动。
Someone's to the right I.
有人在我的右边。
All right.
好的。
Sounds like a sound.
听起来像一个声音。
I hear the sounds of off
我听到关闭的声音
is the purple on you.
是你身上的紫色。
We're dead
我们要死了
It was nice knowing you all.
“此生”认识你们真是太好了。
He's coming after. Us.
紧随我们其后。
Well well, tonight it's been.
好吧好吧，今晚就是这样。
It's been an honour.
It's been an honour serving.
这是一种荣誉。 这是一项荣誉。
Goodbye for you
为你再见。
I bucks
follow the classics to.
追随经典来。
Follow the classics. Get the fuck out.
追随经典。 滚出去。
Oh, bonfire, bonfire, bonfire, bonfire.
哦，篝火，篝火，篝火，篝火。
We ha.
我们哈。
This is our Siebert circle fucker.
这是我们的西伯特圈混蛋。
Get out of here.
离开这里。
Yeah, oh.
是啊，哦。
Oh, my God. We just need one more.
我的天啊。 我们只需要一个。
We already found it.
我们已经找到了。
Please.
请。
Just one more.
还有一个。
One more.
一个。
Please. Just.
请。 只是。
My goodness.
我的天啊。
I don't.
我不。
I don't know how to find it again.
我不知道如何再次找到它。
Yeah, I really.
是的，我真的。
I really just want to find it,
and then that's it.
我真的只是想找到它，然后就是这样。
And then we dones though
然后我们就完成了。
but the question is, where the fuck is it?
但问题是，它他妈的在哪里？
Was it a.
是不是一个。
Leading us to a haunted house?
带我们去鬼屋？
That's the haunted house that.
I want to go back to.
那就是那个鬼屋。 我想回去。
The first bonfire we ever found
我们发现的第一个篝火，你在开玩笑吧。
oh, you're kidding me.
Yeah. I think it's coming after me.
是的。 我认为它正在追赶我。
Oh, it is.
哦，是的。
Oh, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔
Circling us.
绕着我们转。
See? Bear, see, bear.
看啥？ 熊熊。
Nice
Does this kind of thing go away?
这种事情会消失吗？
My IQ inside this house right ike.
我在这房子里的智商不错。
I'm sorry for being loud. Ike, ike.
我很抱歉大声说话。
Are you in here? Ike?
你在吗？ 艾克？
Oh, he's out here.
哦，他在外面。
I think I'd want to check out the house
我想去检查一下房子
He went back to the original house.
他回到了原来的房子。
Yeah.
是的。
We are gonna go pick up vox.
我们要去接Vox吗
Mm hmm. Just him updated.
嗯嗯。他刚刚更新了。
Oh, he found the effigy. Oh, he found it.
哦，他找到肖像了。 哦，他找到了。
He found it. Oh, dude. Well, now.
他找到了。 哦，伙计。 现在好了。
Where do we have to go
now? Do we? We got to the mausoleum.
我们现在必须去哪里？ 我们要不要？ 我们到了陵墓。
The ritual I think we need.
我认为我们需要的仪式。
Yeah, we need to go back to the cemetery.
是的，我们需要回到墓地。
Oh, oh, oh, whoa. Six.
哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦 六。
I keep looking.
我一直在寻找。
Over on.
结束。
Thank you so much for the raid.
非常感谢你的raid。
Who raided? Hold on.
稍等。
Somebody raid it, and I didn't get to say
thank you for that.
有人raid，我没来得及说谢谢。
Thank you so much for the raid.
非常感谢你的raid。
Whoo hoo!
嗬嗬！
Who's here. Huh?
谁在这里。 嗯？
Best dish raid.
最好的raid。
Thank you for the raid, dude.
谢谢你的raid，伙计。
Hello? Hello, Ike?
你好？ 喂，艾克？
I found it.
I found it. I got it. I got it.
我找到了。 我找到了。 我得到了它。 我得到了它。
You got it. Nice.
你找到了。 好极了。
We just got to get back to the house
now, right?
我们现在就得回屋，对吧？
I was in it.
我在里面。
The ah, the mausoleum that we have to go
to, that's the thing that.
啊，我们要去的陵墓，就是那个东西。
Was there, like a blade up there
that we needed again or something.
在那里，就像我们再次需要的刀片一样。
Or was it.
或者是它。
Was that what we needed? I don't know.
那是我们需要的吗？ 我不知道。
To the haunted house?
去鬼屋？
You won't go back to the haunted house,
right?
你不会回鬼屋吧？
Well,
I thought there was still something there.
好吧，我以为那里还有什么。
I is there.
我在那里。
I thought all we had to do
was just I grab something from there,
我想我们所要做的就是从那里拿点东西，
and then we read the book,
and then we got the outline.
然后我们读了这本书，然后我们得到了大纲。
You know, if we grab anything, OK,
maybe we need to go back then and to the
你知道，如果我们抓住任何东西，好吧，也许我们需要回到那个时候
the cemetery or whatever
the heck it wants, right?
墓地或任何它想要的东西，对吧？
Yeah. The mausoleum. You know, the master.
是的。 陵墓。 你知道，大师。
Because there's a door that was sealed off
I think that's where it is.
因为有一扇门被封住了，我想那是它所在的地方。
Where is Reimu?Reimu?
Reimu人呢？ Reimu啊。
I was actually, like, in front of me,
but she didn't come back for some reason.
实际上她刚刚就在我面前，但她出于某种原因没有回来。
Hmm. Couldn't hear us
唔。 没听到我们说他在这里吗？
was he here?
Oh, no, vox vox vox vox
哦，不，vox
Vox. my hair.
vox，我的头发。
Thank you so much for the raid
非常感谢你的raid。
Hope you at a great stream.
希望你可以收看到一个很棒的直播。
I'll come here. We are just reviving afar.
我会来这里，只是重新复活。
I've never even seen that thing
very close up.
我甚至从未近距离看过那东西。
It looks like a deer.
它看起来像一只鹿。
I think.
我认为。
Yeah.
是的。
And long arms.
还有长臂。
We oh,
我们哦，
you're cute when you're young,
both of you.
你们年轻的时候都很可爱，你们俩。
Very adorable.
非常可爱。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Howhhh.That's.
(Vox:咆哮。) 那是。
That's how, like, you do it again. howh.
那就是你的独特风格，再叫一声。 (Vox:敷衍的咆哮。)
Is it, son?
是吗，儿子？
He's like.
他就像。
(嘤~)
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh, my God. Now, that.
我的天啊。 现在。
That was some range.
那真是超出我的范围了
you're having.
你正拥有的。
We're having, like,
some kind of a commune.
我们有，就像，某种公社。
Anyway, I like squeak battle
无论如何，我喜欢吱吱作响的战斗。
squeak off.
I hear Reimu, like,
cutting in and out from the distance.
我听到蕾姆能发出，就像从远处切入和切出一样的声音。
Yeah, the game does that.
是的，游戏就是这么做的。
The game does that.
游戏就是这样做的。
Occasionally. You just had, like, a
偶尔你刚刚发出了，啊
yeah,
是的，
but. Oh.
但。 哦。
What what happened?
发生了什么事？
What did you do?
你做了什么？
What did she do?
她做了什么？
All now. We're.
现在都。 是。
We're kids.
我们是孩子。
There it is.
它在那里。
Zoo were getting clamped by this.
动物园被这个钳制了。
Look at that here.
看看这里。
What is that?
那是什么？
Hello? Oh.
你好？ 哦。
Oh, that hurt my stomach.
哦，这伤害了我的胃。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
It's OK.
没关系。
Can't touch us here.
它不能在这里碰我们。
He's like, dum dum dum dum dum dum.
他就像，达达达达达达达达达达达
You got a friend in me
你有一个我的朋友
I guess we're going to go.
我想我们要走了。
He's pretty far away.
他离得很远。
Let's try to find the.
让我们试着找到。
The cemetery or the mausoleum,
whatever the heck you call it.
墓地或陵墓，不管你怎么称呼它。
The for and near miles.
为和近英里。
And you're
而你
she just did it for us.
她刚刚为我们做到了。
I'm pretty sure
Reimu just did it for us.
我很确定蕾姆刚刚为了我们做到了。
Reimu  Reimu. Oh, my God, Reimu.
蕾姆，蕾姆？天，蕾姆
We were just chilling.
我们只是在放松。
And then suddenly,
where did you get to the next area?
然后突然，你从哪里到下一个区域？
Did you go to the mausoleum?
你去过陵墓吗？
We got stuck.
The monster kept circling us.
我们被困住了。 怪物一直绕着我们转。
Oh, my goodness.
哦，我的天啊。
I like it.
我喜欢。
I think my heart
can take much more of this.
我想我的心可以承受更多。
Yeah,
I think this is a good place to stop.
是的，我认为这是一个停下来的好地方。
Yeah, this is a good place to stop.
是的，这是一个停下来的好地方。
To be honest, we did a lot today. Oh.
老实说，我们今天做了很多。 哦。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
For a. While, it was a lot of fun.
为一个。 同时，这很有趣。
Making
制造
chicken complete
this game one of the day, though.
不过，小鸡在一天中完成了这场比赛。
I'm really curious of the other chapters.
我真的很好奇其他章节。
Yeah, I think.
是的，我想。
Like Reimu carried us at the end there.
就像最后蕾姆带我们飞了。
Yeah, you carried us.
是的，你带飞了我们。
We couldn't go anywhere, so thank. You.
我们当时哪儿也去不了，谢谢你。
Yeah, we were surrounded by the big deer bitch..
是的，我们被傻叉大鹿包围了。
We just hanging out here?
我们只是在这里闲逛？
Yeah.
是的。
deer bitch.
傻叉，大鹿。
I don't like you
我不喜欢 你。
ok. OK.
行。 好的。
Well, how do we exit this?
那么，我们如何退出呢？
I don't know how you exit this arm.
我不知道你是怎么退出这个手臂的。
Oh, go to sleep.
哦，去睡觉吧。
I don't think it's a safe lane.
我不认为这是一条安全的道。
It is. I'll go to lobby intended.
这是。 我会去游说打算。
I think that's all.
我认为仅此而已。
Hello. Here we are.
你好。 我们到了。
There he go. Lobby.
他去了。 大堂。
Yeah, I think this is right.
是的，我认为这是对的。
You may go back to this court
just to say bye.
你可以回到这个只是为了说再见。
Yeah. Yeah, I can see that.
是的。 是的，我可以看到。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
Let me put your guys's volumes
back to normal again.
让我让你们的音量恢复正常。
Yeah, I remember to turn off,
like, your voice activity in the game.
是的，我记得关掉你在游戏中的语音活动。
Yeah. Push it out.
是的。 把它推出来。
Push.
推。
It's OK.
没关系。
Hello?
你好？
Hello.
你好。
Oh, oh, oh.
哦哦哦。
There we go.
我们去吧。
Oh, my goodness.
哦，我的天啊。
Whoo! Boy! How was something?
哇！ 男生！ 怎么样？
That was a lot. I do.
那是很多。 我愿意。
I don't know. How finnane on Lucca.
我不知道。 对卢卡的看法如何。
They did this in, like, six and seven.
他们当时玩了。
They played this for 7 hours
or something like that.
他们玩了6 7个小时或这么久。
Yeah, I would have guy and died.
是的，我会死的。
They just they just, like,
他们只是，就像，继续，喜欢它整个晚上，
continued on, like it the entire night
and, like, made it to the end somehow.
就像，以某种方式走到了尽头。
Built this. Friend. Yeah,
建了这个。 朋友。 是的，
I could not do that.
我不能那样做。
Did they clear the whole game?
他们通关了整个游戏吗？
Yeah, they clear the whole game. Oh, wow.
是的，他们完成了整个游戏。 哦，哇。
Well, we have we're not going
to let ourselves be outdone.
好吧，我们不会让自己不甘示弱。
Let's do this again
sometime. Yeah, definitely.
让我们在某个时候再做一次。 是的，绝对的。
We can finish this.
我们可以完成这个。
And because we have two more chapters
left, right, it looks like two or three
而且因为我们还有两章左右，看起来还有两三章。
more chapters off.
Yeah, I think it looks like it. Yeah.
是的，我觉得它看起来像。 是的。
If you look on the board. Yeah.
如果你看板上。 是的。
If we can look at the blade
如果我们能，看透刀片。
through.
Three, more. Like.
三，更多。
Through productive voice.
通过富有成效的声音。
Actually.
实际上。
I take a look at it.
我看一看。
We can finish this
and in a second livestream yeah.
我们可以在第二次直播中完成这个，是的。
Yeah, for sure. We can have chapter four.
耶，当然了。 我们可以有第四章。
Look at that. Yeah,
we did literally. Yeah.
看那个。 是的，我们确实做到了。 是的。
Next time we can like end this off
since there's only one seat.
下次我们可以结束这个，因为只有一个剩下的了。
Yeah,
there should be only six chapters, right?
是的，应该只有六章吧？
Because yeah, it looks like
there's only room for six chapters. Hmm.
因为是的，看起来只有六章的空间。 唔。
Chapter four. But
is it really long before you let me chat?
第四回。 但是，真的很久以后才让我回去看聊天室吗？
So I think we just finished this
in the, in the next collab.
所以我想我们刚刚在下一次合作中完成了这个。
I guess yeah.
我想是的。
Yeah.
是的。
Sounds good to me. Sounds like a plan. OK, yeah.
听起来不错。 听起来像是个计划。 好的，是的。
All right. Thank you guys for coming by.
好的。 谢谢各位光临。
It was really fun going to play with you
all again.
再次和大家一起玩真的很有趣。
Yeah, it was something that wasn't UNO,
like we promised.
是的，正如我们承诺的那样，这不是像UNO的那种东西。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I remember that was like,
oh, let's do this again.
我记得那就像，哦，让我们再做一次。
Just not,UNO. Yeah.
只是不是UNO， 是的。
Oh, thank you for inviting us.
哦，谢谢你邀请我们。
It was really fun. Yeah.
Thank you for wanting to play.
这真的很有趣。 是的。 谢谢你。
It was really.
这是真的。
Yeah, I love that.
是的，我喜欢那个。
That was a lot of fun. Really. It was.
那很有趣。 真的。 它是。
OK. I'll see you guys around.
好的。 我会看到你们周围的。
Bye, guys.
再见，伙计们。
Bye bye.
再见。
Take care.
小心。
OK, let's see
好吧，让我们来看看
Gonna go back to the bedroom, guys.
要回到卧室了，伙计们。
So give me a second.
所以给我一秒钟。
Oh, oh.
哦，哦。
Oh. Well,
I guess saw the bedroom overlays.
哦。 好吧，我猜我看到卧室的场景。
Don't want to show off
for some reason. Unlucky.
出于某种原因不想展示给大家。 倒霉。
What the heck, brah?
什么鬼？
Yeah, they just don't want to show up
是的，他们只是不想出现
Bruh
All right,
好的，
And my music's not playing.
而且我的音乐没有播放。
It's, like, polaroid love
Oh, we gotta play for a long time.
哦，我们要玩很久。
I'm really glad that everyone enjoyed
that.
我真的很高兴每个人都喜欢它。
Sorry, I wasn't talking or chat too much
because I did want to focus on the game
抱歉，我没有说太多聊天，因为我确实想专注于游戏
and some just, you know,
有些人只是，你知道，确保我们通过了，
make sure that we were getting through
or, like, make sure that everybody was.
或者，比如，确保每个人都通过了。
I was giving, like, my full attention
to the the game in the collapsible aisle.
我全神贯注于可折叠过道中的比赛。
We were through some of the donations
我们现在来过一些捐赠和其他东西，因为我没有看到。
and stuff right now
because I didn't get to see that.
All of that while I'm
everything was everything was going down
所有这一切，因为所有的怪物，伙计。
because all the monsters, dude.
All the fucking monsters.
所有该死的怪物。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
The Miyagi, thanks for the $3
carbon boxes for any of you
that really got your heart off
I like Alec.
Having those little moments were far in.
Not just with me both. Like I can remove.
不只是我俩。 就像我可以删除一样。
It's really fun, right?
这真的很有趣，对吧？
I think that's like a part of, like,
the appeal, that scheme.
我认为这就像上诉计划的一部分。
When you do get separated, you're
kind of like forced to have a, you know.
当你分开时，你有点像被迫拥有一个，你知道的。
Of a little.
一点。
Fun interaction with whoever
与任何人进行有趣的互动
or what kind of buddy
you get some locked up with
或者你和什么样的朋友在一起
you uniting you for the sub.
你团结你为子。
Oh, there's a lot of subsidy,
a lot of sobs.
哦，有很多补贴，很多啜泣。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Thank you for all the subs
and for all the new subsidised channel.
感谢您的所有订阅和所有新的补贴频道。
It's means a lot.
这意味着很多。
And again, only thank you for the be great
hope your stream was good.
再次感谢您，希望您的直播很好。
Zoe, thank you for the talent.
佐伊，谢谢你的才华。
You come back after you finish your exams.
考试结束后你回来。
Good luck on your exams and let's everyone
that's, you know, also gone through
祝你考试顺利，让每个人，你知道，也经历了考试周。
exam week as well.
Kochel thank you for the bits and
Kochel 谢谢你的点点滴滴
the on the thank you for the bits as well.
也谢谢你的帮助。
Next time tonight was really fun.
下次今晚真的很有趣。
I hope you have fun too.
我希望你也玩得开心。
I'm glad you guys enjoyed it.
我很高兴你们喜欢它。
Also Gil thank you for the five guest
subs on antelope.
吉尔也感谢羚羊的五位嘉宾潜艇。
Thank you for the 200 bits on the monthly
for the five zone gift songs and koala.
感谢五区礼物歌曲和考拉每月200比特。
Thank you for the 1000 bits too.
也谢谢你的 1000 位。
Thank you. Thank you guys so much.
谢谢你。 非常感谢你们。
And Yuki thank you for the 1000 bits to
Yuki 感谢您提供的 1000 位
build up the paper.
建立纸。
Let me see I lost myself.
让我看看我迷失了自己。
Did lose myself.
确实迷失了自己。
Lose yourself in the music moment.
在音乐时刻迷失自己。
Leon Heights, Leon Hart,
thank you for the.
莱昂高地，莱昂哈特，谢谢你。
Oh, no. Yes,
it was your birthday. Oh, happy birthday.
不好了。 是的，那天是你的生日。 哦，生日快乐。
I didn't get to say happy birthday.
If you did say something last time.
我没来得及说生日快乐。 如果你上次确实说了什么。
My apologies, but, um.
我很抱歉，但是，嗯。
Yeah, I hope you had a great birthday.
是的，我希望你生日快乐。
And so I thank you for coming by our yummy
thank you for the bits as well,
所以我感谢你来我们的美味感谢你的位以及，
Linus.
莱纳斯。
Thank you for the 100 bits.
There's a lot of bits.
谢谢你的100位。 有很多位。
Oh, my God, Gail, thank you for another
five yourselves and love you.
哦，我的上帝，盖尔，谢谢你的另外五个人，爱你。
Thank you for the get our bits as well.
谢谢你也得到我们的东西。
In June, Herman,
thank you for the bits and file.
六月，赫尔曼，谢谢你提供的资料和文件。
Yeah.
是的。
Thank you for the bits as well.
也谢谢你的比特。
And Ernie, thank you for the deal.
还有厄尼，谢谢你的交易。
Now, uh, you asked me to sing a song.
现在，呃，你让我唱一首歌。
I don't think I can sing a song
考虑到我们一直在谈论很多声音，我认为我现在不能唱一首歌。
now given how many voices
as we've been talking a lot.
But next time maybe
但下次也许
Hebner is and he wrote 5000
bits of noise I'll be having a great day,
Hebner 是，他写了 5000 位噪音，我将度过美好的一天，
Adam.
亚当。
I thank you for the resolve.
我感谢你的决心。
And Buzzy,
thank you for the Zaino as well.
还有 Buzzy，也谢谢你的 Zaino。
And just thank you for this.
谢谢你。
And give yourselves off.
并放弃自己。
You're having a great day and have been
enjoying the stream and midnight.
您度过了美好的一天，并且一直在享受溪流和午夜。
Thank you for the 49 year
one gifts of Midnight Light
感谢午夜之光的 49 周年礼物
I'll know if you're still around.
我会知道你是否还在。
I appreciate it.
我很感激。
Thank you so much for all the gifts
I've been getting recently.
非常感谢你最近收到的所有礼物。
It's really sweet.
真的很甜。
And Zion Nazi.
还有锡安纳粹。
Thank you for the nine sirens as well.
也感谢您的九个警报器。
And QED with Zeno
还有与 Zeno 的 QED，我也非常感谢老师们
and I really thank you
for the teacher ones as well
good nights.
晚安。
Yeah. Thank you guys for coming by.
是的。 谢谢各位光临。
It means a lot
and hope you enjoyed the collab with Vox.
这意味着很多，希望您喜欢与 Vox 的合作。
I can remember.
我能记住。
Be sure to go support them
and follow their journals
一定要支持他们并关注他们的期刊
if you haven't done so already. OK
如果你还没有这样做。 好的
go. Thank you for the gift sub.
去。 谢谢你的礼物子。
And my god
我的上帝
papa I can't see you out. Name.
爸爸，我不能送你出去。 姓名。
I can't see that name
看不到这个名字
mandy.
曼迪
Thank you for the gifts for the five kids
loves.
感谢您为五个孩子所爱的礼物。
OK and fearless.
好，无所畏惧。
Thank you for the $10 donation.
感谢您捐赠 10 美元。
OK, tomorrow, guys, we are
好的，明天，伙计们，我们将有另一个直播，因为本周是我们忙碌的一周。
gonna have another stream
because this week is our busy week.
Tomorrow we're going to be playing power.
明天我们将发挥实力。
We're playing tomorrow.
Stanley Parable. Right.
我们明天玩。 斯坦利寓言。 对。
So reason why we re playing the game
is because we didn't get to finish.
所以我们重新玩游戏的原因是因为我们没有完成。
We didn't get to finish the game last time
because we got cuts.
上次我们没能完成比赛，因为我们被裁掉了。
Looking forward to the collab. Again.
期待合作。 再次。
Now we got some last time.
现在我们得到了一些最后一次。
We tried to play it because of like
a bunch of internet issues.
我们尝试播放它是因为一堆互联网问题。
So hopefully this time
there's going to be no issues.
所以希望这次不会有任何问题。
We try to play a game again.
我们尝试再次玩游戏。
Let's just hope it doesn't,
you know, mess itself up.
让我们只希望它不会，你知道，把自己搞砸了。
Also, ah ah ah ah.
还有啊啊啊啊。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
For that's l know
the club was very interesting.
因为那是我知道俱乐部非常有趣。
It was really fun.
这真的很有趣。
I love getting to play with these guys
我喜欢和这些家伙一起玩，我希望我们将来能玩不同的游戏。
and I hope we get to play a different game
sometime in the future.
It's until I say hey,
thank you for the five year old gift subs.
直到我说嘿，谢谢你五岁的礼物潜艇。
I got it here yeah.
我在这里得到它是的。
Pre manifest.
预清单。
No Internet issues.
没有互联网问题。
Please stream please
no more internet issues.
请流请不要再有互联网问题。
Excited for upcoming collabs
期待即将到来的合作
upcoming collabs.
即将到来的合作。
Yeah.
是的。
So I think we're going to be playing
ah, we're going to be having our Valens
所以我想我们会玩啊，我们将在周五与
collab with SHU, Lily Picchu
and a few other people on on Friday.
SHU、Lily Picchu
和其他一些人进行 Valens 合作。
Yeah, and on Saturday we're going to be
playing ah, Operation Tango with Yuuki.
是的，周六我们要和优树一起玩啊，探戈行动。
So yeah, hope
you guys are excited for that because men.
所以，是的，希望你们为此感到兴奋，因为男人。
Your next collab exclamation mark.
您的下一个合作感叹号。
That's really fun.
这真的很有趣。
You and Vox are really cute
你和Vox真的很可爱
I guess.
我猜。
I guess he's OK or whatever.
我猜他还好或其他。
I don't know.
我不知道。
I guess. I guess Vox is fine.
I don't know.
我猜。 我猜Vox很好。 我不知道。
He's, he's, he's all right or whatever.
他是，他是，他很好，或者别的什么。
Yeah, he's all right.
是的，他没事。
OK, but yeah,
I look forward to the collabs this week.
好的，但是是的，我期待本周的合作。
Finally gets to play something off shoe.
终于可以玩脱鞋了。
And we've always wanted to play around
together because he's cracked.
我们一直想一起玩，因为他已经崩溃了。
I, I feel like I'm just a
mid is out with the kids.
我，我觉得我只是一个和孩子们在一起的中间人。
So these days. Middleton whatever ends on
所以这几天。 米德尔顿无论如何结束
what else we're playing with
我们还和莉莉一起玩什么，因为我和莉莉真的很想一起玩一些东西。
lily because me and Lily really wanted
to play us some stuff together, too.
Like the other,
it'd be a league or violence,
和另一个一样，它会是联盟或暴力，
and she's inviting a couple other people,
too, so.
她也在邀请其他几个人。
Yeah, we'll see. We'll see what happens.
是的，我们拭目以待。 我们会看看会发生什么。
And, ah, on Saturday,
it's going to be my first call.
而且，啊，星期六，这将是我的第一个电话。
I was lucky.
我很幸运。
Yeah.
是的。
A lot of purple boys this week,
so that's really high.
本周有很多紫色男孩，所以这真的很高。
Bright purple club.
明亮的紫色俱乐部。
Lots and lots of purple
很多很多的紫色波尔卡舞曲。 很多紫色，
polka. Lots of purple,
which is fine.
这很好。
You know, I've been waiting for this
some day.
你知道，我一直在等待这一天。
I got to get,
我必须得到，你知道，Celine Boogie
you know, Celine Boogie and shoe together
for one, like for person collab.
和鞋子合二为一，就像人合作一样。
So it's just all, you know, for purple.
所以这就是紫色的全部。
OK, go live for Sunset right now.
好的，立即为 Sunset 直播。
So I'm going play an ad break,
所以我要播放广告插播，但对于这里的新闻，请务必关注我们的不和谐。
but for people for a news here,
be sure to follow our discord.
Janel Joyner, Joyner
Discord, discord, tragedy slash total.
Janel Joyner，Joyner
Discord，不和谐，悲剧斜线。
And that's where I'll post announcements
I might go live next time.
这就是我将发布公告的地方，我下次可能会上线。
If you're a subscriber to the channel
or on YouTube, you'll get additional
如果您是该频道或 YouTube
perks on us
sneak peeks and such like that.
的订阅者，您将在我们偷窥等方面获得额外的好处。
And also follow me on Twitter.
并在 Twitter 上关注我。
We're almost at 500 K on Twitter and also.
我们在 Twitter 上的访问量几乎达到 500 K。
We're all.
我们都是。
We've already hit like 400 K on YouTube.
我们已经在 YouTube 上达到了 400 K。
So thank you again for that big milestone.
因此，再次感谢您的这一重大里程碑。
Appreciate it, guys.
欣赏它，伙计们。
Been growing a lot lately and
I really hope that we can keep this up.
最近成长了很多，我真的希望我们能保持这种状态。
I'm going to. Upload a video later.
我要去。 稍后上传视频。
Today on YouTube. It's really good.
今天在 YouTube 上。 这真的很好。
Please
keep your eyes out for the new upload.
请留意新上传的内容。
OK, like, oh my.
好的，就像，哦，我的。
It's, it's some highlights
from the overcooked collab.
是的，这是过度烹饪合作的一些亮点。
They have a box,
so I think you guys would like it.
他们有一个盒子，所以我想你们会喜欢的。
It's really, it's really fucking cool.
真的，真的太他妈酷了。
So yeah, I'll upload that later today
like in about 6 hours.
所以，是的，我将在今天晚些时候上传，大约需要 6 个小时。
So keep an eye out for that. Purple Heart.
所以请注意这一点。 紫心。
Arts.
艺术。
Purple Hearts.
紫心。
Hearts. Purple Hearts.
心。 紫心。
All right, let me go
play an ad and I'll look for a song.
好吧，让我去打个广告，我去找一首歌。
OK, Barbie,
好吧，芭比，
OK, who's around.
好的，谁在附近。
All gossip to belong gossip.
所有的八卦都属于八卦。
The Nana are cute.
娜娜很可爱。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Mm mm mm.
嗯嗯嗯。
I'll send
我会发送
Margate.
马盖特。
They're gonna the nugget gone.
他们要让金块消失了。
I think we can go and read who?
我想我们可以去读谁？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I don't know.
我不知道。
Now, a lot of people are alive
at the moment.
现在，很多人都还活着。
I could just look around.
我只能环顾四周。
The tributes are maybe on
致敬也许在
Polly's still alive.
波莉还活着。
I mean, you can go read Polly again,
but we are afraid of Polly recently.
我的意思是，你可以再读一遍波莉，但我们最近很害怕波莉。
Jamie Foxx
杰米福克斯
yeah. Let me look around.
是的。 让我环顾四周。
Let's see,
who can we go and share some love with
让我们看看，我们可以去和谁分享一些爱
I i-i-i-i-i.
我-我-我-我-我。
I'm hot, hot, hot, hot.
我很热，很热，很热，很热。
You're so cute. I love you.
你太可爱了。 我爱你。
I love you guys. Yeah,
我爱你们。 是的，
I guess they beg for a second.
我猜他们乞求一秒钟。
I like a one big
some people like one big deal.
我喜欢一件大事，有些人喜欢一件大事。
Not, you know, that that way, but,
you know,
不是，你知道，那样，但是，你知道，
I mean, we're big, OK?
我的意思是，我们很大，好吗？
I don't see.
我没有看到。
And everybody.
和每个人。
No, I'm
不，我是一个全白人。
an all white.
You know what I think
你知道我的想法
I think we're just going to go and ride
我想我们只是去骑
actually, Louise live.
其实，露易丝还活着。
I don't think we've rated Lumi in a while.
我认为我们已经有一段时间没有对 Lumi 进行评级了。
Yeah, you know what?
是的，你知道吗？
Let's all.
让我们都。
Let's read Lumi.
让我们读一读卢米。
Momo is also live. Fuck.
莫莫也在现场。 他妈的。
Oh, there's only two options.
哦，只有两个选择。
OK, ok.
You know what? I'm just going to slide.
好的好的。 你知道吗？ 我只是要滑动。
Eeny, meeny, my name.
呸呸呸，我的名字。
Up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up.
向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上。
Let's read Momo.
让我们读一读莫莫。
Go, go read Momo.
去，去读陌陌。
I think they all be nice to check them
out there.
我认为他们都很高兴在那里检查他们。
They're an artist.
他们是艺术家。
They draw really cute boys
他们画了非常可爱的男孩和非常可爱的女孩。
and really cute girls.
You guys like you boys and girls, right?
你们喜欢男孩女孩，对吧？
OK, have a good night, guys.
好的，晚安，伙计们。
Sleep well and take care.
I'll see you tomorrow.
睡个好觉，照顾好自己。 明天见。
And thank you
for coming by to the collaboration.
并感谢您前来合作。
Be sure to support my friends as well
on their respective YouTube channels.
一定要在他们各自的 YouTube 频道上支持我的朋友。
They're wonderful people and it's
always a pleasure to play with them.
他们是很棒的人，和他们一起玩总是很愉快。
Cute puppy. Tilda
可爱的小狗。 蒂尔达
may I get a happy birthday from you.
祝我生日快乐。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Him there's it's your birthday.
他在那里，这是你的生日。
Happy birthday.
生日快乐。
Do to have birthday.
一定要过生日。
Happy birthday. To you.
生日快乐。 给你。
You know happy birthday. Man.
你知道生日快乐。 男人。
Thank you so much for,
you know, always supporting the general.
非常感谢你，你知道，一直支持将军。
And we have a great one.
我们有一个很棒的。
Take care. OK.
小心。 好的。
None of that.
都不是。
That's OK. Let's go.
那没问题。 我们走吧。
Good night, guys. Bye bye.
晚安，伙计们。 再见。
See you next time. OK.
下次见。 好的。
Love. I.
爱。 一世。